Chapter 124: Innate Spell

“I am almost used to the familiarity of my physical body, but I wonder what kind of innate spell did I obtain?”

After a long run, Leylin casually did a few standard swordplay movements. After having some understanding of his reinforced body, he shifted his thoughts to other matters.

According to the Kemoyin’s Pupil meditation technique and the introduction of the Book of Giant Serpent, Leylin had more understanding about the innate spell of Magi.

As far as regular Magi were concerned, most of them would choose a rank 1 defensive spell model and complement it with Grine Water to make a breakthrough.

Magi, who advanced with this method, had the smallest potential. In future, if they were unable to obtain more precious resources and a Rank 2 spell model that were suitable for them, they would have absolutely no hope of advancing.

As for some large organisation heads or first-rate Magi Families’ core members, they could practise the high-level meditation techniques.

Each level of the meditation technique could correspondingly promote the rank of a Magus. Moreover, the innate spell model found in each level is fixed.

In other words, it would be easy to guess a Magus’ innate spell just by looking at a part of the high-grade meditation technique that the Magus practised.

However, Warlocks were different; they were literally “dependant on the heavens to have bountiful crops”.

[TL note: (看天吃饭) – Depends on the heavens to have bountiful crops refers to luck.]

The formation of innate spells was heavily dependent on luck, purity and concentration of the blood essence of that bloodline.

Leylin knew his luck was only so-so, but he had got the blood essence of an ancient being — the Kemoyin Serpent! Thus, it should be highly compatible with this high-level meditation technique, and would thus be good for him.

After putting a thread of his Spiritual Force into the crystal, almost instinctively, Leylin knew the details of his own innate spell.

Eye of Petrification… and… Scales of Kemoyin!

Two innate spells! That’s right! There were two innate spells!

“Haha…” Leylin did not contain his laughter and let out a hearty laugh.

Concerning Warlocks, in the process of forming their innate spells, there was another scenario that could happen. That only occurs when the blood essence of the bloodline was extremely rich, almost the same as the origin of the bloodline. In such circumstances, there would be an additional innate spell.

Of course, the two innate spells Leylin obtained were Rank 1 Spells, not that he immediately advanced into a Rank 2 Magus.

Inside a Rank 2 Magus, they would have two innate spells too. However, one was a Rank 1 Spell while the other was a Rank 2 Spell! As for now, Leylin only had two spells that were of Rank 1.

Only after advancing to a Rank 2 Warlock, the Rank 2 innate spell would be formed!

As for the might of the Rank 2 Spells, they would naturally overpower the Rank 1 Spells.

Even so, having an additional spell will allow Leylin to be proud and unyielding amongst Rank 1 Magi.

This was equivalent to having an additional spell amongst the magicians of the same level, so naturally he had a great advantage.

Very soon, Leylin looked through the Kemoyin’s Pupil meditation technique and the Book of Giant Serpent, obtaining more information on those two innate spells.

“Eye of Petrification: A petrifying gaze will be emitted from the eyes, equivalent to the might of a petrification spell. The target will immediately be petrified. For more powerful beings, they would become rigid temporarily! Consumption: Spiritual Force 1, Magic Power 1!”

“Scales of Kemoyin: A layer of scales will form instantly providing a layer of defense. Physical defense: 25 degrees! Magic defense: 27 degrees! Consumption: Every 5 hours Spiritual Force 1, Magic Power 1!”

The consumption was calculated by the A.I. Chip. Leylin looked at it blankly.

According to the estimations of the A.I. Chip, these two innate spells were rather outstanding even amongst all the Rank 1 Spells.

If it was formed through a spell model, each of the spells required consumption of at least 10 points of Spiritual Force and Magic Power.

As for now, the consumption was one-tenth of before. This was the advantage of innate spells!

Furthermore, Leylin also felt that he could only spend a consumption of 2 points in Spiritual Force and Magic Power to have the Scales of Kemoyin always in effect.

At this moment, he roughly knew what the defensive forcefield, which always hovered around Magi, was.

Those were the innate defensive spells that they had activated around them perpetually. Any attacks, as long as they do not break through their innate spell defense, will never be able to cause them any harm.

“These two innate spells, one is for offense, and the other is for defense. With them, my current abilities, even amongst official Magus, can be considered excellent!”

Leylin estimated his might calmly.

As he chose the path of Warlocks which had good meditation technique and bloodline, the benefits he obtained right after an advancement greatly surpassed that from regular Magi.

As for those newly advanced Magi, they were not Leylin’s opponent at all. Only those who remained for some time inside the Rank 1 domain, those with their Spiritual Force and Magic Power almost reaching the limits and having recorded a large number of Rank 1 Spells, would be a force to be reckoned with for Leylin.

As for Rank 2 Magi? Right now Leylin was far from being their opponent. He did not even have much confidence in fleeing from them.

Every level between Magi had the difference like that between heaven and earth. It was not something that the bloodlines or better meditation technique could solve.

However, Leylin was extremely pleased with the present outcome.

After all, he had just advanced, and his path in future was broad.

With a joyful heart, Leylin took off the black robes that he put on and changed into a new set of clothes as he began to rearrange the things that he had brought along with him.

After wearing black robes, Leylin immediately hung the Fallen Star Pendant on his neck again.

“The defense of this pendant is rather low now! Most of the Rank 1 Spells are above 20 degrees. Any attack from an official Magus will be able to break the defense of this Fallen Star Pendant!”

“A.I. Chip! Establish mission and calculate the probability of improving the Fallen Star Pendant!”

[Beep! Mission establishing, beginning analysis…] The A.I. Chip carried out its mission, and also gave a stream of information for Leylin to check on the progress.

After advancing into a Rank 1 Warlock, the A.I. Chip that was connected to Leylin’s soul also obtained large benefits. Its calculation abilities were evidently more powerful than before.

After changing his robes, Leylin walked towards a small stream and looked at his reflection.

In the clear waters, a handsome, black-haired youth looked back at him, his body emitting a strange charisma.

“My hair, why has it turned black?” Leylin looked at his reflection, suddenly recalling the black haired snake woman inside his dream.

“Could it be…That the dream was not just an illusion?”

Leylin faintly guessed that it was the external changes caused by the changing of bloodlines.

Moreover, Leylin realised that there were some slight changes to his face.

Leylin had a rather average countenance at the start, at most having the looks of a youth. As of now, his eyes were brighter than before, his brows sleeker and the face turned more handsome than before. Combined with the dignity as a Warlock, there was a mysterious charisma to it.

“In legends, not only did Warlocks have powerful spells and physical bodies, each and every one was a handsome man or a beauty. So, this was all influenced by the bloodline!”

Leylin looked for a while more, before continuing with his preparations.

He was a Warlock, not someone who relied on his face to live, so being handsome or ugly had no difference.

……

Sapphire Lake, situated at the eastern part of the Poolfield Kingdom, was an extremely beautiful lake.

During winter, when the sun shines down from the sky, looking at it from a vantage point the azure lake seemed to be crystal clear like sapphire.

Not only that, there were even a special species of Blue Ice Fishes living in the Sapphire Lake. Its taste was extremely fresh and succulent. If acolytes were to include it in their diet often, it would have a slight boost in their meditation.

Hence, this area was controlled by a Magus Family.

Tyler Family was the Magus family which controlled the Sapphire Lake from nearby, to which Bicky belonged.

On this afternoon, there was a visitor inside the Tyler Family’s ancient castle.

“This is the ancient castle of the Tyler Family?”

Leylin looked up at the large stone castle.

The Tyler Family’s castle was erected on a cliff close to Sapphire Lake. Around it there was even a layer of poisonous cloud hovering around it, so very few people were able to come here.

Leylin sized up the giant castle. The large yellowish cliff had the depression and precipitation that withstood the test of time, silently standing here, bringing on a gloomy and declining feeling to it.

At the front of the castle were two fire breathing statues.

“The Tyler Family was known to have a period of golden age; one can tell just by looking at the outline of this ancient castle. A pity…”

Leylin touched the two lifeless statues and sighed.

Magus families which were slightly more powerful can lay a defensive spell formation around their fort. At the very least, the door guards should at least be guarded by magical creatures.

As for now, Leylin only saw two stone statues, and there was no aura of radiation coming from the ancient castle.

With Leylin’s strength as a Rank 1 Spell right now, he could completely demolish this castle.

It seemed like the news of the Tyler Family of not having a Rank 1 Spell was true.

After lingering around the front of the castle for a while, the people inside it were shocked.

*Boom!* Huge stones axles revolving sounded, and the two sides of the door opened slowly.

“May I ask…Who are you looking for?”

A chirpy birdlike girl’s voice sounded. From behind the door, a green haired girl roughly 8 to 9 years old peeked out.

“I am Leylin, looking for your family’s head!”

Leylin caressed the little girl’s hair.

“My Lord! I’m sorry my Lord, this is my daughter, I did not pay attention to her for a while…”

At this moment, a middle-aged man with the energy waves of a Level 2 Acolyte finally appeared from the door, looking at Leylin in fright.

“Kushy! Hurry up and bow!” The middle-aged man hugged and placed the girl behind him, making her do a bow.

From the middle-aged man’s knowledge, although Leylin seemed rather young, he had the terrifying energy waves which had far surpassed himself.

“He’s at least a Level 3 Acolyte!”

He would never be comparable to a Level 3 Acolyte that this young man was.

Moreover, the Tyler Family was in decline for a long time already, so they did not have much backing.

Chapter 125: Tyler Family

“Hi! I’m Leylin, here to meet the head of the Tyler Family!”

Leylin repeated his intent.

“Leylin? Leylin!” The middle-aged man repeated the name before his expression changed suddenly, before asking in a more respectful tone, “May I ask if you are the Leylin from the Abyssal Bone Forest Academy?”

“That’s right!” Leylin affirmed.

The smile on the middle-aged man’s face grew in splendor; it seemed more forced than good-natured as he said, “Welcome to the Tyler Family! I will immediately announce your arrival…”

After learning of Leylin’s identity, this man’s manner changed.

The man had heard Leylin’s distinguished name many times; not only was he Bicky’s junior, and Professor Kroft’s accomplished student, as well as a genius in the Abyssal Bone Forest Academy, rumor has it that he has astonishing talent in Potioneering and advanced to Level 3 Acolyte, with potential to become a Magus before turning 20 years old.

However, the most important thing in the letter was, Leylin had promised to compensate the damage caused by Bicky.

Thinking of this, although the man appeared deferential on the surface, there was a trace of greed within the nervousness he felt.

“I feel very upset regarding the matter of Miss Bicky…”

The man squeezed out some tears as he said, “Previously, Miss Bicky was a very obedient child, but now…”

“I am well aware of all this, bring me to see your family’s head!”

Leylin gaze turned frosty, and the middle-aged felt a chill run down his spine. He felt as if he were being stalked by an extremely dangerous beast.

“I shall go at once! I shall go at once!”

Following which, he took hold of his daughter and immediately vanished behind the door.

More than ten minutes later, Leylin had already been received within the great hall of the castle and was in the presence of the Tyler Family’s patriarch.

“Distinguished guest! I am Tyler Family’s patriarch — Johnson Tyler! I welcome you to the Tyler Fort, and I hope that your stay here will be pleasant.”

The patriarch of Tyler Family was known as Johnson Tyler. He was an old man wearing a formal black attire and had a head of lustrous, silver hair which had been carefully combed. But his eyes appeared a muddy white.

[Johnson Tyler. Level 3 Acolyte. Strength: 1.9, Agility: 2.5, Strength: 2.0, Spiritual Force: 13. Magic Artifact on target’s body can unleash attacks up to three times, each producing a force of more than 20 degrees. ]

A trace of blue light, invisible to others, flashed through Leylin’s optic nerve, as the A.I. chip scanned and recorded the information regarding the Tyler Family’s patriarch.

Then, Leylin’s nose twitched; he had smelled a deteriorating and decaying odor emitted from that Patriarch’s body.

It was clear from the many wrinkles on this patriarch’s face that this man did not have many years of his lifespan left.

Too weak! This kind of strength, in front of Leylin, was the same as grinding an ant to dust.

Leylin swept a glance from top to toe of the patriarch and found that the Magic Artifact he wore was somewhat decent.

If a Level 3 Acolyte were allowed to pay an extremely high cost, they could attain a Magic Artifact suitable for a Rank 1 Magus. It seemed that this was something that was passed down the family.

However, from what Leylin saw, instead of one hit, he needed just two to take Johnson down.

The disparity between their strengths was too high, and Leylin did not feel inclined to gossip with him.

“My purpose for coming here is: as stated in my letter from before, I will pay a sufficient cost to compensate for the Rainbow Potion, and you all must pardon Bicky of her crimes.”

Leylin ignored the angry look upon the patriarch’s face and found a seat to sit down on.

Seeing that Leylin did not show any courtesy, a trace of fury flashed in the eyes of Johnson Tayler, but he quickly suppressed it.

But within his mind, he felt aggrieved, as if a large stone had been placed in his heart. Since when could a Level 3 Acolyte act this brazenly inside the Tyler Fort?

However, Johnson had, after all, had plenty of experiences during his span of life. Moreover, he could always detect a trace of danger from Leylin.

The many years of training made Johnson put a smile on his face as if he was not even the teensiest bit angry due to Leylin’s actions.

“The Rainbow Potion is a precious ancient treasure, right now many of its ingredients are hard to find…”

“I will give the Grine Water in exchange for it!”

“Wh… What…” Johnson stammered immediately, and an unbelievable expression filled his face.

“I said that I will give the Grine Water for it! That would be enough to exchange for the Rainbow Potion, would it not? After all, the Rainbow Potion’s effect is to complement the success rate with the Grine Water. When comparing the treasures, the Grine Water is much rarer!”

Leylin interlaced his fingers as he smiled, immediately throwing out a temptation that Johnson could not refuse.

The composition and effect of the Grine Water had long since been analysed by the A.I. Chip during this period.

Only that the brewing process required a lot of ingredients to carry out. Leylin did not have that many ingredients on him, so he could only make do with the analysis.

According to the A.I. Chip’s calculation, the effect of the Grine Water was to burn the life force of the acolyte and breakthrough the Spiritual Force bottleneck.

This method had very evidently had a huge backlash and after effect.

As for Leylin, although he burnt a little of his life force during his advancement, it was very soon replenished by the Giant Kemoyin Serpent’s blood essence.

Leylin guessed that it was the tremendous vitality found within the Giant Kemoyin Serpent’s blood essence that substituted his own life force that was burnt during the advancement.

Hence, after advancement, right now Leylin had at least 500 to 600 years of lifespan according to the A.I. Chip.

As for normal Rank 1 Magus, even if they used many methods to prolong their life, they would at most live up to 200-300 years old.

Moreover, after Leylin advanced to a Rank 1 Warlock, the Grine Water that had effect for acolytes was not of much use to him anymore.

Leylin had planned to exchange it for some resources, but now it seems that using it as compensation was not a bad idea too.

As expected, after hearing the words ‘Grine Water,’ this patriarch Johnson began to pant.

There hasn’t been the birth of an official Magus in the Tyler Family for over 300 years!

Moreover due to the decline of the bloodline and lack of resources, the Tyler Family members had very little chance of advancement. They did not even have a Level 3 Acolyte where the academy chairman could fawn upon to sign a contract. So naturally they had no way of obtaining the Grine Water.

As for other families, they were extremely pleased to watch the decline of the Tyler Family before stepping in to swoop all of their resources. Thus, there weren’t any good-natured people to aid them.

Although the Rainbow Potion was good, it was not rarer than the Grine Water.

After all, the Rainbow Potion’s effect that could raise the success rate was rather hard to determine. It would at most raise it by 20%.

However, the Grine Water was different! With it and an outstanding acolyte, the Tyler Family could definitely try to cultivate their own official Magus! They did not have to be restrained by other contracts!

However, although this wily fox Johnson was extremely willing, he still put on a difficult expression.

“When Bicky stole the Rainbow Potion, she even ruined some treasures…”

Leylin shook his head. He had already predicted such a scene before his advancement.

Even if he was willing to compensate, he would definitely be ripped off.

As he was merely a Level 3 Acolyte, yet the other party was from a Magus family. Even if it was a declining family, their power is still to be reckoned with for any regular acolytes.

If Johnson did not ruthlessly try to knock off a huge amount from Leylin, then he would have lived to this ripe old age in vain.

“Enough!” Leylin’s face darkened.

At the same time, a mighty Spiritual Force energy wave emanated from his body.

*Hu Hu Hu!* As if a strong gale had swept past, the cloth on the tables and curtains on the windows let off a rattling sound.

The mighty Spiritual Force of an official Magus mercilessly swept through the fort as frightened wails were heard.

Many youths in the Tyler Family fainted on the spot, without making a sound.

They were all regular humans without any resistance to Magus’s methods.

As for those Level 1 Acolyte and Level 2 Acolyte, they were not any better off. Their faces were reddened as they tried their best to support themselves and not fall onto the ground.

“Of… Official Magus?!”

As if seeing a ghost, Johnson’s mouth gaped widely, large enough to stuff several duck eggs inside.

After which, fright surfaced on his face as he immediately knelt onto the ground, “Most respected Lord Magus! Please be appeased and let my family members off!”

Seeing that Johnson, who had wanted to rip him off just a few moments before, was now kneeling on the floor like a frightened rabbit, Leylin harrumphed coldly. However, he still retrieved his Spiritual Force.

Leylin only did a slight test earlier with some restrain. If not, the regular humans in the fort would have all died from the radiation.

Johnson shuddered as he knelt, his inner heart wildly howling, “This Spiritual Force definitely belongs to an official Magus! It can’t be wrong! He… He is only 18 at most!”

Once he thought of having offended such a genius official Magus, Johnson desired to cry yet there were no tears. He even had the notion of committing suicide.

“Bicky! Yes! His relationship with her is good!” Johnson’s eyes lit up as he suddenly thought of this point.

“Quick! Quick bring Bicky here! No… Maid! First, bring her for a bath…”

After seeking approval from Leylin, Johnson scampered off and ran into a large hall, screaming at an acolyte that was sprawled on the floor.

After which, Johnson put on a flattering smile as he bowed towards Leylin. “My Lord, do you have any other orders?”

Looking at his shameless behaviour, Leylin was somewhat speechless.

After all, this was Bicky’s family; he could not do things to the extremes.

After Johnson accompanied Leylin in trepidation for another dozen minutes or so, Leylin finally got to see Bicky.

Bicky had apparently gone for grooming; her hair even had water droplets which had not been dried properly. She wore a white gown, her expression, however, did not seem very well, having huge eye bags and dark circles around her eyes.

“You… You’re Leylin?!”

Bicky looked at Leylin who stood there unyieldingly and then at her family head who was smiling obsequiously, suddenly feeling dizzy as she tried to connect the dots…

Chapter 127: Defeat

The moment Clayde declared his name, Leylin gave out an order silently.

“A.I. Chip, Scan the target in front of me!”

[Beep! Mission establishing, scanning in progress… A defensive forcefield around the target detected, unable to collect data!]

As expected, the A.I. Chip still gave the same answer.

“Which is to say, if I broke through the layer of forcefield, I’ll be able to scan it?”

Leylin used an immense force on his legs and charged towards Clayde like a bullet.

*Bang!*

Leylin’s right hand bulged, and the strength of his fist reached 7.1 degrees, smashing onto Clayde’s chest.

The sound like a hammer striking at leather sounded. With a huge spark, Clayde was sent flying backwards.

Leylin stood at where Clayde stood originally as he looked at his arm.

Black scales appeared above the skin. On the scales, there were tiny traces of flames continuously flickering.

[Data of target’s defensive forcefield obtained, comparing to database!]

[Determined target’s innate spell as high-temperature forcefield, creating a flame of 24 degrees to burn objects within its vicinity!]

[Target’s forcefield damaged: 4.6%. 20 more strikes are estimated to break the defensive forcefield!]

The A.I. Chip reported to data to Leylin.

“Cough cough…”

At this moment, Clayde who was lying on the ground got up. There was soot on his somewhat dirtied face.

“What tremendous speed and strength! A pity that you only advanced not too long ago, so how many Rank 1 Spell could you have learnt? Two? One? Or do you only have your innate forcefield?”

Clayde patted his chest and yelled.

Often Magi, who just advanced were in their weakest stages, not to mention memorising a few Rank 1 Spells. More often than not, they could not afford a single use scroll or Magic Artifact either.

After Clayde had finished yelling, he chanted an incantation immediately.

The energy particles in the air changed visibly, shining a dazzling yellow light.

“This might, at least 20 degrees…”

Leylin’s expression turned solemn. Right now his Kemoyin’s Scales resistance was only at 27 degrees. It was considered pretty good amongst newly advanced Magi, but it could not fend off all of the Rank 1 Spells.

Only by continuously tapping into the strength of the bloodline, the Kemoyin’s Scales would become stronger.

As for now, once the opponent’s attack exceeded 27 degrees, it would immediately break through his forcefield.

“I can’t let him cast any spells!” Leylin’s pupils contracted

*Crash!* The black light flickered, and finely articulated scales surfaced on his body, even his face was included.

In an instant, Leylin was covered by a layer of snake’s scales. He right now looked half snake and half human.

The blackness of the scales had an ancient aura and reflected a cold, glossy light which sent Clayde’s heart racing a little faster.

“Such a defensive forcefield? So strong!”

“Die!” Leylin shouted, and he moved quicker than before, charging towards Clayde.

Clayde snorted, and a layer of green light appeared on his body which turned into thorns as they blocked Leylin.

*Bang!* *Bang!*

Leylin’s expression did not change as he swung his fists. After two punches, the thorns shattered.

After covering himself with the Kemoyin’s Scales and coupling it with his Strength, Leylin was now like an ancient creature, with an aura that was unstoppable.

Clayde face turned rather unsightly after seeing Leylin breaking through the thorns like wild grass.

“You damned worm! What other methods you have, use them all now!”

Leylin howled and felt every drop of his blood being set ablaze. It made his appetite to battle even more intense than before.

“Damn it!” As Clayde chanted, he kept on changing positions. Moreover, he even activated several Magic Artifacts to block Leylin from advancing.

Although the might of these low-grade Magic Artifacts were not strong and mostly restraint type, breaking through them still required some effort.

After Leylin broke through another layer of ice, Clayde finally finished his incantation of a Rank 1 Spell. An enormous blue fireball was sent flying towards Leylin.

*Boom!*

After the heat wave had dissipated, the mud around the area melted, creating a large pit.

“Haha… No one could survive after being hit by my corrosive fireball!”

Clayde laughed heartily. The joy of killing a genius early in developing stages swelled in his chest.

However, Clayde’s expression very soon changed and he hurriedly retreated several steps, as if he saw something unfathomable.

“How… How’s this possible, he’s actually still alive?”

In the sea of blue fire, a human figure parted the flames and walked out from it.

At this moment, Leylin’s clothes were thoroughly razed to ashes, revealing his scaly body. The A.I. Chip’s warning continuously rang within his ear.

[Host has suffered an energy attack! Element: Fire, Acid. Estimated power: 20 degrees. Actual power: 26 degrees. Host’s innate spell, Kemoyin’s Scales, was activated! Energy consumed: 34%. No harm dealt directly to Host!]

“It’s actually an attack of 26 degrees. Just one more degree to breaking my defense!”

Leylin had some lingering fear before it manifested into a stronger killing intent!

*Bang!* His figure flickered and appeared right in front of Clayde. The fist covered with scales punched Clayde’s chest with a tremendous might.

*Crash!* A bright red flame rose from Clayde’s chest, engulfing Leylin’s fist within.

*Bang!* Clayde’s face turned red as he was sent flying backwards.

Leylin stepped forward, ignoring the flames on his body as he throttled Clayde.

“Run! Why don’t you run again?”

Leylin’s expression turned malevolent, ramming fists after fists on Clayde’s body.

*Bang!* *Bang!* *Bang!*

Massive explosions sounded continuously, and the earth quivered as if there was an earthquake.

Finally, after some time, Clayde cried out, and the flames on his body disappeared.

[Target’s defensive forcefield broken, acquiring data…]

The A.I. Chip’s voice intoned, bringing Leylin, who was somewhat frenzied back to his senses.

“What happened? I was actually this impulsive and reckless?”

Thinking of how he did not dodge or block as he smashed his opponent’s defensive forcefield, cold sweat trickled down Leylin’s forehead.

Normally he would have never acted that way. Not to mention the final barrage of attack like a madman was not his way of handling things usually.

[Clayde Lilytell. Strength: 4.5, Agility: 3.7, Vitality: 5.6, Spiritual Force: 31. Elemental Essence Conversion: Fire! Progress: 30%…]

Clayde, who was lying on the ground, had his data extracted and sent to Leylin.

“Elemental Essence Conversion? No wonder his acidic fireball was so strong!” Realisation appeared on Leylin’s face.

After advancing into a Rank 1 Magus, if one wanted to advance again, the basic conditions was to complete the Elemental Essence Conversion!

At this time, the importance of having an affinity for elements was finally shown. If one does not choose the highest affinity element to cultivate in, it’s impossible to have the Elemental Essence Conversion progress to get over 80%. Which is to say, they would never be able to advance into a Rank 2 Magus!

Furthermore, with the increase in Elemental Essence Conversion, it would improve the might of spells of that particular element.

Originally Clayde’s acidic fireball only had a power degree of 20. However, after the 30% Elemental Essence Conversion it reached 26 degrees, almost breaking Leylin’s defenses.

Moreover, the multiplier effect could only be applied on one’s chosen element affinity. For instance, Clayde’s fiery spell could have a 30% multiplier, but the spells of other elements would remain the same. In cases such as Water or Ice Elements, the power might even be reduced.

However, why would Magi gifted with the affinity of Fire element even use Water and Ice spells?

Blue light flashed in Leylin’s eyes continuously. This was the first report of data he obtained from a Rank 1 Magus. It could aid his understanding towards himself, complete the database and even compare the stats to a Warlock’s.

“You… Kill me now! The Lilytell Family will never let you off!”

When the innate defensive forcefield of Magi was broken, they would also suffer damage on their sea of consciousness. At this moment, Clayde was already near his last breath.

“Why do I suddenly feel like the villain?”

Seeing Clayde, who put on a ‘loyal and unyielding’ expression, Leylin wanted to laugh.

“You wish for death? It’s too early for that!”

Leylin forcefully chugged a potion down Clayde’s throat. Clayde’s eyes turned white immediately, and he fainted. There were even some forbidden runes appearing on his body which isolated the branding of spell formation on his body.

After hastily cleaning up the area and packing his spoils, Leylin picked Clayde up and left the area.

With the Vitality of 8.5, even if Leylin were to run for a day he would not be exhausted. The reason why he chose to ride a horse previously was just for convenience.

After running wildly for several li, Leylin then had the notion of checking his body status.

It worried him that he lost his control in the battle earlier.

“A.I. Chip! Bring out the data monitored earlier and investigate the cause of losing control!” Leylin managed to simmer down only after sitting in a refreshing stream and cooling off.

[Beep! Mission establishing! Bringing out monitored data!] The A.I. Chip intoned icily, not bringing any trace of emotion.

[14 Hours 23 Minutes, abnormal activities observed within Host. Blood flow increased by almost 45%, activity of the Giant Kemoyin Serpent blood essence significantly increased!]

The A.I. Chip reported the series of data to Leylin. Through a comparison, there was a strange stimulant released by the Giant Kemoyin Serpent’s bloodline during the battle earlier. It was similar to doping, and the stimulation caused Leylin to lose his rationality.

“This is the origin of the Warlocks’ emotional aftereffects?”

Leylin muttered, immediately asking, “A.I. Chip, bring out the best solutions to solve this!”

[Beep! Method 1: Forsake the Giant Kemoyin Serpent! Method 2: Use the Serenity Potion! Method 3: …]

Very soon, the A.I. Chip presented the possible solutions to Leylin.

Chapter 129: An Incurable Curse

“Yes, I remember it clearly. That meat vendor wore a black hood, his dishevelled hair covering half his face. There was a metal hook on his left hand…”

The housekeeper vividly recalled the memory of the meat vendor.

“This is really strange!” Fayle shook his head and looked at the little girl beside him.

“How is the construction of your mind runes coming on?”

“I have already constructed three but I can’t seem to construct the fourth! Also, inside the <All Living Things> biology…” The little girl reported back meekly.

“So it’s like this?” Fayle interlaced his fingers.

“Your progress is too slow. Tonight you must come to my room, I’ll be personally ‘coaching’ you!”

“Yes, Mentor!” The little girl replied softly.

*Dang Dang Dang!*

The copper grandfather clock in the hall gave a resounding boom and the clock struck 12 times. The sky outside had already darkened and one could slightly see some visible blue stars.

“It’s already so late, why isn’t Nida here yet!”

Fayle slammed opened the door with a loud bang, annoyance evidently seen on his face.

“Nida! Nida!” Fayle began to shout.

His voice echoed throughout the silent hallway, reverberating for a long distance.

The surroundings were in dead silence. Fayle could even hear his own breathing and the flow of his blood.

“Housekeeper! Housekeeper! Maids! Where are they?!”

Impatience began to show on his face, as he hurriedly put on his outer garments and stepped outside of the door.

*Dong Dong Dong!* The sound of leather boots striking the floor was heard.

A black figure walked slowly towards Fayle.

“Who? Who’s there?” Fayle called out warily, a silver short sword appearing in his hands.

No matter how Fayle shouted, the footsteps maintained a constant pace that was neither too fast nor slow and walked towards him.

When the black figure drew closer, Fayle could almost see the full appearance of the figure.

It was a middle-aged man who wore black robes. On his chest hung the trademark apron that butchers wore. On his head was a black hood, his dishevelled hair covering most of his face. What was especially attracting was his empty left sleeves. Instead, only a rusty metal hook was seen at the end of the sleeve.

This description perfectly fit the one that the housekeeper mentioned earlier.

*Weng!*

The silver short sword glinted and flew directly to the man with a whistling sound.

*Pu!* As if piercing through an illusion, ripples appeared on the meat vendor’s body and the silver short sword went through it.

“Illusory spell?!” Fayle’s lips started to move as he chanted a high pitched incantation.

*Xiu Xiu!*

A mixture of the sound of a quick panting on a metallic flute and like the sound of a rusty knife scraping against a metal continuously sounded, causing ripples in the air.

After the whistling sound ended, it was still absolute silence in the tall tower, as if the world only had Fayle and the meat vendor in it.

The black robed man immediately raised his left hook and swung it at Fayle.

*Bubble!* From Fayle’s body, a layer of fluid formed transparent water shield, blocking the metal hook’s assault.

This was Fayle’s innate spell which was finally activated in crucial moments!

Seizing this opportunity, Fayle hurriedly chanted and multiple frost spikes were shot towards the man.

*Pu!* *Pu!*

The frost spikes entered the body and countless blood was spurted out. However, the man in the robes seemed not to be conscious about it, even his expression did not change, like that of a zombie who did not know pain. He continuously brandished his metal hook, causing ripples after ripples on the water shield.

“Fuck, what is this damned thing?”

Fayle struck at the man in the robes for several more times before his mental fortitude seemed to be on the verge of collapse.

No matter if it was physical or magical attacks, it all amounted to nothing when they landed on this man’s body.

Instead, every strike from this metal hook continuously consumed the energy needed to maintain the innate spell. Fayle could clearly feel that if the opponent were to attack several more times, his innate spell would completely shatter.

“Run!”

Under the life or death crisis, Fayle felt as though he returned back to his acolyte days where he had to greet every Magus respectfully, before turning around and running away.

*Dong Dong Dong Dong!*

Hearing the approaching footsteps of the man wearing the black robes resounding in his ears, it made Fayle run even faster.

20 metres!

10 metres!

5 metres!

1 metres!

Fayle grabbed hold of the large main doors of the tall tower and dashed outside.

*Peng!* The door behind was closed shut. To Fayle’s utter dismay, he actually appeared inside his bedroom once again. Also, there was only a 3 metres distance between him and the man now!

“Damn it! Damn it! Damn it! What’s happening?”

Fayle gritted his teeth and continued to run, yet returning to his room every time.

Finally, tears and mucus ran down Fayle’s face as he returned yet again to his room and closing the door shut tightly.

*Dong! Dong!* The knocking sounds that were the footsteps of the death god. Fayle felt that every step was stepping directly on his heart.

“Mentor! Papa! Mama! Save me!”

Fayle crouched behind the door, crying like a little child.

As if hearing his pants, the booming footsteps halted. Finally, when it was just one step away from the door, it disappeared….

Fayle was pale stricken as he waited for a good half hour before his trembling hands opened the door, only to see no one there.

“Hu….”

Fayle exhaled a large breath and collapsed to the ground as if all the bones had been removed from his body.

“It’s finally gone! I must write a letter to Mentor tomorrow and let him check what had transpired…”

Fayle closed the door.

Suddenly, just when he had turned around, a dishevelled face appeared right before him.

What came closely following it was a black metal hook!

*Pu!* This time, the black metal hook directly broke through Fayle’s defensive forcefield and gouged his right eyeball out.

The moment his eye was hooked out, black and red viscous liquid mixture flowed out.

The man seemed to be unsatisfied as his sent his hook at Fayle’s head again!

*Bang!* Fayle’s body was sent to the ground from the force. The metal hook bore through his brains deeply. Fayle was still unconsciously writhing before he lost all signs of life.

*Brush!*

Following wipe, the man in black robes immediately withdrew a greasy bone saw and began to expertly dissect Fayle’s corpse.

After the dissection, Fayle’s muscles had been completely stripped clean. The colour of it too turned even redder, revealing the veins of blood, similar to that found in the beef tenderloin!

Winding the time back to yesterday morning.

The black robed man knocked on the kitchen’s door of the tall tower, revealing a hideous smile. “Do you want to buy meat? I have good tenderloin steak for sale…”

……

Several li away from Fayle’s tall tower, Leylin looked at a spell formation with a solemn expression.

In the centre of the formation, a black flame was flickering, in the heart of it was the scene of Fayle’s ending.

With the images continuously flashing by, Leylin stared at the image without blinking, mysteriously chanting at the same time.

Finally, after the black robed man killed Fayle and scoured his flesh clean, Leylin’s expression loosened.

*Pa!* The black coloured spell formation collapsed.

The surroundings immediately quietened down and a dead silence followed after.

*Dong Dong!*

The black robed man inside the image earlier appeared in front of Leylin.

“You’re here now?” Leylin seemed to have expected it, with no shocked expression on his face.

“Shihiohj” The black robed man let off several indiscernible words and charged towards Leylin.

*Bang!* The black metal hook was grabbed by a scaly palm.

Leylin faced the black robed man and could even see the crude construction of his facial features.

“Look into my eyes!” Leylin spoke gently with a hissing voice like that of a snake’s.

The black robed man unconsciously looked into Leylin’s eyes.

At this moment, there were some phenomenal changes in Leylin’s eyes — both his eyes turned into vertical pupils, letting off the crystal glow like amber!

Innate Spell—Eye of Petrification!

*Ka-Cha!* *Ka-Cha!* A grey-white colour extended from the man’s face to his whole body.

Several seconds later, the black-robed man completely turned into a grey-white statue.

“Seize the chance!” Leylin picked up the grey statue and tossed it into the heart of the black formation!

*Crash!* The stone statue shattered in pieces, from it grayish-white gases appeared as if wanting to form into a human figure.

“Dust to dust, earth to earth, return to where you came from!”

Leylin chanted in the ancient Byron language.

A black circular whirlpool suddenly appeared in the middle of the formation. With a huge suction force, it sucked in the grey-white gas in.

After the whirlpool disappeared, Leylin then heaved a sigh of relief and collapsed to the ground.

“Such a curse cannot be easily activated by anyone!” Leylin smiled wryly.

After destroying all traces of Clayde, Leylin hurried along the way as he brewed the Serenity Potion, finally suppressing the emotional fluctuations that Warlocks had.

However after some thought, he wanted to see things come to an end. So he decided to kill Fayle before escaping the area.

The Lilytell Family would definitely have a wanted list on him through the Abyssal Bone Forest Academy, so what if he were to add another pursuer, the Purple-Gold Flower Family to it? Anyway, it was the wanted list put up by Abyssal Bone Forest Academy, so having one or two families chasing after him had no difference.

Furthermore, Leylin saw a Rank 1 curse spell inside the Book of Giant Serpent. It could completely kill Fayle with no one the wiser, and no trouble would come after him.

However, Leylin did not think that this curse was this malicious, it would even reverse the sorcery on the spell caster!

This left him with some lingering fear, especially after seeing the monstrous way Fayle was killed.

These Rank 1 Spell requirements were extremely harsh.

First of all, he had to cast a Darkness body and use the opponent’s trace of scent, if not it could not be casted.

Afterwards, it required one to know the basics of spirit bodies. Fortunately, Leylin had amassed some experience in Extreme Night City, so he picked it up rather quickly.

Finally, this curse had a limitation which was the distance. Moreover, it could only attack a target that had lower stats than the spell caster.

Chapter 131: Pursuers

Previously, Leylin held himself back from taking action, not because he was afraid of doing something, but because he didn’t want to be inconvenienced.

However, this girl in front of him had something that interested him. Furthermore, once his research was a success, he would greatly benefit from it.

It was only natural, that he now intended to take action.

However, for prudence’s sake, he still chose to lay low on the sidelines and observe the strength of his enemies first.

If their might was average, he would definitely not be modest. He would immediately abduct or coerce the girl to follow him and not be afraid of the pursuers.

If they were too strong, he could only give up. In any case, the world was so big, and she was not the only one with a Warlock’s bloodline. There might be very few of them on the South Coast, but there were definitely many in the Central Continent.

Several days later, the horse carriage entered the district of York City.

This was already along the borders of the Inlan Dukedom. As for the old man, his anxiety had already intensified to the maximum. Most of the time he would stay on the horse carriage, seldom leaving it. He even closely guarded the little girl by his side, as if being afraid of something.

The hazy night had dyed the sky an overcast grey. Only somewhere far away in the horizon was there a little light.

The horse carriage stopped by the roadside, and the weary passengers began to alight, and then sat in a circle around a bonfire for refreshments and rest.

After so many days of travel, the people in the horse carriage also got close with each other. Especially that little merchant, who took out a flute and played an upbeat tune and the beautiful woman beside him followed suit by performing a gorgeous dance.

There were several middle-aged men who took out wine flasks from their sacks and walked forward to the beautiful woman to ingratiate themselves. As for that woman, she chuckled, seemingly not rejecting these suitors.

After the atmosphere reached a climax, the people began to sing and dance. Even the horse keeper gulped down several mouthfuls of strong wine and had a tinge of red at the end of his nose.

Leylin reclined against the trunk of a tree, his hand holding a wine flask from which he drank occasionally. He shot a glance inside the horse carriage and grinned.

Although the sky had already dimmed tonight, the old geezer still urged the carriage driver to move on.

However, travelling in the middle of the night was extremely dangerous. Hence, this suggestion was rejected by carriage driver and all of the passengers.

That old geezer’s expression then was really a sight to be seen.

Furthermore, tonight the old geezer had decided to stay within the horse carriage, not even letting his granddaughter leave half a step away from the horse carriage. Ugly rumours had already begun to have gossiped amongst the travellers.

However, Leylin knew that this pair who pretended to be a grandfather with his granddaughter was afraid of pursuers, that’s why they hid in the horse carriage. Looking on at the situation, the pursuers were almost arriving too.

No, they were already here. Leylin turned his head, and with the A.I. Chip, he saw several acolytes, who did not hold back their energy waves radiation, hiding in a dark corner.

Looking at the strength of the energy waves, there were all Level 3 Acolytes.

*Bang!*

A red arrow was released and it directly shot through the brains of a muscled, half-naked man who was dancing by the fire.

“Ahhh!” The blood splattered onto a woman nearby. Her expression turned sluggish, only letting off an ear piercing scream several seconds later.

“Bandits!” “Help!” Various cries sounded in the camp.

As for the carriage driver, he very quickly donned a leather armour and crouched, hugging his head and not moving at all.

The horse carriage providers had a promise with the nearby bandits, that they would only rob the passengers. As for the drivers, the bandits would often let them go scot-free — after all, they would not have much money on them.

However, tonight the carriage driver’s plans were in vain.

*Xiu!* Another red arrow was shot, directly piercing through the driver’s neck! He clutched his neck with both hands, his eyes popping out and frothing blood at the corner of his lips. His mouth gaped open and close for air as if wanting to enjoy the freshness of the air one last time before he died.

“A sharpening spell added on the arrow? Interesting!”

Beside the chaotic campsite, Leylin was still reclining against the tree. He gulped down another mouthful of wine, his expression appearing indifferent.

At this moment, his lax behaviour was vastly different from the current situation, yet nobody was paying him any attention.

The second arrow obviously caused greater chaos within the camp. Be they man or woman, young or old — they were all wildly running away.

Several minutes later, the campsite that had once had a lively and jovial atmosphere, now only had a crackling bonfire and several wine flasks which had been forsaken.

*Crash!* 3 figures wearing black robes appeared from within the forest.

Leylin’s outstanding vision allowed him to see clearly the appearance of this trio.

There were two men and a woman, all of them were of middling years. The woman had applied a very thick layer lipstick, which seemed like she had just drank a mouthful of blood.

These 3 were obviously not students of an academy. Their attire were rather casual, however, there was an image of a dodo-bird stitched on their robes, seemingly a family emblem.

These were the acolytes nurtured by a family.

Some of them from Magi families, who had poor aptitudes, could not be accepted into academies, so they could only be nurtured by their families themselves.

Most of them could not even advance to a Level 3 Acolyte, so the majority of them remained as a Level 1 Acolyte or Level 2 Acolyte.

These 3 who were able to advance to Level 3 Acolytes, either had good aptitudes or were expelled from an academy or had graduated.

“Miles, come out! We know you’re inside the horse carriage!”

The three of them took on a triangular formation to surround the horse carriage, and a silver-haired man laughed smugly.

*Boom!*

What replied him was a burning red fireball.

*Pa!* As the middle-aged man dodged the fireball, the horse carriage suddenly shattered and a black figure with a smaller figure wrapped on his lower body rapidly sneaked past the gap that the middle-aged man exposed.

“Thinking of escaping?” The woman smirked and hurriedly chanted an incantation, casting a speed reducing spell.

A layer of murky green shone on the black figure and his speed dropped drastically.

“Xiu!” The eyes of the third person who held a bow flashed, and immediately he fired another red arrow.

*Pu!* The arrow bore into the left chest of the black figure, drawing fresh blood from it. The black figure groaned and fell to the ground, revealing the face of the white-bearded geezer.

“Run! Why don’t you keep running?”

The man, who had been the target of that fireball shot previously, was in a miserable state. Seeing the old geezer on the ground, his expression turned malevolent and he drew out a curved blade, hacking at the old geezer Mile’s left leg.

*Ka-Cha!* The old geezer’s left leg was immediately chopped off.

“Ahhh!” The little girl fainted immediately after having blood spurting on her.

“Such a beautiful little girl, killing her outright is such a pity!” The man who held the bow licked his lips, revealing a lusty grin. “Why don’t you let me have some fun first?”

“It’s your call, we still have plenty of time!”

It was very obvious that these three acolytes did not have any regard for the old geezer, Miles, at all. They were extremely relaxed and had their guard down.

In fact, this was the reality. Miles was only a Level 3 Acolyte and the little girl was not even an acolyte. Such a line-up can be easily destroyed by just sending one Level 3 Acolyte.

It was only for added assurance that 3 such acolytes had been sent.

When the bowman grinned lewdly, a lazy voice sounded.

“I say, you guys seem to have forgotten about me!”

Leylin flung the flask away and announced himself in a crisp voice.

“You… You actually didn’t run away?” The other male acolyte was somewhat shocked. Normally, wasn’t the reaction of people, after seeing someone get killed, to run away? Much less to mention encountering magicians of the sorts.

“Just right, I wish to loosen my muscles after pursuing this old geezer. Leave him to me!”

The only female acolyte among them looked at the handsome Leylin and her eyes flashed. Her mouth gaped open and close with the heavy lipstick as if wanting to swallow Leylin immediately.

Right now, Leylin’s charm factor had increased significantly after advancing to a Warlock. Along the way, he met many girls who cast flirtatious glances at him. However, meeting this kind of elderly woman, he felt rather disgusted.

“My apologies, but I don’t have any interest towards aunties!”

Leylin spoke very ‘sincerely’, turning the face of this female acolyte red.

“Brat! I will let you feel the most unbearable pain on earth. An hour later, if you don’t prostate yourself like a dog in front of me, you will have my admiration!”

The female acolyte looked at Leylin as if she wanted to bite a piece of meat off him that very instant.

“No need for that, if you don’t prostate yourself like a dog right now in front of me, you will have my admiration!”

Leylin’s eyes flashed icily as he dispelled the concealment spell. An immense force field immediately surrounded the area of the horse carriage.

“Of… Official Magus!” The eyes of the male leader of the trio popped out as he collapsed feebly onto the ground.

“Lo… Lord! Please pardon our accidental intrusion!”

The bowman acolyte, too, no longer had any interest in defiling the little girl. He immediately knelt in front of Leylin, cursing the damned bitch thousands and tens of thousands of times.

“How is it?”

Leylin looked at that female acolyte with a toying expression.

“Lo… Lo… Lo…“ The female acolyte also fell to the ground, her jaws trembling, not being able to speak a single word.

“Lord, we are from the Yale Family… Our family head is also an official Magus!”

The leader noticed that Leylin’s gaze was hostile, immediately bringing up the backing of his group.

“Yale Family?” Leylin shook his head, indicating that he did not recognise this name.

Leylin had already scrutinised the large families around the Poolfield Kingdom before and did not recall any Yale Family of the sorts.

“A.I. Chip, scan database!”

[Beep! Yale Family: Situated in the Denisque Province of the Inlan Dukedom. The family head’s name is Sam Yale. Originally an acolyte from the Sage Gotham Hut, he advanced to an official Magus at thirty years of age. Information source: History of Magi families, page 1928!]

An extremely simple introduction. From the information recorded on the A.I. Chip, it seemed like a newly founded Magus family which was completely reliant on a Magus who had shockingly advanced as an acolyte.

It was far from being comparable with the Lilytell Family and only slightly stronger than Bicky’s family. There was not much backing and easily classified by the Magus World as the nouveau rich.

“Wait! Wait! I have the secret imprint of our family’s head!”

Seeing that Leylin was about to take action, the leader immediately shouted and ripped his clothes apart.

Chapter 133: Elemental Essence Conversion

In a somewhat dilapidated campsite.

Erected in the middle of the campsite was a tent made from cowhide, and it had a sturdy look to it.

Beside the tent was a small fire, where bright yellow flames continuously lapped against a metal pot hanging above it.

A broth that contained some pieces of mushroom and beef-jerky was boiling in this metal pot.

Around the fire, there were many pieces of forked branches, which was used to grill several small fishes. There was also some barbecued meat, which frothed with tiny bubbles as the golden-yellow grease continuously dripped down, while the aroma of sizzling meat permeated the air.

The little blonde girl sat by the side, looking at the piping hot food, involuntarily gulping down her saliva.

Thereafter, she turned her head to look to the side.

There, on a patch of grass, a handsome, black-haired man sat cross-legged on a white sackcloth as he practiced meditation.

This person was, naturally, Leylin.

After bringing Ivy along for quite some distance, he initiated a break to rest awhile.

Although Leylin, with his current Vitality, would not be tired even after journeying for 7 days and nights, the little girl would definitely not be able to keep up.

Moreover, he had to take out some time every day to cultivate with his high-grade meditation technique.

The meditation technique that he had gotten was the Kemoyin’s Pupil meditation technique that was compatible with his bloodline. Adding on to the A.I. Chip’s purification of the blood essence, his progress in meditation was extremely fast.

“Eyes are the windows of the soul, by concentrating your sight with the Kemoyin’s Pupil, you will rediscover yourself – Norco Curadu Sfar!”

This was what Leylin saw repeatedly at the start of the Kemoyin’s Pupil meditation technique.

And now, Leylin shut both his eyes and felt that he was staring right into a pair of vertical pupils that were amber-like.

Darkness with burning flames seemed to engulf his body.

As for Ivy who had been watching Leylin, she realised that a black and red mist emerged from Leylin’s body. This mist revolved around Leylin, not dissipating.

The strands of mist began to converge, forming the shape of a small snake, coiling around Leylin, at the same time spitting out its scarlet tongue.

The small snake continuously roved around Leylin, finally coiling on Leylin’s face, turning into a strange mask. A wave of darkness energy particles was continuously absorbed by the mask.

A dozen minutes later, the mask shattered, turning into black gases and threaded into Leylin through the seven orifices.

“A.I. Chip! Scan my current data!” Leylin opened his eyes wide and commanded in silence.

[Beep! Leylin Farlier. Rank 1 Warlock, Bloodline: Giant Kemoyin Serpent. Strength: 7.1, Agility: 6.7, Vitality: 8.5, Spiritual Force: 28.2, Magic Power: 28 (Magic Power is in synchronisation with Spiritual Force). Status: Healthy]

[Host completed a level of high-grade meditation technique. Spiritual Force increased by 0.005. Elemental essence conversion: Darkness. Progress: 1%]

“Every time I meditate there will be a definite increase in the Spiritual Force, it’s not bad already!”

Leylin nodded his head in satisfaction.

Increasing the Spiritual Force of magicians would only get more difficult in the long run. Especially for official Magi, the meditation techniques they used as acolytes were completely irrelevant now. If they did not have high-grade meditation techniques, they could only rely on external resources to increase their Spiritual Force.

Resources which were able to create an effect on official Magi were extremely rare even on the South Coast. Hence, after advancing into a Rank 1 Magus, many of the Magi found it extremely difficult to advance again.

Only those who had cultivated with the high-grade meditation techniques would be able to maintain their progress.

However, every level of high-grade meditation techniques was extremely challenging. The first level was still alright. However, after that, every level required tens of hundreds of years.

As for the special characteristics of high-grade meditation technique, they would only get more difficult the further one is. According to Leylin’s guess, after the third level, a Magus required thousands of years to advance to the next level!

Hence, many Magi could not advance in time before their lifespan was up, and died from old age just like that.

“A.I. Chip, calculate how long more I need to reach the criteria to advance and become a Rank 2 Warlock, given my current progress!”

[Beep! Mission establishing, gather Host’s data, simulating conjecture…]

[With the Host’s current stats, estimated to reach the requirements of advancement into a Rank 2 Warlock in 14 years and 7 months!] The A.I. Chip’s voice intoned.

“That’s quite long! However, compared to those regular Magi who cannot advance in tens of hundreds of years, it seems like my current situation is pretty good!” Leylin’s brows furrowed but quickly relaxed.

From the graphical analysis made by the A.I. Chip, the increase in Spiritual Force that the high-grade meditation technique gives will also begin to slow down after reaching a certain extent. Moreover, the elemental essence conversion progress will only get slower as he progresses. This was the reason stopping Leylin from advancing quickly.

According to the A.I. Chip’s estimates and the Book of Giant Serpent implicit divulging, Rank 2 Magus advancement criteria was to have a Spiritual Force of at least 80, and the elemental essence conversion to be over 80%.

These two conditions alone have stumped many genius acolytes before.

The Spiritual Force requirement was still alright. Whether it was about cultivating in high-grade meditation techniques or finding large amounts of resources which could stimulate the Spiritual Force, it could still be solved over time.

However, elemental essence conversion was a different story altogether. First of all, if the Magus chose the wrong energy particles, then he would find it extremely difficult to exceed an elemental essence conversion of 50%. To be specific, one has to first choose the energy particle with the highest elemental affinity to get the elemental essence conversion to over 80%.

Moreover, this was only the most basic criteria. To some heirs of large families and true geniuses, they would waste their potential if they advanced with an 80% elemental essence conversion. Only by getting a 90% elemental essence conversion and above, would they face fewer bottlenecks while advancing to become a Rank 2 Magus.

These were all mentioned in the Kemoyin’s Pupil.

In addition, some regular Magi had to solve the problem of obtaining a Rank 2 spell model. If they were unable to find one which complements their Rank 1 innate spell, mishaps will occur during the inscribing of their Rank 2 spell model, such as having their brains exploding.

Hence, those magicians who used Grine Water with spell models to advance, their path in future would become extremely narrow.

Although his progress was extremely fast already, Leylin still felt somewhat pressured deep down.

He had utterly offended the Lilytell Family. This was a large-scale family with the family head existence that could rival the Abyssal Bone Forest Academy’s chairman.

That was a Rank 2 Magus or an expert close to that level!

As for Leylin right now, once he was to meet someone like that, his only outcome would be death!

Advancing into a Rank 1 Warlock only let him have the simplest form of self-preservation. To be able to live free in the future in broad daylight, he had to at least be a Rank 2 Warlock to be able to handle the pursuers from Abyssal Bone Forest Academy.

After having access to the high-grade meditation technique, Leylin realised that magicians who cultivated with the high-grade meditation techniques also required some resources.

This was because some precious resources could increase the progress of meditation.

There were several ingredients that could complement his meditation — that was mentioned in the Kemoyin’s Pupil meditation technique.

Hence, he was somewhat impatient to hurry and reach the Ennea Ivory Ring Tower, situated within the domain of Light Magi.

It had the largest, free trade market and collection centre. Leylin could definitely rely on it to get his resources and improve his progress quickly.

“Lo… Lord… The broth is ready…”

Seeing that Leylin had finished with his meditation today, Ivy hurriedly scooped a bowl of broth and brought it to Leylin.

“You have worked hard!”

Leylin smiled at Ivy and took the bowl.

Ivy looked at Leylin’s unfathomable eyes that had endless depths and stared at them blankly, her eyes lifeless.

“This is…” Leylin had a slight shock and immediately reached out a hand glowing in white light as he tapped Ivy’s forehead.

“Lord! Just now…” Very soon Ivy recovering, yet she did not dare to look into Leylin’s eyes again.

“This is a circumstance of mine which I did not restrain properly earlier. In the future do not be this careless again…” Leylin understood what had just transpired.

It was the result that the A.I. Chip indicated earlier, elemental essence conversion progress: 1%.

When Magi continued to improve their progress of elemental essence conversion, the Spiritual Force radiated will bring about a strong power which was attributed to the elements.

Ivy losing her bearings earlier was considered as a mild effect.

If Leylin had had an elemental essence conversion of 50% and above, and by not restraining himself, in that situation Ivy would most likely have been attacked by the Darkness energy particles and thus would have become a shrivelled corpse

As for different elemental energy particles, the final elemental conversion would also be reflected differently.

For example: if a Magus chose the Ice energy particles as the attribute to cultivate with, he would be able to freeze the Spiritual Force of anyone who stares into the said Magus’s eyes.

As for those who cultivated in Fire energy particles, enemies who probed their Spiritual Force would be burnt, even suffering from a backlash.

Leylin cultivated in the Darkness energy particles, which was emphasized more towards the aspect of a person’s Spiritual Force and soul. In later stages, if regular humans were to come into contact with his high-density elemental essence conversion, their soul would immediately perish, their physical bodies decomposing into a shrivelled corpse.

“Sorr…sorry!” Ivy lifted her skirt and bowed, hurriedly moving out of the way.

Seeing that the girl was unharmed, Leylin nodded his head and poured the meat broth into his mouth.

The warm savoury meat broth laced with bites of fresh mushroom excited Leylin’s palette.

“This tastes pretty good! I guess you have not eaten yet too?”

Leylin looked at Ivy, now with his eyes back to normal there was no chance of causing unintended harm anymore.

“Yes!”

Ivy softly replied. She helped herself to some dry rations and a bowl of broth. Together with Leylin, they feasted.

Leylin looked at Ivy and let out the slightest sigh of relief.

If this was the past, Ivy would surely be treated like a princess by her own family.

However, this present way of living by roughing it out in the open would surely help her to mature quickly.

“After you are done eating, come find me in my tent. I need a sample of your blood!”

Leylin gobbled his food quickly and said to Ivy.

The underlying reason he saved Ivy was not due to kindness but to use her Warlock’s bloodline for his research.

Chapter 134: Upgrade

Out in the wilderness, the night was freezing cold. Even the blazing bonfire was unable to dispel the chill in the air.

Inside the tent, however, it was much warmer — enough to make one feel slumberous.

Leylin waited for a few minutes and saw Ivy’s silhouette shivering as she slowly got into the tent.

You could tell she was very nervous, her hands clutched tightly to her skirt hems, exposing her pale white ankles.

Fear was inscribed on a pair of beautiful eyes.

But it was as if her body was controlled by someone, as she advanced towards Leylin, step by step.

“Don’t worry! It’s very simple to take a sample, and it will not cause you any harm!” Leylin said, to try and pacify her.

“Please pull up your sleeve!”

Upon hearing Leylin’s words, Ivy hesitated for a moment. She then pulled up her sleeve, revealing a length of her jade-white arms.

“It’s going to hurt a little, but don’t be afraid!”

Leylin took out a huge needle-like item from behind him and spoke gently to comfort the little girl.

Unfortunately, the little girl started to tremble even more severely.

With the girl’s arm in one hand, Leylin stuck the needle into the exposed vein on her arm.

Ivy’s face winced when the needle entered her vein as if she was about to cry but still forced herself to stay strong.

After drawing enough blood from Ivy, Leylin sent chased the little girl back to her own tent.

“Why does it feel like I was bullying a little girl?”

Leylin rubbed his chin as he looked at the needle in his hand.

No matter what, it was unsettling being on the receiving end of a “You bullied me” look given by a little girl.

“A.I. Chip, begin the experiment, and prepare the microscope…”

After being in a daze for several seconds, Leylin came to his senses and his expression turned solemn. His slender hands began to move expertly like butterflies treading and dancing through flowers.

Next morning, Leylin saw a pink liquid within the vulcanised tube and his expression looked unclear.

“A.I Chip, scan!” A blue light glowed within Leylin’s eyes, falling onto the test-tube.

[Beep! Detected a trace of ancient creature’s bloodline in the drop of blood. Pala Night Hawk! Unable to purify further!]

The A.I. Chip ended its feedback, turning Leylin’s face darker.

Ivy did carry a trace of an ancient bloodline, a pity that the inheritance of the Pala Night Hawk bloodline ends with her. The traces had already thinned to the absolute minimum and only a bit of aura could be extracted from her blood but it did not have many uses.

“From this density, even if Ivy was completely exsanguinated, or made to bleed some blood from time to time, it wouldn’t be enough to even purify a single drop of the pure ancient bloodline.”

However, Leylin did not feel particularly disappointed or anything similar to disappointment.

It wasn’t that he would be successful with every single experiment of his. However, if one doesn’t even try, there will be no chances of success.

He had learnt this lesson back in his previous life.

“Moreover, this bloodline that carries a trace of the ancient creature’s aura, adding on with some of the broken magic artifacts pieces I’ve gotten in the secret plane, they could aid in the modification of the Fallen Star Pendant…”

A notion rose in Leylin’s mind.

The Fallen Star Pendant was only a low-grade magic artifact which was useful back in his days as an acolyte. However, for Leylin now it was somewhat of little value.

The A.I. Chip had been given the task of researching the possibilities of upgrading the Fallen Star Pendant, and now it seemed to have borne some fruits.

However, Leylin was a Warlock now, if he was able to add some power of the bloodlines on top of the other ingredients needed for the upgrade, it would definitely achieve a better potential!

“A.I. Chip, establish this mission as a subtask: calculate the possibility of adding Ivy’s bloodline into the Fallen Star Pendant!”

[Beep! Mission established, classified in a subfolder under the mission of upgrading the Fallen Star Pendant!]

The A.I. Chip intoned promptly.

Although he was unable to purify the ancient bloodline, but he had obtained an ingredient that could complement the upgrade of the Fallen Star Pendant. So Leylin felt that he had reaped a huge benefit and hence his mood was uplifted, too.

The next morning, he even greeted Ivy during breakfast, which was something that he seldom did. This caused the little girl to be confused and out of sorts. Seeing this scene, Leylin laughed inwardly.

After eating breakfast, Leylin brought the little girl and carried on with the journey.

He even bought a horse carriage while making a stop at a town, putting out the misery of the little girl, who had had to walk all along.

The reason why he did this was not because of kindheartedness. It was because the little girl provided him with blood every day, and while Leylin brewed some potions to replenish the blood, her mental state did not seem very well as her face was as pale as dead people.

After purchasing the horse carriage, Leylin led his life even more leisurely. He would journey when the sun was up, and at night, he would continue to extract the essence from the Pala Night Hawk bloodline to upgrade the Fallen Star Pendant.

“Dawn’s Peak! According to our speed, we should be able to reach the Great Canyon Margaret tomorrow!”

Leylin pointed to a mountain which peak was amongst the clouds as he spoke to Ivy behind him.

“… ”Ivy looked at the landmark in front of her and clutched her knees in silence.

His eyelids hung low, not knowing if it was because of the fears of what the future would bring, or because of bewilderment.

“The ingredients gathered are now sufficient. I will upgrade the Fallen Star Pendant tonight!” thought Leylin.

Naturally, he controlled the pace of the journey, so he was able to obtain enough blood right before reaching the Great Canyon Margaret tomorrow.

In the middle of the night.

The surroundings were dark and serene, and from time to time the sounds of insects and howls of wolves could be heard.

Ivy was in a deep sleep within the tent beside the horse carriage.

As for her who was in deep slumber, her eyelids twitched continuously, as if dreaming of a nightmare.

Seeing her in this manner, Leylin heaved a sigh of relief and returned to the horse carriage.

“A.I. Chip, simulate the start of the experiment!”

Leylin set up an illuminating spell and lit the interiors of the horse carriage.

In the middle, several wood boxes were set up in a flat platform with some apparatus displayed on it.

In the middle of all was a silver grey cross, with several fragments of jewels on it.

This was the original shape of the Fallen Star Pendant. Ever since he had advanced into a rank 1 Warlock, he had rarely used it.

The Fallen Star Pendant’s physical and magic defense were both valid for at most 20 degrees. As for any rank 1 spell cast by an official Magus, it would exceed these limits.

Hence, Leylin would think of methods to raise the capabilities of the Fallen Star Pendant, hoping for it to be of use again.

[Simulation for experiment over, success rate to be 87.9%.] After a flash of blue light, the A.I. Chip reported a string of data back to Leylin.

Right now, the A.I. Chip could simulate most parts of the experiment and produce the success rate. This meant that as long as Leylin followed the steps given by the A.I. Chip, he could attain the same success rate that was indicated.

As for those magicians who painstakingly gathered ingredients yet not knowing their success rate, the A.I. Chip’s capabilities showed that it could save Leylin a huge amount of resources.

So much so that this capability could even be employed during an advancement.

If the A.I. Chip’s success rate was too low, Leylin could give up on the advancement and amass more resources before trying to breakthrough. This was much better after comparing this with other magicians who try to breakthrough in the dark and even suffer from a backlash.

“First of all, it’s to separate the ingredients for the magic artifact!”

Leylin looked at the other items placed on the platform.

There was half a dagger and a broken arm. These spoils of war were obtained by Leylin during the bloodbath in the secret plane. Although some time had passed, the arm still shone with a silver light, completely concealing the fact that it was a human arm made of flesh.

“Silver-Claw Saurun actually imbued his magic artifact into his own arm, what a crazy fellow!”

Leylin picked up the silver arm and placed it within a golden funnel, setting it alight at the bottom.

A golden yellow flame continued to swirl in the funnel, turning the funnel red.

The blazing temperature continued to radiate from the hand. Once Leylin noticed the change, he began to drip some blue fluid, drop by drop, onto the arm.

The blue liquid fell onto the arm, turning into red immediately, extending it towards the whole arm.

The temperature increased yet again.

Leylin was ecstatic as he placed a transparent beaker below the funnel.

*Pitter-patter**Pitter-patter* Droplets of silver liquid continued to drip down.

Very soon, this liquid filled up half of the beaker.

Leylin’s right hand rapidly gathered some powder and jewels and tossed it into the beaker, while his left hand reached for a metal wire and stirred the beaker.

The powder and jewels melted immediately upon entering the beaker, and the silver liquid began to turn muddy.

A dozen minutes later, there were two obvious layers in the beaker. On top was a liquid the colour of flesh, and at the bottom, it was a layer that was pure silver in colour.

……

After being busy for a while, Leylin looked at the several ingredients laid in front of him with a gleeful expression.

The formerly mentioned dagger and silver arm had not turned into two blocks of black and grey metal as they shone with lustre.

As for the Fallen Star Pendant, it was now submerged within a beaker. The beaker was half filled with pink blood with the scent of orchids

“Keliesiding Guraweier Alongsuo….”

Leylin chanted an incantation as he made a cut on his finger, dropping a dark red drop of blood into the beaker.

*Bang!*

Once the dark red blood entered the beaker, it immediately had a chemical reaction.

The pink coloured gases continued to rise and the blood began bubbling.

Threads of red liquid continuously climbed onto the Fallen Star Pendant, turning the original silver-grey colour into a dark red colour.

After the blood in the beaker completely evaporated, the Fallen Star Pendant turned into a dark red cross.

“What’s next is to modify the runes inscription!”

Leylin’s expression turned extremely solemn. This was the most crucial step to upgrade the Fallen Star Pendant!

Chapter 135: Angler Town

[Modifying the Fallen Star Pendant’s runes inscription, increasing illusory runes to make Host compatible with its control.]

A.I. Chip sounded at this very moment.

Blue light flashed across Leylin’s eyes, and many transparent patterns began appearing on the surface of the Fallen Star Pendant.

Next, all he needed to do was to proceed with the modifications according to the transparent patterns on the Fallen Star Pendant.

And the A.I. Chip could assist Leylin during his inscription process, so there would not be any mistakes.

Using a pair of tweezers to fish the Fallen Star Pendant onto a white cloth, Leylin took out a solid inscription pen and started to finely carve on the surface of the cross.

At this point, his hand was like a steel sculpture — it was as steady as possible, without even a single tremor.

This required an enormous amount of attentiveness and endurance and consumed a lot of time and energy.

As time passed, beads of sweat started to drip from Leylin’s forehead.

[Fallen Star Pendant’s runes modification is a success! It has newly added reinforced runes, energy dissipation runes, extension runes…]

As he listened to A.I. Chip’s reminders, Leylin revealed a smile.

Immediately, he picked up another inscription pen from beside him. It had grooves on its body and was just as solid.

“Next, I shall fill in these carvings!”

Leylin lit two beakers and proceeded to melt the raw materials he had separated earlier from the magic artifacts. Those beakers now contained only liquids.

Subsequently, Leylin followed a fixed proportion and mixed the two liquids together.

Leylin played with the grooves on the pen and it split open, revealing a hole to pour water into.

Immediately, he poured the concentrated silvery black liquid into the body of the pen.

Fine runes started to twinkle and flicker around the inscription pen, producing an enchanting radiance.

With a face of satisfaction, Leylin pushed the pen nib against the tracks of the inscriptions carved earlier on, repeating the process again.

But this time, the pen left silvery black liquid in its trail, filling every notch of the inscription.

After finishing the last stroke, Leylin sized up the completely reformed cross and nodded his head with satisfaction.

“Activate!”

Leylin used the ancient Byron language and read out two words.

*Pong* A cylindrical beam of gray light began to emit from the cross. Threads of silver light were moving along the rune inscriptions that Leylin had carved earlier.

As the silvery gray rays kept blending, they got brighter and eventually engulfed the Fallen Star Pendant in it.

When the rays completely vanished, the Fallen Star Pendant had changed in appearance entirely.

It only retained the shape of the cross but was bulkier than before.

Also, it had changed from a silvery black colour to a shade of dark red.

On the surface there were numerous fine and detailed rune inscriptions, causing the original fragments of gems to be concealed beneath it.

Leylin then took the dark red Fallen Star Pendant, noting its weight was heftier than before.

[Beep! Fallen Star Pendant’s upgrade is now successful with those middle-grade magic artifacts! Current Physical Defence: 24, Magic Defence: 25!] A.I. Chip sounded again, bringing Leylin the good news.

“Physical defence rose from 13 to 24, and magic defence rose from 15 to 25! Not bad, really not bad!”

This range almost surpassed the Scales of Kemoyin’s defense. It was almost equivalent to gaining another innate defensive spell. Leylin was naturally very pleased.

But there were a lot of other magic artifacts that have better innate spells. The would have another increase in power and defense in the future.

As for the Fallen Star Pendant, unless he finds even more precious materials to upgrade, it would be difficult to increase its defensive characteristics as per Leylin’s requirements.

Hence, in the long run, concentrating on his own innate spells was more dependable.

“In the south coast, acolyte ranks use beginner grade magic artifacts. Level 1 Magi use middle-grade magic artifacts and the occasional beginner grade magic artifacts. Only the extremely powerful level 2 Magi have the capability to get hold of high-grade magic artifacts!”

Leylin thought of the information he saw from the Book of Giant Serpent.

Although the era of the great Magus Serholm was somewhat distant, the general distribution of power and culture throughout the south coast could be seen.

Now that the Fallen Star Pendant had been promoted to a middle-grade magic artifact, it’s effective for Leylin as a level 1 Warlock. This, of course, put him in a good mood.

……

The Great Canyon Margaret spanned across the Inlan Dukedom and several nearby kingdoms. It was also a place that was necessary to travel through to enter the Ennea Ivory Ring Tower, controlled by the Light Magi.

Of course, this was only with regards to Magi.

Ordinary citizens of this dukedom seldom step out of the kingdom, from their birth until their death. Even their mercenaries only received missions within the kingdom.

Mercenaries and wandering bards who had travelled the vicinity could use the experience they gained to flaunt or gain respect.

“Great Canyon Margaret is filled with danger. Even a hastened journey takes several months…”

Leylin slightly frowned as he thought over the information about the Great Canyon.

Transportation in the Magus World was inconvenient, causing a great deal of inconvenience for magicians who travel far and wide.

Of course, he had another choice — he could ride in an airship.

But unfortunately, not only was this mode of transportation costly, there was only a fixed number of dates per year for its departure. Furthermore, there were stringent requirements for passengers. They needed a local family or an organisation to be their guarantor.

Leylin was already on the wanted list of Abyssal Bone Forest Academy. So naturally, he wouldn’t wait for the airship and had to rush by foot.

“Your parent’s good friend, that Aunt Marian, where does she live?”

Leylin asked Ivy, who was behind him.

“Angler Town beside the Great Canyon!” Ivy said in a low voice.

Leylin nodded. This girl’s blood had greatly helped him. Besides, there was no clash in the itinerary. Under such circumstances, he didn’t mind lending a helping hand.

“Well then! I will first send you to Angler Town to find your Aunt Marian!”

Leylin told Ivy.

“L…Lord! Is it okay if I followed you around?”

After what Leylin said, Ivy stayed silent for a moment before asking this question.

“Oh? But why? I did not treat you very well!”

Leylin was surprised. When he crossed over, he was from nobility, a respected Magus acolyte. He’d never taken care of anyone before. Ivy even suffered a small illness on this journey. Things would have taken a bad turn if Leylin wasn’t a Potions master.

Moreover, every now and then, Leylin had to take from Ivy a big tube of blood. He simply could not comprehend why this girl would still want to continue following him.

Maybe, I was too charming? Or was she so oppressed that twisted feelings began emerging?

Leylin let his imagination run as he rubbed his chin.

“Is this for revenge?” But, he soon figured out what the girl had in mind.

Ivy lowered her head, obviously tacitly agreeing.

“Ivy you should be aware that due to the genetic constitution of your family, before you can find the lost meditation technique, you’ll never be able to be an apprentice. Even I can’t do anything about it!”

Only because Ivy and Leylin were inheritors of the same ancient bloodline, he felt that he should clarify it with her.

“I know! But I request from you to get me vengeance! For this reason, I’m willing to suffer any consequence!”

The little girl made her last effort.

“My apologies. Magus advocate fair transactions. And regardless of your wealth, health or spirit, it is not enough for me to deal with another official Magus!”

Leylin did not hesitate to reject the girl’s plea.

Upon hearing Leylin’s ruthless yet very real words, Ivy’s shoulders trembled, hugged her knees as she sat in the carriage and fell silent.

Soon, the carriage entered Angler Town.

This was obviously a Magus gathering area. There were little, almost none, ordinary people, and the architecture of the buildings around portrayed a gloomy style that appeared cold and weird. Even the atmosphere was filled with a moist putrefying stench.

“This kind of place doesn’t seem very good!”

Leylin frowned. According to his experience, these kinds of dangerous district beside the major transportation road, dwells those who harbors bad thoughts, Magus who have nowhere to turn to. Simply put, wanted criminals!

Leylin felt bad for Ivy. They followed the street and eventually got to the number plate Ivy had reported before.

Appearing in front of Leylin was a dilapidated two-story loft. Black wooden planks on the verge of collapsing revealed a decadent atmosphere.

The first floor had been converted to look like a grocery store. But it didn’t seem to be doing very well, and the people who entered were but a few.

Parking the carriage at a side, Leylin pulled Ivy’s hand as they entered the grocery store.

“Marian! Is Marian here?” Leylin yelled out. He did not attempt to conceal the energy fluctuations in his body as the road to Angler Town was unimpeded.

“Respected Magus Lord, how may I serve you?”

Before Leylin could finish his words, an obese middle-aged lady with a greasy grey apron and thick makeup made her way out, expressing humility and flattery.

If it wasn’t for the level 3 acolyte’s aura she had on her body, with this kind of image, she looked exactly like an unkind housewife.

“Is this Marian?” Leylin asked Ivy who was standing at a corner.

“Yes… Yes!” Ivy nodded her head. Leylin finally understood why Ivy was so unwilling.

By the looks of it, Ivy’s parents probably did not have anyone else to turn to back then. Hence, they allowed their housekeeper to send Ivy to Marian.

“This is Ivy! Any impression?” Leylin pulled Ivy in front of him.

“John’s daughter?!” Marian’s face changed slightly. “About the Langster family matter, I feel sad…” Marian said as she squeezed out a few drops of tears.

“…Back then, I just happened to pass by and the housekeeper begged me to bring her here…”

Leylin briefly spoke about the cause and effects.

Upon hearing that she has to offer shelter for Ivy again, Marian’s face completely turned embarrassed, as if things were already difficult for her. Leylin reckoned, if he wasn’t around, Ivy would have already been chased away.

“Since it is what the Lord wants, then alright!” She replied with an ugly smile after struggling for a long time.

Chapter 139: Sentinel Slate

The rain drizzled continuously, as if like a thread of yarn.

It pelted onto the tarpaulin Leylin had draped over his shoulders; it gave a cooling sensation.

Riding on the Seated Lupin Wolf that had a night’s rest, Leylin appeared tranquil as he peered through the ashy haze, trying to look at the scenery ahead.

*Whoosh*

It was as if the curtains were pulled apart. Leylin felt like he had rushed out of a dense fog as extremely dazzling sunlight directly shined on them.

*Rustling*

Wolf claws slowly sunk into the countless grains of sand they were stepping on.

The rain-filled, dark clouds had gradually dispersed, and now the fiery sun had taken over the sky. It brought with it burning hot rays of brilliance, which constantly spread across the wide desert.

From what they could see, there was a field of gold as well as modulating levels of sand dunes.

“Golden Desert, we’ve arrived!” Leylin felt the surrounding temperature increasing constantly. It must have gone up by at least twenty degrees since the rain earlier.

The sweltering humidity continuously flooded into the tarpaulin, and even with Leylin’s constitution, he felt a little uncomfortable.

*Crash* He hastily removed the tarpaulin and stripped off some clothes, and even then he only felt a little better.

This sudden change in temperature within the Grand Canyon Margaret was not unusual. If ordinary people came here, it would have been a torment for them. However for Leylin and his group, it was only a wee bit troublesome.

“Awooooooo!”

The leading Seated Lupin Wolf howled, and the rest of the wolves that were being ridden by the others also howled. It wasn’t clear if these howls were due to excitement or was meant as a warning.

With the howling of the wolves, Leylin noted that the body hairs on the Seated Lupin Wolf began to change.

The Seated Lupin Wolves had black fur, and only the head had a touch of bright red fur. But now in the hot sunlight, the wolf’s hair color gradually faded. Finally, it completely transformed into a pale white color, then a streak of light blue lighted up from the wolf’s body. The whole piece fur turned ice blue.

An icy breath emitted from the back of the wolf. The icy-cool feeling was very comfortable, especially in this desert.

“It actually even knows of the uses and the difference between thermal absorption properties of light and dark colors!”

Leylin could not help but to gasp in amazement of the adaptability of the Seated Lupin Wolf. Under the scorching rays of the sun, the ice blue fur was not affected by the heat as much as the dark fur. As for the fact that the Seated Lupin Wolf knew of these — it made Leylin feel somewhat shocked.

Moreover, they even applied the slight use of Ice element energy particles.

The Seated Lupin Wolf was undoubtedly the best creature to traverse the terrains of the Great Canyon Margaret!

The six huge wolves with icy blue fur gave off a chilly sensation. They very soon proceeded on their journey along with the Magi riding on them, and stepped into the Golden Desert which was 10 times more dangerous than the Limestone Wasteland.

Under the scorching rays, Leylin gulped down some more water.

With his vision and the A.I. Chip’s detection, he had already discovered many dangerous creatures in the nearby desert.

To put it bluntly, the level of danger in the Limestone Wasteland was the lowest in all of the terrains within the Great Canyon Margaret.

A dozen days before, the journey for Leylin and the others were extremely relaxed. There was no difference from an excursion, and the dangerous creatures they met were rare.

However, things were obviously different in here.

With the slightest observation, Leylin already discovered many dangerous lifeforms concealed within the sand dunes.

Six-Eyed Poison Snake, Golden Scorpion, Toxic Compound Eye Lizard were a few creatures that Leylin saw before in illustrations as they continued to appear before his eyes. There were even some grotesquely shaped creatures.

“The energy density in the air here has even been replicated. It’s even higher than in the outside world, no wonder there are so many troublesome things!”

Feeling the energy particles that filled the air, Leylin gasped slightly.

“Everyone, keep your spirits raised. The dangers in the Golden Desert cannot be compared with the Limestone Wasteland!”

The female Magus, called Lancey, shouted.

Even without her reminder, the other Magi present had already recollected their absent-minded pace from before.

One can loosen their guard occasionally in the Limestone Wasteland, but if they chose to do the same in the Golden Desert, they were foolish and seeking for death! Those magicians who were able to advance into a rank 1 Magus were seldom such people.

“Awoooooo!”

Just then, Lancey’s steed let off a howl. Its huge claws were raised and its sharp claws at tip slashed down with a cold glint of light!

*Pat*

Suddenly, a black scorpion with the image of an eye appeared in front of where the wolf was. It was patted down by the sharp claws of wolf as it continuously writhed its body and hissed.

*Ka-Cha* The Seated Lupin Wolf dropped its jaws and opened its gory mouth as it placed the scorpion into its jaws. The razor sharp mandible continued to chew, bringing along the snapping sounds of the scorpion’s bones being crunched.

“Such a life form can be settled by the Seated Lupin Wolf. However, dangerous creatures such as the Kary Vultures must be dealt by us personally!”

Lancey slighted nudged her steed forward and said to the Magi behind her.

“This is…”

Where the Seated Lupin Wolf had attacked earlier, it sent a huge amount of sand flying in the air and Leylin spotted several grains of gold within it.

He reached his hand forward and grasp a handful of gold sand in his hands.

In the middle of the normal grains of sand, several golden grains were mixed in with it. Its weight was also heavier than the others by a large margin.

“Golden sand?”

Leylin looked at the gold which seemed to be alluring and was somewhat speechless.

“Golden Desert, this here is the real Golden Desert!”

“If it was the secular world, it will definitely cause chaos. A pity, however…”

With a look of contempt, Leylin flung the gold sand back onto the ground.

To magicians, only the magic crystals, the ingredients which could stimulate the spiritual force and the various advanced information was considered to be the real currency!

As for the gold belonging the secular world, apart from its uses as an ingredient, it was no different from regular metals.

Moreover, the Golden Desert was situated inside the Great Canyon Margaret, an area forbidden to regular humans. To traverse it also required the employment of the highly expensive Seated Lupin Wolves.

Thinking of the cost of excavation would already frighten the kings in many dukedoms!

Leylin only felt some pity regarding the golden sand, but he very soon regained his composure.

The A.I. Chip’s detection had been activated by him all along as his eyes surveyed the surroundings. In the Golden Desert, one must always be on alert.

The six giant, icy-blue wolves seemed to be six small boats in the Golden Desert as they continuously plodded on.

After the sky gradually darkened, the temperature in the desert also dropped.

At this moment, the Seated Lupin Wolf gave off warmth; their furs also turned back to black, as if storing the heat from day time.

“Today, I shall stand guard during the night!”

After Leylin had built his tent, an official Magus present among them all, said so.

There was a total of 6 in the group. Leylin, Lancey, the old leader, and the huge bloke and two others who remained silent most of the time. The one who spoke was one of these two.

These two Magi had grey robes on at all times, and seldom spoke. Their personality was also extremely antisocial. Up till now, Leylin managed to exchange two sentences with only one of the two.

“We will count on you!” Lancey did not look too good, her face appeared tired as she went into her tent.

During the day, she had used her spiritual force to scan the surroundings for any activity going on. Now, she urgently needed to rest and meditate to recover her spiritual force.

As Leylin had the A.I. Chip to help with his tasks, his mental state was still doing fine. Yet he still put on a false impression of being weary.

“Are you not going to rest awhile?” Leylin appeared in front of one of those official Magi and casually spoke to him.

“I need not rest. I have these. Come out, my little babies!”

The Magus on night duty gave a deep laughter as his pair of arms performed a strange gesture.

*Bang* *Bang* *Bang* A layer of Earth element particles continued to emanate from his body.

The surrounding sand rose up by a layer. After which, it was quickly broken, revealing a dozen yellow slates.

These muddy yellow slates each had a human face on it. Some were young, some were old. They even a pair of slim arms and legs. Just like a gingerbread man.

“Father! We await your commands!” A dozen stone slate people knelt on one knee in front of the Magus on night duty.

“Very well, you all shall guard the night for me. You are in charge of…” The night guard Magus nodded his head and unrestrainedly began giving out orders.

“Sentinel Slates?” Leylin was bewildered.

These creatures were very similar to the Sentinel Slates in the database of the A.I. Chip, yet it seemed like a creature of a higher level.

“It’s a rank 1 Sentinel Slate but they have undergone modifications from me!” The night duty Magus declared proudly.

After becoming an official Magus, magicians will often attempt to modify and improve some rank 1 spells and even the rank 0 spells of acolytes.

Once they were successful, it could absolutely turn into a unique trump card. Or it could be sold in exchange for a large amount of resources.

A pity that these things and finding replacement potions were the same. Unless one was extremely lucky to chance across it, or only after undergoing a vast amount of experiments, would it be possible to see results.

“It’s really quite a remarkable spell!” Several traces of admiration, which was just right, appeared on Leylin’s face, turning the gaze of the spell caster gentler towards him.

“Let’s go! The Sentinel Slates originally have to use of acting as a warning. After my modification, their detection abilities can span a dozen miles…” The Magus on night duty said.

Leylin looked at the Sentinel Slates, which, having received orders, hurriedly ran to the outer area of the camp encirclement, using the sand to conceal their own bodies.

Along with the sand that continuously trickled down, the energy waves of the slate got smaller, finally turning into an untraceable spell. Leylin could not help but approve in silence.

Any Magus would have their own trump card. Once they were disregarded, it would definitely be a painful experience.

Deep in the night, Leylin who was in a light sleep heard an ear-piercing scream.

“Hurry, get up. We have trouble!”

The earlier Magus, who was on guard duty, went into the individual tents and his face showing utter exasperation.

“What happened?” Lancey’s expression was the worst. There were several spots on her body where the robes were not yet arranged, as it revealed her alluring flesh. A pity nobody at the scene bothered to have another look.

Chapter 140: The Golden Giant

“A Golden Giant is in the process of moving towards us!”The Magus on night duty exclaimed hurriedly. “The Sentinel Slate used to alert the others have been completely eaten by it, too!”

“Fuck!”

After hearing these words ’Golden Giant’, Leylin quickly heard the startled oaths of nearby Magi.

The Golden Giant was a type of elemental species. Its power was close to that of a fully converted elemental Magus. On top of that, it has its own unique racial talents. Only a rank 2 Magus had the capabilities to thoroughly kill or banish it.

“Wasn’t it said that the Golden Giants from the Golden Desert are extinct? Furthermore, it appeared conveniently in our way. “

The old leader clenched his jaws in a state of madness. His eyes emitted a green radiance.

“Can we avoid it for the time being?”

Lancey suggested. “The Golden Desert is so huge, he might not be able to find us!”

“I am afraid not!” Leylin was the first to interject. “The Golden Giants have a natural instinct to chase species with high energy levels. The energy propagating from our bodies acts like a lamp in the darkness for the giant’s eyes. The more we move, the more likely the Golden Giant will assault us!”

“If that is the case what should we do?” A look of despair appeared on Lancey’s face. “Unless we have a rank 2 Magus within our party, we will all fail to escape the assault of the Golden Giant….”

There is a large gulf of difference in power level between the official Magi of different rankings

Leylin and his party of six were only slightly stronger than a rank 1 Magus. They would even have difficulties going head on with a semi converted elemental Magus. They had no chance of surviving an encounter with a fully converted elemental Golden Giant.

Semi elemental conversions refer to Magi whose elemental essence conversion has reached a level of 50% and above. At this stage, their increase in magical power due to the elemental essence conversion starts to become very obvious. When faced with budding Warlocks, they held a great advantage.

While Leylin was still an acolyte, he had an encounter with a semi converted storm elemental sprite while on the dirigible. If not for the fact that there was a large gathering of Magi from the different academies, the only outcome would have been death.

In the current predicament, Leylin had to face something far more powerful and dangerous than the semi converted storm elemental sprite.

“Perhaps, we should scatter and escape in different directions…”

The large bloke hesitated for a while before suggesting.

Upon hearing the suggestion, the Magi present entered a state of silence and eyes started flickering nonstop.

“Are you people mad?”

The old geezer interrupted the large bloke in a fit of anger. “If we fled in different directions, can you guarantee that you individuals are lucky enough to escape the assault of the Golden Giant? Furthermore, what will you do after you reach the Kary Vultures’ territory?”

The two sharp questions abruptly brought about a deeper silence.

After fleeing in different directions, they could once again head towards the intended destination. If they were lucky, there was even a chance of heading back to Broken Axe Pub.

However, this was only the last resort. The Magi will not accept their foul fate just like that.

“Quick! Another three of my babies are dead!” The night shift Magus said with a heavier breath than before.

“Maybe we could use the Sentinel Slate along with a rune which dissipates energy continuously to distract the Golden Giant. While it is distracted, we could do our best to restrain the energy emitted from our bodies and sneak away… If it fails, we could do as mentioned earlier and scatter in different directions…”

In the midst of silence. Leylin suddenly spoke up.

“Although this plan is unreliable, we obviously have no better options…”

The old geezer let out a sign of deep resignation and pointed at Leylin. “We will do as he says! I happen to have the material for a few Sentinel Slates…”

Following which, he handed out vials filled with grey powders to the night shift Magus.

Having looked at the materials handed out by the old geezer, the night shift Magus displayed a look of unwillingness. However, he still received the materials from the old geezer. “Alright, let’s try it! But I cannot guarantee that it will work!”

Soon after the chants from the nightshift Magus, a few pieces of Sentinel Slates that resembled the destroyed one rose up from the sands.

At this moment, the people in the camp could clearly see a golden glow appearing in the eastern direction.

This glow was like the sun dissipating the darkness and brought about a glimmer of warmth.

In front of the solar disk was the colossal shadow of a giant.

The giant’s body radiated a golden light. It was armoured very simply. A leather armour on this upper body with an iron hoop in the middle that joined the two shoulder pads.

On the shoulders rested the head of the giant with rigid face lines that looked like it was caused by the scrapes and slashes of weapons. The tangerine hair on top of its head looked like it was burning mightily.

[Beep! High energy species life form spotted, determined to be a Golden Giant, recommended to leave immediately!]

At the same instant, the A.I. chip displayed out of a red warning screen.

“Quick! Quick!” The old geezer’s voice was filled with urgency.

“I know a few energy concentration runes, hopefully, it is of use!” The other usually quiet Magus stood up and said. Following which he applied what looked like a mixture of circular and triangular runes on the Sentinel Slate.

After the rune was inscribed, it radiated brightly and suddenly a power energy surged out from the Sentinel Slate. This enormous energy fluctuated chaotically causing the Golden Giant to let out a roar and accelerate towards it.

“Nice! It grabbed the Golden Giant’s attention!” Lancey exclaimed happily.

“Let’s add this on top!” Leylin uncorked a red test tube and poured its content on the inscribed Sentinel Slate.

After the liquid from the red test tube assimilated fully into the Sentinel Slate, the Sentinels let out angry snarls and transformed to be bigger and with stronger limbs.

“Hopefully, this will help them hold out longer!”

Leylin tossed away the empty test tube. The energy propagating out of his body was reduced from that of an official Magus to a normal person.

This was done using the Transfiguration Spell. It diluted the level of energy propagating from his body.

After which, he went over to his Seated Lupin Wolf, placed a cover over the wolf’s mouth and gave it a pat on its head.

The Seated Lupin Wolf seemed to be aware of the presence of the incoming Golden Giant. It got low to the floor with limbs trembling and waited for Leylin’s command.

The other Magus followed Leylin’s action.

They also used the protection of the environment to conceal their whole body.

Finally, the Golden Giant was nearer to the camp. It was less than only 500 metres away!

At this sort of distance, Leylin was able to see clearly every single hair on the giant.

“It’s up to you now, babies, attack!”

“Attack! For our father!”

The burly and buffed up Sentinel Slates roared. Some of them rushed head on towards the Golden Giant while the others split up and ran in different directions.

Whether it was the brave Sentinels Slates who charged heads on towards the Golden Giant or the others who ran in different directions, their bodies carried a large source of energy which pulsated out of them. The energy was almost like that of a rank 1 Magus.

“kjfl” The Golden Giant let out an unknown type of shout as if swearing.

It stretched out its large palms in a posture like it was hiding the sky and covering the earth. It pushed against the ground and dredged up the earth.

A few of the Sentinels were picked up by the Golden Giant

“For glory! For protection!”

The Sentinel Slates roared as their little fists rained down upon the giant’s large arm.

“Creak Crunch!” The large Golden Giant placed the captured Sentinels directly into the mouth. It sounded as if he was chewing through biscuits.

After ingesting the Sentinel Slates, the Golden Giant let out a loud roar and chased after the fleeing Sentinel Slates with large strides.

“Now!”

The old geezer’s voice was soft. The six men covertly pulled the Seated Lupin Wolf and left the camp area.

Everyone was doing their utmost to contain the energy pulsating from their bodies. There was even a cover on the Seated Lupin Wolf’s body. Like moles, they stealthily left the area

The Golden Giant shouted at the fleeing Sentinel Slates and chased after them. It never gave the camp a second look.

“Run!”

Someone exclaimed softly after the golden glow disappeared. Without hesitation, everyone ran at the speed of light.

……

*Crash!*

The wolf pack ran past, kicking up a dust of sand and stones. The dust glittered a faint glow of gold.

Leylin and the party had been on the run without a break ever since he was disturbed from his rest state at the camp. This, coupled with the Golden Giant incident had caused Leylin to have an unhealthy complexion.

From the pitch black darkness of the night to a fully risen sun, almost half a day had passed while on the run.

However, the thought of the Golden Giant spurred the party on and nobody grumbled about the lack of rest.

“We were lucky the Golden Giant does not seem to have high intelligence! It only knows how to mindlessly chase after high energy life forms. If not, the stealth attempt yesterday would have failed. It was a really suspenseful situation…”

Leylin felt a lingering fear in his heart.

Although he has advanced his magical powers and is considered to be someone of considerable power in the world of Magus, the Golden Giant was something that was entirely out of his league.

“However, the Golden Giant is an elemental species. It does not have a bloodline. If not, I would rather like to have a few drops of the Golden Giant’s blood for my experiments…”

Leylin’s eyes betrayed a glimpse of regret.

There were countless types of mythical species in the Magus world. The Golden Giant belonged to the elemental species. Its whole body is made up of various type of elements and minerals. There is not even a drip of blood in it, naturally there will be no blood line.

In ancient times, the paths to becoming a Magus were many. The Warlocks chose the path of the bloodline.

And obviously, the Golden Giant chose a different path.

There are different paths to reach the pinnacle. Leylin’s plan was to follow the path of the Warlock.

“Shall we rest? If we do not meditate and recuperate our spiritual force…” Lancey’s voice was heard from the front of the party. She travelled together with the old geezer on the Seated Lupin Wolf.

All Magi make use of the both their spiritual force and magic power to perform miraculous magic. Due to the Golden Giant incident yesterday and the constant travelling, the six Magi were unable to mediate to recuperate their spiritual energy. Looks of exhaustion were spread across their faces.

“No need for that, we are yet to be out of the danger zone, the Golden Giant might catch up to us anytime soon…”

The wind carried the old geezers reply though the party.

After hearing the old geezers reply, the party sank into a solemn silence and carried on with their hasty escape.

The Magi feared the Golden Giant more than any other dangers in the Golden Desert.

Chapter 145: Teljose City

“This looks like it was caused by some sort of body possession spell!”

The knowledgeable Leylin was quick in assessing the situation.

“Old geezer, you only have the strength of a semi-converted elemental Magus, and you want to take me down?” Although Leylin looked like he could not have cared less, his right hand had already reached into his belt pouch.

*Boom!*

With a flip of his hands, a couple of potions exploded on the giant’s body. Following the explosion, a cloud of purple flame engulfed the giant’s body and continued to erode it.

“Negative energy flames? Child’s play!” The giant shook his head and widened his mouth to let out what seemed like a vacuum force, sucking all of the flames into his abdomen.

“Now, it’s my turn!” The giant let out a satisfying belch and grinned at Leylin.

In an instant, the giant turned into a silver flash and appeared right in front of Leylin.

The giant’s huge body structure and protruding muscles were faintly oppressing Leylin.

*Whoosh!* The giant’s skin was suffused with a metallic silver tone. It swung its mace-like arms towards Leylin, and Leylin could only raise both his arms up to protect his chest.

*Peng!*

Like an artillery shell, Leylin’s body was rammed viciously into a wall, causing a large building to collapse in half.

*Bang!* The rubble rolled apart and revealed Leylin’s figure.

[Host’s ribs fractured, multiple muscle injuries, immediate medical attention recommended!] The A.I. Chip alerted.

“Such great strength, it must be at least 15 or greater! On top of the amplification caused by its metallic element”

Leylin’s eyes flashed blue, “A.I. Chip, input the site information, activate the prediction system!”

[Site data transmitted, simulating opponent’s information!] The A.I. Chip’s voice intoned. Moreover it projected a 3D image for Leylin to look at.

[According to the opponent’s movement, the next attack will appear at an angle of 38 degrees on the right side. Probability: 98.7%!]

*Shua!* Just then, the giant charged over again.

[Most optimal action: Duck to the left at 63 degrees, jump backwards!]

Leylin’s body twisted and barely avoided the attack of the giant, before hurriedly jumping back.

*Pu*

At this moment, many half-metre-long metal spikes were piercing the ground where Leylin had stood before. If Leylin were still standing there, he would have died.

To outsiders, Leylin was extremely nimble, making inconceivable dodging movements and evasions as he avoided a barrage of attacks.

“He could actually stall a Magus who has converted half of his elemental essence and also has a reinforced body!”

The old geezer was drenched in cold sweat. “I still thought…”

“You thought that he was just a budding Magus that can be bullied easily, right?” The huge bloke said. “Count yourself lucky, old man! Managing to survive to this point hasn’t been an easy task!”

On the other side of the battlefield, the giant was visibly agitated because of Leylin’s successful evasive maneuvers. The human face on top of the left side of its chest blustered, ”Damnit! Goddamn pest!”

After which, the giant executed a maneuver.

Using its large hands, it broke apart its own stomach and pulled out what looked like a golden hoop.

“Hoop of Imprisonment!”

A bright white light emitted from within the golden hoop and immediately struck Leylin.

As the white luminescence fell upon him, Leylin was shocked to realize that his body had been weighted down by what seemed like an entire mountain. He could not move a single inch.

“Although this type of magical artifact is only of middle grade, It has been said that even a semi-converted elemental Magus would be shackled for at least a minute by its imprisonment powers!”

Blood continued to flow from the silver giant’s abdomen, and its guts were visibly hanging out. Unperturbed, the giant advanced towards Leylin and started choking his neck. Its eyes danced with gleeful ridicule, “Now, run for me, little thing!”

“It’s over!”

The crowd in the vicinity sighed.

“Being in a deadlock with a semi-converted elemental Magus for such a long time did not change the fact that he is just a budding Magus. On top of that, the opponent had a middle-grade magical artifact!”

The bespectacled, white-bearded, old geezer from the pub lost his earlier look of pity, and with a tinge of regret, he said, “What a shame! He was a gifted Magus”

“Young man, say your last words!”

A cold smile spread across the silver giant’s face.

“The person who should be saying his last words is you!” A wide smile spread across Leylin’s face.

“Fallen Star Pendant, activate!”

A dark red ray projected from Leylin’s chest and spread to his four limbs at a rapid rate. Immediately, Leylin held down the giant’s two hands. His pupils became vertical slits and carried an amber luster as they radiated a mysterious light.

Innate Spell—Eyes of Petrification!

*Kacha! Kacha!”

The silver giant’s expression became blank, after which an ash-grey color started to grow from the giant’s eyes. The ash-grey color covered the giant’s face in no time and spread quickly towards its chest and limbs.

“Petrifying magic? Goddamn!” The old geezers head on the giant’s chest cried out in an alarmed tone.

Following which, the old geezer ground his teeth, and spat a mouthful of blood on the giant’s body. With a metallic flash, the rate at which the petrifying spell was spreading on the giant’s body slowed down.

“To hell with you!”

Leylin reached out his right hand, and the glow from the Fallen Star Pendant turned into what looked like a long sword, which was then swung down.

*Pu!* On the first swing, the giant’s skull flew up.

On the second swing, Leylin directly dug out the old midget’s visage from the giant’s chest.

*Pa!* The face fell onto the ground. “I will not forgive you!” it shouted.

“It is I who will not forgive you!” With a cold look, Leylin stepped onto the human face.

“Ah…” A depressed voice sounded out, and a puddle of green blood slowly formed under Leylin’s foot.

……

*Huu Huu*…

A light breeze passed. There was a deathly stillness in the crowd.

“He… he actually managed to slay a semi-converted elemental Magus!”

The old geezer with his hanging mouth opened constantly surveyed the surroundings as if he was looking for something.

Immediately, upon seeing Leylin’s gaze turn towards his direction, the old geezer put on a smile and flattered him by saying, “Master Leylin! Please forgive me for offending you, it was a misunderstanding…”

Looking at the old geezer who had changed his facial complexion, Leylin shook his head and was not prepared to deal with him.

There will be no benefit even if I were to murder him. Leylin concluded that he himself was no homicidal maniac.

He picked up his bundle and the loot from his victory, and hastily left the scene. The surrounding crowd naturally opened up a path for him to exit. Magus or acolyte, nobody dared to make eye contact with Leylin.

“I must leave this place quickly!”

Leylin looked at the rapidly shrinking Andre Town in the distance and muttered to himself.

The midget from earlier was obviously just one of the many clones of the opponent.

This aligned with Leylin’s earlier reports. According to the report, the Lilytell family’s elders’ powers should have reached an elemental essence conversion rate of 80% or more, which was the minimum requirement for initiating one’s advancement to a level 2 Magus.

Based on an estimation, the midget earlier had, at most, a 50% elemental essence conversion rate. It was not very stable, and the difference between his and an elder’s true strength was too huge.

Leylin had been introduced to this type of Magus before. It was not easy for them to create a clone, as a copious amount of time and precious materials were needed. Furthermore, if their clone were destroyed, the Magus would be heavily affected as well.

So far, only the clone had chased him up till this point.

Leylin guessed that either the opponent was not able to be here physically, or the clone was intentionally placed on the other side of the Grand Canyon to facilitate communication and to do his bidding.

Regardless, the next wave of attacks from the Lilytell family would arrive soon.

“Speaking of territory, I am still within the boundaries of the dark Magi. Once I reach the domain of the light Magi, even the Lilytell family will not dare to trespass…”

……

Leylin turned his head to take one last look and vanished into the darkness.

Months flew by unconsciously.

In the span of these months, Leylin hurried along his journey with little rest. He traversed large kingdoms, and finally entered the boundary of the light Magi’s domain.

In the south coast, there were two types of Magi. One type of Magus advocated violence, believed in natural selection, and looked up to the enduring dark Magi, while the other type was fond of peace, and revered the scientific research of the light Magi.

Within these two factions, there lay many different groups and academies. While there was a lack of cohesion and an abundance of friction between these groups and academies, they would always stand together as one whenever it was against an enemy.

The extent of the rule of the light Magi lay in the heart of the south coast, while the dark Magi occupied the more desolate outlying areas.

From Leylin’s observations, this sort of distribution of territory looked like a couple of concentric circles. The light Magi occupied the most fertile land in the middle, while the dark Magi occupied everything else around it.

After a prolonged period of travel, Leylin found it hard not to admit that the light Magi territory was generally more prosperous than that of the dark Magi. The commoners in the light Magi territory also enjoyed more peace and stability.

In regards to government administration, the light Magi had to do much more than the dark Magi in order to keep a firm hold on the vast and rich territory

According to the map on the A.I. Chip, Leylin would reach the market place of the light Magi domain, Teljose City, by today.

Leylin had few opportunities to change out of his black robe. He changed out into a clean set of leather armour.

The exquisite armour comfortably fit Leylin’s well-proportioned body, and brought about an air of heroic spirit, making him look more masculine.

The light Magi instinctively viewed the dark Magi as their adversaries, so Leylin did not wish to incur any trouble by doing something rash.

Although it might only be a trade centre, there would surely be people, like the dark Magi, who were there to sell their contraband items. Leylin took extra caution and kept a low profile.

Following the horses, Leylin forged on ahead. He observed that the pathways became wider and wider, and the people used a larger variety of transportation devices to aid in their travels.

Upon further observation, he came across a variety of new and odd things.

For example, he observed a female Magus on a winged steed, and an old geezer on a hot air balloon. Hanging from the hot air balloon, there was a banner, which read, “Welcome to Hookety’s miscellaneous goods shop, we have a supply of…”

Furthermore, Leylin even saw a few machines that resembled the components of futuristic vehicles. The machines, which carried a bunch of dwarfs, roared and rumbled loudly as it sped along the road.

Chapter 146: Jenna

Amongst those who were travelling on the same route as Leylin, there were not only magicians, but also many regular people.

Most of the regular people rode on horse carriages, and they stored large amounts of vegetables and fruits at the back.

Even though they might treat magicians with much respect, it was obvious that they held no fear when facing them. It seemed that in the light Magi domain, magicians were often revered, yet were on close terms with the civilians.

This situation somewhat puzzled Leylin. In a kingdom where the dark Magi ruled, the mere mention of Magi would give rise to thoughts of terror and bloodshed. Even an acolyte would be enough to scare away a whole town of people.

“By the looks of it, the fact that light Magi and regular humans are able to coexist harmoniously is true!” Leylin glanced at a farmer who had taken off his hat to greet him, and nodded in acknowledgement.

“And…” His blue eyes shone, “There is no trace of radiation in his body. Does this have to do with the purification tower?”

In the area under the light Magi’s rule, white lofty towers were erected a distance away from each other. The towers were able to neutralise the radiation from magicians, which was vital in allowing magicians and regular humans to mingle within this area.

As for the area ruled by dark Magi, Leylin had once seen inside the library at the Abyssal Bone Forest Academy, the designs for the Purification tower. But, it was apparent that the dark Magi were disinclined to build such a thing in their own territories. Besides the problem of the costs of constructing such a tower, Leylin guessed that the dark Magi liked to rule the commoners with a bloody and terrible regime.

As the mount was continuously flying, Leylin felt that his horizons was continuously expanding.

Green waves, almost like the waves of an ocean, was rippling in the breeze, giving off a thick atmosphere.

Here was the Teljose Great Plains which covered an area of several thousands of square kilometers and had several cities with population larger than 100,000.

And the Teljose City was located in the middle of this huge plains, and was the central zone of this huge region.

“The vegetation is lush and abundant here!”

Leylin heaved a heartfelt sigh. The closer he got to the Teljose City, the more lushly the crops were growing, as if they were fond of people. There were even wheat plants which were as tall as a man — seeing which Leylin felt moved.

“Isn’t this very amazing? Are you a Magus from outside this region?”

A red pony suddenly drew to a halt besides Leylin’s own saddled mount, and the female Magus sitting atop this red pony, spoke to Leylin.

This female Magus wore a white, Chinese-styled gown, and wore a necklace strung with pearls and precious stones around her neck. Her appearance was quite ordinary, but on her face, she wore a gentle smiling expression.

Leylin had experienced this feeling of tranquility a few times.

Although this female Magus radiated the energy waves of a rank 1 Magus, she had very little actual combat experience. There was only one layer of innate defense spell upon her body, which appeared to suffice for her.

“That’s right, Miss, I come from afar and am a wandering Magus! You can call me Leylin!”

Leylin put on a harmless smile as he introduced himself.

“My name is Jenna, I’m a local Magus of Teljose. You are surprised upon seeing these many crops, aren’t you?”

The female Magus smiled and struck a conversation with Leylin.

“Indeed, you seldom see wheat grow this tall and let’s not forget the quantity… “Leylin’s face suffused with a puzzled expression.

“This is a Magus’ blessing! In a while you can experience it by yourself!”

The female Magus wore an expression of mystery but also expectation.

“I’m looking forward to it!” Leylin smiled briefly.

He could judge with just a look that this woman is like an innocent sheep, lacking the experience of meeting Magi of her peers and extremely curious about everything.

Just like a young lady from a large family, that has wandered off.

Afterwards Leylin stopped observing these matters, as the City of Teljose was appearing in front of Leylin’s eyes.

In Leylin’s line of sight, there first appeared a black dot.

Afterwards, that black dot increased in size as if it turned into a dark cloud, enveloping the whole sky.

Leylin’s jaw dropped — he saw a tall and erect mountain, reaching through the clouds and standing quietly on the plains.

Leylin had seen a lot of large mountains in his past life, but he was sure that he’d never seen a mountain so large that it could cover the skies.

In addition, on that large mountain there were numerous tightly packed buildings and black dots moving around on the many layers on that mountain.

At the foot of the mountain, a large tall city wall was erected in a circular fashion. A visual estimate gave its height at a couple of dozen meters and that it was entirely made out of grey granite. It looked extremely impressive.

At the giant peak of the mountain, there were layers of luxuriant snow. Smoke was continuously emitted from the peak, as if it was going to erupt at any given moment.

“An active volcano! Teljose City is erected on an active volcano!” Leylin gasped.

“Correct! Keep on looking around!”

The Magus Jenna pointed towards the opening of the volcano with a laugh.

Boom!

Countless black smokes were rising, the whole volcano was coming to life. Just like a mythical giant laughing sadistically at the sky.

A giant pillar of smoke rushed into the sky, coloring part of the sky black.

“Strange, why were there no tremors?”

Leylin came to sudden realization, “this must be the work of the Magi of Teljose City?”

“Correct, continue to look!” Jenna pointed towards the black clouds, “Magus’ blessing will soon descend!”

Rumble!

A soft rain was arising, tiny droplets of black rain were falling through the breeze.

Back rain fell on the ground, turning the whole ground ashen grey.

Soon a couple of farmers ran out from the fields, kneeled in front of Leylin, Jenna and other Magi and kowtowed respectfully as they said, “We thank our lords, the Magi, for our harvest!”

“This is volcanic ash?!”

Leylin’s body started to emit grey light, it enveloped the giant steed and kept the black rain on the outside. He extended his right hand to collect a drop of grey rain drop and started to examine it.

“Looks like some artificial things have been added to it, it resembles nitrogen-based fertilizer!”

Volcanic ash was naturally nutrient-rich, which was conducive for plant growth. Coupled with some other things the magicians had added, it was no wonder crops here had an astonishing form and output.

“That’s right, the Magi control the Teljose Volcano’s eruption. They transport and evenly distribute the volcanic ash across the plains and fertilize the land. As for resources such as geothermal energy, the Magi will collect them and convert them into a source of power for Teljose City. Hence, the alternate name for Teljose City that I love even more — Nightless City!”

Jenna explained

“….. This technology is simply amazing!” Leylin murmured. Teljose Volcano, as compared to the biggest volcano Leylin saw before his reincarnation, was much broader. To control such a big live volcano, they needed constant maintenance and magic spell formations, which exceeded what Leylin could have thought of.

Furthermore, to directly control a volcano as a power source and a place to live… This kind of design and boldness left Leylin feeling admiration towards these Magi.

“But, please forgive my bluntness, I’ve once travelled to the eastern region. The magicians there don’t seem to spare a thought for the normal people…”

Leylin properly expressed his curiosity.

“Yes, magicians are a group of intellectual people. They did this because it was for their benefit.” Jenna nodded her head. “The way we see it, the normal people that are alive are also a type of resource. Besides, as long as there is sufficient people, they can serve us at all times, procuring resources, and in addition, sow our seeds and producing acolytes of excellent quality, increasing new bloods…”

“Hence, in the middle of our light Magi region, not only were there Magi who specialised in solidification innate spells to be used for helping to prevent all kinds of natural disasters, there’s even a full-time Magus in charge of farming land and increasing harvest yield…”

“This… this really is…”

Leylin wore a shocked expression while secretly releasing a breath of relief.

Although Jenna seemed pure and straightforward, she still considered herself superior to regular humans, similar to how the dark Magi thought.

The one difference they had was in their system.

Akin to the herding of sheep, dark Magi tended to operate in a more boorish manner and would reap the harvest at irregular intervals. In comparison, light Magi adopted a micro-management style, taking special care of each and every sheep.

But they both had the same purpose — to obtain the needed materials from regular humans.

Just based on this process, Leylin felt that the regular humans in the light Magi region had a more comfortable life, compared to those living in Poolfield Kingdom.

However, although Leylin could lament over the hardships faced by the regular humans, it did not mean that he thought of reducing the power and authority that the Magi held; it was foolish to advocate an ideal of achieving equality between all humans.

Not mentioning the mysteries and strength of the Magus world, even Leylin himself only believed in one truth — that one’s status would determine one’s course of action.

Leylin himself was a Magus and fully supported the privileges and political power that all Magi had. As for those who had delusions of overthrowing the Magi in power, they would be killed immediately.

As part of a higher tier in the social pyramid, it was only natural to consciously defend the rights and privileges of that social class.

Naturally, there were also the strange ones who chose to betray their peer’s interests, and would eventually be abandoned by their own peers.

Leylin concluded that: unless there were any signs of the Magi falling out of power, he would definitely not betray his peers.

“Very surprising, isn’t it?”

Jenna laughed, “Seems like you’ve always been travelling around the dark Magi region. But once you’ve arrived at the Nightless City, you’ll need to learn to acclimatize, and adapt to the new rules…”

Jenna’s words implied that she had discovered Leylin’s true identity.

But Leylin only picked up his eyebrow and didn’t seem to care in the slightest.

Teljose City, or reputed for being a Nightless City, on one hand was the accumulation of the light Magi’s hard work, and on the other hand was supported by the dark Magi.

If the dark Magi was totally removed, then Nightless City’s total trades would immediately fall by more than half!

No trade center would reject a dark Magi member from joining them.

Chapter 147: Prophecy

From what Leylin gathered, dark Magi from all over the continent disguised themselves in order to enter Nightless City each day. Their aim was to trade items, amongst other activities.

The guards of the city turned a blind eye to their actions.

It could be said that Nightless City’s prosperity was largely dependent on the dark Magi.

Within the city, as long as dark Magi did not intentionally reveal their identity, light Magi would not bother about them.

Hence, Leylin simply smiled and told Jenna, “I came to the Teljose Plains to seek a peaceful way of life. I’m willing to abide by the rules here.”

“Nightless City is a fertile and beautiful city. I’m sure you’ll like it here!”

Jenna laughed and said.

Leylin made small talk with Jenna and managed to gather quite a lot of exclusive information about the city.

Leylin had seen a glimpse of Volcano City in the afternoon, but it was only after the sky dimmed that he reached the gate.

At the moment, there were rows of people queueing up in front of the gates of the city.

The numerous heads seemed like ants as they were separated into different groups and entered various entrances.

Leylin noticed that beside the many small doors, there were also several huge passages. The gates to the city itself were over ten metres high, and the passageways were closed.

“These doors are for giants and large creatures, so they aren’t usually open!” Jenna explained at the side.

“As for us, we are official Magi, so we are able to enter by the prestigious pass!”

Jenna explained as she led Leylin to a smaller door which was quieter.

As for the doors on both sides, there were even a dozen guards with the strength of level 3 acolytes, their bodies radiating the energy waves of their magic artifacts.

“Respected Lords, may I ask if it is a temporary or permanent lodging…”

After seeing Leylin and Jenna, these dozen acolytes immediately bowed and greeted them.

Leylin noticed that they held a circular item that was emitting the glow of a magic spell, in their hands. Looking at the runes on the surface, it should be the runes formation to detect energy waves.

Jenna immediately raised her right hand and revealed a white ring on her finger.

The ancient ring had a silver body with detailed inscriptions on the surface, constantly emitting bits and pieces of light.

“So it’s a Lord who has a permanent residence. Please enter!” The acolytes respectfully made way.

“It’s my first time here. Are there any procedures I need to follow?” Leylin asked the acolyte from before.

“Yes. For magicians who enter for the first time, we have a simple procedure. You can pay 200 magic crystals and obtain permanent residence, or spend 10 magic crystals and stay in Nightless City for a month!”

“Handle a permanent residence for me!” Leylin immediately tossed out two high-grade magic crystals.

“Of course. Please wait a moment…” The acolyte quickly produced a piece of parchment and scribbled something on it. “May I have your name?”

“Leylin Farlier!” This was the light Magi’s territory and the Lilytell Family’s influence did not extend to this area. Leylin decided to use his real name.

“Here is your token. Please keep it well!”

The whole process was surprisingly straightforward. The acolyte merely asked for Leylin’s name, noted it down, and then passed him a silver ring.

“This is a token you will need to enter the city. Please keep it safe! Also, please do not linger on the streets after 12am. If not, the law enforcement group will apprehend you!”

The acolyte reminded him as he bowed.

Leylin nodded in understanding before leaving with Jenna, who had been waiting at the side.

“Jenna, I’ve been waiting for you!” Leylin went through a passage that was around five or six metres deep, and before he even had the chance to look around the city, he heard a hoarse voice.

A burly blonde man who had been standing at the door for some time immediately rushed forward with a worried expression.

“Uncle Manla!” Jenna put on a coquettish expression and immediately embraced the large man. “Jenna missed you!”

“Haha…Me too!” The burly man smiled and looked at Leylin beside her.

“This fellow reeks of blood, it seems like he’s from the eastern marshes!”

The murderous aura and strong scent of blood from Leylin’s body immediately caused the man to raise his guard against Leylin. He positioned himself between Leylin and Jenna.

“This is…” The burly man’s glared at him, as if ready to make a move the moment he misspoke.

“This is Leylin, someone I met along the way!” Jenna hung on to Manla’s arm.

“He’s a wandering Magus who is planning to stay in Nightless City!”

“Really? This is a city that advocates peace and harmony, so I hope you’ll enjoy your stay here. Here is a complete map of the city!”

The burly man showed him a kind smile and passed the map to Leylin. It was very obvious that he did not want Leylin to travel together with Jenna.

“Many thanks!” Leylin grinned brightly.

He could understand where the man was coming from. If he were a parent who saw his child mixing with a suspicious person, he would have the same reaction.

“It was great fun travelling with you! I’ll see you again, milady!” Leylin turned to Jenna with a smile and gave a gentleman’s bow, and Jenna answered with a bashful expression.

Having received the map, Leylin took a quick look at it and entered the trade centre of the south coast, also known as the Teljose Volcano City, where the night was as bright as day.

The burly man waited till Leylin was completely gone before turning to the female Magus, a stern expression on his face.

“Jenna, from what I know, you don’t usually get this close with strangers?”

The large man put on a puzzled expression.

“I don’t know why, but I have some premonition that makes me want to get closer to him…” Jenna’s eyes seemed to cloud over.

“Or perhaps, this is what fate decreed!”

“That seems plausible!” The man scratched his head. “The high-grade meditation technique that you’re cultivating in may not be very powerful, but at times, it is able to accurately pinpoint a trace of the future. Since that Magus gives you such a peculiar feeling, do you need me to send someone to check out…”

“Leave it! I have a feeling that if we do that, it’ll definitely incur his displeasure.”

Jenna’s eyes suddenly turned completely white, with no hints of any other colour.

“Twice! You actually made two prophecies about him!”

The burly man looked shocked. “That Magus’ fate is sure to be intertwined with yours!”

“Not me, but the whole of the south coast!”

The female Magus’ eyes regained their colour, cold sweat pouring down her face. She looked as if all of her energy had been wrenched from her.

“Quick, send me back to grandmother’s place!”

Jenna spat out and immediately fainted.

“Jenna! Jenna!” The expression on the burly man’s face was grim as he held her in his arms and quickly left the area…

Leylin, however, was completely oblivious to the situation. He was currently strolling through the streets of the Nightless City.

The moment he entered, Leylin’s first impression was—People! A sea of people!

Numerous heads were gathered close to each other, forming a sea of blackness. There were also various stores, as well as stands that were messily displayed. The constant haggling and bawling noises attacked the ears.

Many Magi and acolytes who were dressed in different coloured clothing were arguing aggressively with the vendors.

This almost reminded Leylin of the markets in his previous world.

However, the different races that he saw within the masses brought him back to the present.

There was the scaly marine race, the sub-humans with fur and marks all over their bodies, the smaller version of giants who were over five meters tall, as well as the little green people who had pairs of transparent wings on their backs, dancing gracefully in the air.

Many lifeforms from the Magus world were communicating with each other, their speech slipping back to parts of their own languages.

Among the humans, Leylin even saw several regular humans who had absolutely no energy waves radiating from them, and yet they were still confidently trading items on the street out in the open.

“My Lord, is it your first time in Nightless City?”

Leylin’s intrigued expression naturally attracted the attention of many people. A man who was so skinny that he was like a stick approached Leylin as he bowed, wearing a flattering expression on his face.

“Do you need a tour guide? My fee is definitely the lowest. Moreover, my home is within Nightless City, so I am familiar with every nook and cranny in this place!”

“Are you the ‘ears’ of this city?”

Leylin inquired to clarify.

“Of course. If there is anything that you want to know, I could also make some inquiries…”

“What is your name?” Leylin asked.

“Sean! My Lord, you can call me Sean.” The thin man was delighted as this situation meant it was possible to seal the deal.

“Good. I wish to stay here for an extended period of time. Take me to a place where I can rent some lodgings. It must have all the facilities!”

“If you wish to stay here for long, renting an apartment which is in the heart of Nightless City would be the most worthwhile!” Sean said quickly without needing to think.

As if fearing that Leylin did not understand, Sean quickly went on, “The heart of the city is controlled by several large factions that back Nightless City. There are different types of apartments for sale, and they are generally quite safe and convenient…”

“Very well, let’s go there!”

Leylin nodded his head, and Sean hurriedly led the way with a gleeful expression.

After going through the throng of people and walking for about half an hour, Sean brought Leylin to a small door.

“Nightless City has five zones, and the outermost zone is meant for regular people and acolytes to live in. Its organisation is the most chaotic, and as long as one is in possession of a token, he or she can enter and leave the city at will.”

“The second zone is reserved for those who have done the paperwork to stay here permanently. Of course, Official Magi are allowed to stay here too!” Sean brought Leylin to the queue in front of the door and explained further.

“As for the third and fourth zone, they are the residences of the official Magi. There is also a trade area specifically catered to the official Magi erected within the zone.”

“Lastly, we have the fifth zone, where various powers have established their branches there. Usually, they are not open to the public and if you are not a member, you are not allowed to enter!”

Sean gave Leylin a clear explanation.

Chapter 148: The Communal Centre

The queue progressed quickly, and within a few minutes, it was Leylin’s turn.

Leylin produced the ring he had recently acquired, and showed it to the guard, who respectfully stepped aside to allow him to pass.

The second zone was a lot bigger than the first, and the shops were arranged in an organised manner, unlike the situation in the first zone.

*Thud Thud *

His leather shoes thudded as they descended upon the marble floor.

With Sean’s guidance, Leylin arrived at the centre of the second zone.

What was known as the communal centre was situated at the middle of the second zone. It was a humongous building that, based on its outward appearance, looked like a person’s inverted palm pressed to the ground.

Each of those fingers was a wide entrance.

Magicians formed long lines, looking like ants as they constantly went through the entrances.

“This is where the Nightless City’s internal affairs are conducted. These includes the renting of lodgings, the applications for store licenses, the issuing of missions, and so on.”

Sean brought Leylin into the passageway on the forefinger.

“This is the second passage that is specially catered for the Magi who wish to rent lodgings. Of course, we also provide property agents, though the price will be higher and the rentals may not be of the best quality…”

“Sir, would you like to rent a lodging? Come to Old Hork’s place! Our facilities are complete, and there are even snake and fox girls who will serve you!”

“No! Come to our side. Our prices are the most reasonable here, and we’re even willing to gift you ten regular human servants.”

The moment Leylin entered, he attracted the attentions of multiple agents, who all looked ready to gobble him down.

“He’s my customer! Get out of the way! Move!”

Sean guided Leylin to a passageway nearby, pushing away the overzealous hands reaching for him.

Within the passage was a spiral staircase. When they got to the second level, Leylin suddenly realised how quiet his surroundings were.

As they passed through a door frame that read “Hall No. 762,” Leylin saw a large domed hall.

On the ceiling, there was a huge crystal chandelier from which multicoloured rays of light bounced off, casting a phantom image on the ground.

To the side of the domed hall, there were many counters, and a few seats meant for people to wait in. A few magicians were already seated, their eyes glazed over as if they were about to fall asleep.

On the right wall, there was also a black screen. There were words in red on it which were constantly being refreshed.

“Apartment #332, West Hall Street West, small sized — costs 6700 magic crystals!”

“Apartment #893, Flamingo Street, of medium size — costs 85000 magic crystals!”

“These lodgings are all second-hand. The prices here are considerably cheaper, and many people wait here, hoping they might be lucky enough to get a good price…” Seeing the look of interest on Leylin’s face, he launched into an explanation.

Leylin was speechless, the thought of a real estate agency from his past life suddenly came to his mind.

“If you wish to rent an apartment, you can proceed to counters 1 to 15. Would you like me to queue on your behalf?”

“Fine,” Leylin nodded.

Even though he had quite a sum at hand, he was unwilling to splurge on an apartment so quickly, when he had not yet made sense of the situation in Nightless City.

Seeing all of these ridiculously high prices made Leylin think of the acolytes back in the academy who were so desperate for magic crystals that they wished a magic crystal was worth twice its actual value. The image made him want to cry and laugh at the same time.

There were many counters in the hall. After Sean left to join a queue, Leylin found himself a seat and began to flip through one of the magazines left on a table.

“Rose Sanctuary and Fresh Blood White Bones are currently in a conflict. They are currently gathered in Margaret City, and the number of casualties is unknown…”

“It has been reported that magicians have found the culprit that caused the tsunami in the Eastern Sea- an Ancient Whale. Currently, Ennea Ivory Ring Tower is holding an emergency meeting to discuss countermeasures…”

“Looking to purchase large quantities of purified gems. Name your price.”

There was plenty of news in the magazine, though they seemed outdated. Furthermore, the majority of the content was on advertisements, sponsorships and the like.

“Sir, it’s your turn now!”

Sean’s voice travelled over. Leylin put down the magazine, heading to the 13th counter where Sean was standing.

“Welcome! How may I help you?”

Behind the counter was an adorable girl with a professional smile on her face, who was wearing something that was similar to lace. She seemed quite young, and Leylin guessed that she was, at most, eighteen or nineteen years old.

Leylin’s gaze shifted to the back of the counter, where he caught a glimpse of the white ball behind the maiden’s shapely backside.

“Of all the half beasts, someone who’s half-rabbit?” Leylin chuckled inwardly, not expecting the centre to actually hire a rabbit maiden.

“I wish to rent a house. The facilities must be complete, and it is best if it includes a laboratory, and the defensive spell formation has to be of at least this standard…”

Leylin stated his requirements.

“Please wait for a moment…” The rabbit maiden quickly flipped through the stack of parchments in front of her, closing her eyes from time to time while caressing a crystal ball with a metal base, as if she was communicating with someone.

“We have many houses that fit your requirements, but in order to rent a lodging in Nightless City, we require you to show evidence of… Ah! My lord! My sincerest apologies!”

Upon seeing the silver ring that Leylin revealed, the rabbit maiden’s previously absent-minded expression completely changed.

She stood and bowed, showing her charming body and sturdy thighs, and the rabbit’s tail behind her backside occasionally appearing. It gave one the urge to reach forward and grab hold of it. “So it was an official Magi! Please excuse Bayjess’ rude behaviour!”

“It’s fine. Tell me about the houses!”

Leylin withdrew his right hand.

“For an official Magus of such high esteem, we strongly recommend apartments that are in the third zone or above. There is a total of thirteen empty houses that meet your requirements…”

As she spoke, she continued to rub the surface of the blue crystal ball.

Rainbow coloured lights converged in front of Leylin and the multicoloured streaks formed many three-dimensional figures.

From the looks of it, it was a map of Nightless City, on which there were thirteen bright spots.

“All information about the apartments are on it, and there are also figures that allow you to view the structures of the lodgings.”

Leylin took a quick look. All of the apartments were in the second zone or above, and the total area of the land was rather large. They were at least medium sized villas that included gardens and other entertainment facilities.

Nightless City was built on a mountain, and the higher up one went, the more valuable every inch became. In a place like this, the privileges and extravagant lifestyle that magicians were entitled to were especially evident from the area of land they had access to.

Leylin raised his hand and pressed on the villa that he was interested in.

*Ding!*

With a flash of white light, the model was magnified, and a three-dimensional figure was displayed in front of him.

“Medium-sized villa’s location: Nightless City Zone 3, Large Whale Street #56. It includes a laboratory, a defensive spell formation, a negative energy reaction pool…”

Beside the 3D figure, there was also a white frame that displayed more information about the villa.

“While this technology is based on magic, it’s just too similar to how it was in my past life…”

Leylin suddenly sighed.

While the foundations of the two worlds were extremely different, one being science, and the other being magic, it somehow made Leylin feel a little nostalgic.

“I’ll take this one. How much is the rent?”

Leylin pointed to one of the models and asked the rabbit maiden.

“Sir, the rent for this villa is a thousand magic crystals per month…” She peeked at Leylin, looking as if she wanted to say something, and eventually made her mind. “If you join any one of the powers backing Nightless City, you’ll be gifted a villa, and…”

“Alright. Which family do you come from?

Leylin was very much aware that these employees were part of the powers behind Nightless City, and it was naturally their job to attract talents. They were sure to receive attractive rewards for their work if they were successful.

“The Mordeken family! I come from the Mordeken Family!” The rabbit maiden lowered her collar and revealed a brand in the shape of a palm under her shoulder.

The shape of the palm was a little strange. Instead of having five fingers, as was the norm, there were actually six.

The sides of the brand were a little charred and twisted. From the looks of it, a branding iron had been used directly on her skin in the past. The contrast between that and the rabbit maiden’s delicate skin gave rise to an abnormal sense of beauty.

“I understand! If there’s anything I need in the future, I’ll consider the Mordeken family first!”

Leylin’s expression remained the same, seemingly unmoved by her attempts. Sean, on the other hand, was salivating at the offer.

“Here are the magic crystals. I’ll be renting it for a year.” Leylin threw a small bag of magic crystals towards the back of the counter.

After being rejected, the rabbit maiden’s expression slightly darkened, but she immediately forced a smile.

Even though she wasn’t able to convince an official Magus to join the family, she would still receive some rewards from this transaction.

The rabbit maiden asked for the ring on Leylin’s finger, and placed it in a device behind her, within which an exotic symbol was inscribed. She then respectfully returned it to Leylin.

“The pattern of the villa’s defensive spell formation has already been marked onto your ring. You may enter the villa using the ring, and also make changes to the spell formation…”

Following which, the rabbit maiden passed Leylin a bunch of keys and a document.

“Here are the keys to the rooms in the villa, as well as some important information. I hope you have a pleasant stay there!”

Leylin retrieved the items and walked out of the hall with Sean.

“He actually spent over ten thousand magic crystals in one go…”

Sean still had a look of disbelief on his face.

Although he had heard of how certain magicians were able to spend unimaginable amounts of wealth, being in actual contact with someone who had the means to do so was still an entirely different feeling.

“Having met such a magnanimous customer, my rewards will definitely not be meagre. I might even be able to get a generous tip as well…”

Sean began to let his imagination run wild.

“Bring me to the villa and these will be yours!”

Leylin smiled, tossing a few magic crystals that were glistening temptingly.

“Of course! Your wish is my command!”

Sean’s eyes brightened, and he quickly ran to the front. “Please follow me! There’s not one place in Nightless City that I, Sean, am not aware of!”

Chapter 151: Absorption

“You reek of blood, young man.”

The old witch cried out in exaggeration.

“You are a dark Magus, am I right?”

“Is there anything wrong? I don’t know of any rule in Nightless City that states that you can’t sell to dark Magi.” Leylin’s brows furrowed.

“Hehehe… Don’t worry, I’m a dark Magus too, though that’s a matter from over 200 years ago. Ah, just remembering those times makes me feel nostalgic…”

The old witch chuckled, which sounded like an owl hooting.

“For you young people who want to take shortcuts, the price of crystallised Darkness energy particles is not something a newly advanced Magus can afford. I doubt you have that many magic crystals, so as a favour as your senior, I’d like to offer you another option…”

Leylin furrowed his eyebrows even more. “What option?”

“A trade! You should be aware that once we get to this level, all ordinary resources mean nothing to us. Only fellow Magi on the same level as us have the supplies we require…”

“What do you need?” Leylin didn’t have a good feeling about this.

“One thousand! I need a thousand spirits brimming with energy! If you provide me with them, all of these Darkness crystals will belong to you.”

The old witch’s eyes shone with excitement.

“Are you out of your mind? If you want me to collect a thousand spirits within the light Magi domain, you might as well be telling me to commit suicide!”

Leylin replied indignantly.

Extracting spirits was a meticulous task, and in order to obtain the amount that the old witch desired, at least ten thousand people’s lives would be consumed.

If Leylin were to harvest such a gargantuan amount, he would definitely be on the death list of white Magi!

“I’m not asking you to harvest spirits here. You can do it in the dark Magi’s domain!” The old witch’s face was nonchalant.

“That’s much too far, and will consume too much time. Furthermore, I do not wish to incur the wrath of more dark Magi forces!”

Leylin immediately shook his head and rejected the old witch’s request. “Since you posted a notice at the trade centre, I imagine you still require some magic crystals. It’s not as if there aren’t any spirits sold in the Nightless City. At most, you’d have to spend more time to amass them…”

“Alright then. However, young man, I have to remind you that the price of the Darkness crystals is not to be underestimated!”

The old witch had an internal struggle for a while, before realising that her requirements were a little too much, while walking back behind the counter.

*Ping Ping Pang Pang!*

After rummaging through the drawers for quite a while, the old witch finally placed a conical glass bottle on the counter.

At the bottom of the glass bottle was a layer of semi-solid crystals. It let off a mysterious lustre as if wanting to suck in the souls of those peering at it.

“300 grams of crystallised Darkness energy particles. Every gram will cost 100 magic crystals!”

“Kiddo, I’ll still reiterate my earlier suggestion. As long as you bring me 1,000 spirits, these will all be yours!”

The old witch tried her best to tempt Leylin.

“No need for that!” Leylin shook his head. However, the given price did surpass what he could pay.

Most of his magic crystals were earned from selling potions that he had brewed. After the bloodbath in the academy, he also managed to earn a huge amount, obtaining many magic crystals and precious ingredients.

However, to offset the amount he spent yesterday, those resources were mostly diminished.

Leylin did not plan to be so foolhardy as to harvest 1,000 spirits just for the sake of this small amount.

Even amongst the dark Magi, if one were to massacre large amounts of humans and harvest their spirits, he or she would be seen as the evilest of existences.

Leylin did not wish to live the life of a street rat1 in the south coast, receiving animosity from everyone.

“Can I use other ingredients to compensate for the remaining amount?” Leylin asked.

“Yes!” The old witch nodded. “However, I only accept ingredients pertaining to spirits. As for those kinds of items, I will only offer a 90% rate for them!”

“Spirits?”

Leylin suddenly understood that this old witch was a Magus who was most likely specialised in spirits. Right now, her experiments had reached a critical point, and she required large amounts of materials for her conjectures and theories.

Leylin did have plenty of precious ingredients on him, but many were still useful to him, and he did not plan on letting go of them anytime soon. Upon the realisation that this old witch was also researching spirits, Leylin’s eyes flashed as he came up with an idea.

“How about… Advanced information regarding spirits? Will you accept that?”

Leylin asked.

“Advanced information? Let me have a look first!” The old witch’s expression brightened.

Leylin chuckled, withdrew a pearl the size of a thumb, and handed it over.

This pearl was a special tool used to store memories. While conducting his research as an acolyte, Leylin had recorded some information regarding spirits and stored it within the pearl.

Although Leylin was only an acolyte at that time, with the help of the A.I. Chip, his research on spirits was extremely profound. It could even surpass the knowledge of his academy’s professors.

Moreover, Leylin only intended to reveal some of the information that he had discovered in his earlier stages.

As for the experiments such as optimising the Blood Vengeance Potion and the bit of information that he had obtained from the Book of Giant Serpent, he was prepared to keep it for himself.

The old witch gave it a once over, “It seems to be research materials at an acolyte level. I won’t reject…”

However, with the passing of time, her expression turned solemn, and she even seemed to be entranced.

“Such exquisite experimentations! Also, the unique perspective! How about the rest of the information! Hurry up and show them to me!” The old witch snarled, looking slightly deranged.

However, upon seeing this scene, Leylin smiled confidently.

“So then, we should be able to discuss and work out the price of this information…”

A dozen minutes later, Leylin left the old witch’s shop smiling.

The glass bottle containing the Darkness crystals was nested safely within his robes.

He had somewhat underestimated the zealotry that the old witch had for spirit research. The information earlier had been sold for a price of 20000 magic crystals almost immediately.

After Leylin withdrew another 100 high-grade magic crystals, the Darkness crystals were immediately sold to Leylin.

Moreover, after looking through Leylin’s experiment research, the old witch seemed to have a complete change in attitude. She became extremely affectionate towards Leylin and even invited him to collaborate in an experiment.

This was quite a sensitive matter, and Leylin eventually rejected after giving it some thought. However, he did leave his secret imprint with her. Although her craziness made Leylin rather reluctant to befriend her, it was undeniable that she had quite a few useful items. Moreover, Leylin had a plan that required a partner like her to carry out.

……

“Magus Leylin, it’s you again. How was your afternoon?”

Under the flickering lamps of the street, Leylin returned to his villa.

Along the way, he coincidentally met that red haired geezer, Crew.

This old geezer was resting on his couch with a contented look on his face. Beside him were several maids with voluptuous clothing, who fed him delicacies time to time.

“Does this old geezer have a fetish for being the target of voyeurism?”

Leylin was somewhat speechless regarding Crew’s nonchalance about seeking pleasure out in the open.

However, he still smiled on the surface. Resting against the fence, Leylin said, “It went okay. I managed to purchase some of the items that I yearned for…”

“Haha… After staying here for a long time, you will realise that Nightless City has everything you need!”

The old geezer chugged down the grape wine in his glass, before grabbing a maidservant beside him and smooching her out in the open.

As for the other maidservants, they chuckled, as if it was a common sight.

Although Leylin knew that after advancement, some Magi would give up on further improvement and turn lewd, engaging in wanton ways, it was still a first for Leylin to see such a sight. It had somehow widened his perspective. After exchanging several more sentences with Crew, Leylin returned to his villa.

Leylin laid on his bed upon returning to his bedroom, recollecting the day’s events.

After obtaining the old witch’s crystallines, Leylin saw that there was still some time to kill. At the same time, he contacted the Magus that wanted to trade the Darkness crystals for the egg of the Fire Ingesting Bird with wishful thoughts, wanting to purchase it off of him through other methods.

However, Leylin did not succeed, as the other party only wanted the egg of the Fire Ingesting Bird. Even though Leylin offered a 50% increase from the market price, it still did not move the seller.

Finally, Leylin could only reluctantly spend several hundred more magic crystals, and put out a notice at the trade centre saying that he wanted to purchase Darkness crystals, before returning to the villa.

“A.I. Chip! Show me my stats and simulate the best way to absorb the Darkness crystals!”

Leylin thought inwardly.

[Mission establishing, gathering Host’s data, beginning model simulation!]

After receiving the command of its host, the A.I. Chip began to rapidly calculate, and rows of data began to flash past Leylin’s eyes.

The next day, Leylin relaxed while strolling throughout the city, finding a restaurant to have a sumptuous feast before returning to his villa.

The basement of the villa had been remodeled, and a large spell formation had been carved into the surface of the floor.

Leylin placed the Darkness crystals that he had recently acquired at the centre of the formation.

“Based on the A.I. Chip’s calculations, the crystals’ absorption rate will achieve an efficiency of 94.7% when placed within this formation.”

Leylin murmured to himself, as he came to the centre of the formation.

“Activate!” He said the opening command in the ancient Byron language.

* Buzz buzz! *

The entire spell formation vibrated, emitting a bright light.

In the heart of the formation, the Darkness crystals began to melt. First, they shifted from a half-solid state to a liquid state and filled in a bizarre rune. Immediately after, a bright red light flashed, and the liquid within the rune vaporised into black smoke, which circled within the basement.

The black smoke converged, and seven indistinct snakes with red eyes emerged, twisting around Leylin’s body.

Ice cold and slimy, the little snakes formed from the smoke resembled a real snake in every way, giving Leylin a bizarre sensation.

Leylin breathed in deeply.

*Sssii!*

Two tiny snakes were immediately sucked into his nose.

Leylin felt as if his body had expanded, and he felt tipsy as if he was drunk.

* * *

TL Note: Unanimous hostility from everyone.

Chapter 152: The Bloodline’s Transition

The five remaining tiny snakes issued cries of terror while struggling to escape Leylin’s reach.

Suddenly, Leylin opened his mouth and inhaled sharply.

All five tiny snakes were all swallowed inside his stomach.

Meanwhile, the spell formations on the ground emitted black lights, engulfing the entire basement.

Wrapped in darkness, Leylin had a feeling like he returned to his mother’s womb— serene and comfortable.

Only the constant notifications from the A.I Chip could be heard.

[A large amount of essential substances are entering the Host’s body, confirmed to be Dark energy particles, absorption in progress…] [Host absorption rate greatly enhanced under the effect of the Darkness rites, crystal utilisation increased!] [Absorption complete! Host’s elemental essence conversion greatly increased, currently 35%.]

*Di!*

A crisp tone sounded in the centre of the formation. Following which, the black light converged into the shadow of a figure at the centre.

“Huff…”

Leylin gradually opened his eyes, and a flash of black light streaked past his eyes.

“This feeling…”

Having the elemental essence conversion increase to 35% so quickly was a strange sensation. Leylin could clearly feel that in the surrounding void, tiny black particles of the Darkness element were hovering around like fireflies.

Although Leylin had a Darkness elemental aptitude, being able to sense the energy particles in the air this easily was still a first for him. It was a feeling of novelty. Moreover, Leylin could sense that it required less spiritual force than before to control the energy particles.

“Latent Fireball!”

Leylin quickly chanted the spell, and from the darkness of the basement, countless black fireballs flew out.

Flames gathered in Leylin’s hands and became five times larger in an instant.

Corrosive flames continuously formed and raised, and even the roof of the basement gradually turned red, seeming to be on the verge of melting.

“A.I. Chip. Calculate the current stats!”

Leylin muttered inwardly.

[Rank 1 Magic: Latent Fireball. Degree of attack: 40.5. Additional damage from elemental essence conversion: 10.5!]

“As expected! The might of the latent fireball has risen sharply compared to before, and the amount of spiritual energy and magic power needed has been decreased.”

Leylin’s lips quirked in a slight smile.

His elemental essence conversion had already reached 35%, which allowed him to have an increase in prowess when he cast Darkness spells. Moreover, as it was energy particles that were from his elemental affinity, the consumption of spiritual force and magic power was lowered too.

“If my elemental essence conversion reaches 100%, I wonder what kind of extent will it reach…”

There was an outward expression on Leylin’s eyes.

Right now, his elemental essence conversion was only at 35% and it had brought him this many benefits. If he was a fully converted elemental Magus, then he could rival the existences of those ancient elemental beasts!

Of course, Leylin was clear deep down that humans were, after all, not elemental creatures, so the possibility of 100% elemental essence conversion was minimal at best.

To some Magi, as long as they reached 80% elemental essence conversion, they could attempt to advance to a rank 2 Magus.

As for those with 90% elemental essence conversion and above, they were the geniuses that were groomed by powerful guilds.

“100% is an unreasonable goal. However, with so many good conditions that I possess, I must have at least a 90% elemental essence conversion before I advance to rank 2!”

The studier the foundations were built, the more benefits one could reap after advancement in the future. This logic had been long since comprehended by Leylin back when he was an acolyte.

“Crystallised energy particles! I need large amounts of crystallised Darkness energy particles!”

His eyes were blazing with a fiery passion.

After waiting for a few minutes, Leylin went to the spiral staircase in the basement.

“A.I. Chip! Check my current stats, and see if there are any residual effects or injuries on my body. Calculate the amount of time needed before I can use the energy particles again!”

A flash of blue light appeared in front of Leylin.

[Leylin Farlier, Rank 1 Warlock. Bloodline: Giant Kemoyin Serpent. Strength: 7.1, Agility: 6.7, Vitality: 8.5, Spiritual force: 29.8, Magic power: 29 (magic power is in synchronisation with spiritual force). Status: Healthy]

Based on the stats that A.I. Chip had calculated, after using the crystals, not only had Leylin’s elemental essence conversion rapidly increased to 35%, his spiritual force had also risen.

[Residual substances have appeared in Host’s body, determined to be elemental impurities! Currently in the process of expelling impurities from the body. Estimated time needed: 4 Months, 21 Days!”

The results that the A.I. Chip gave left Leylin somewhat shocked.

Magi who used external resources to advance would often cause themselves some problems. He had known this since long ago. However, he didn’t think that the damages would have been this much lesser than expected.

“This can’t be correct! According to the meditation technique and the Book of Giant Serpent, after using the crystals, the backlash will only be the invasion of negative energy and a temporary loss in ability to sense the energy particles in the surroundings?”

Leylin was somewhat puzzled. If using such crystals had such a good outcome, then the price should have been several times higher.

The reason for the circumstances that happened to him most likely stemmed from his own body.

“A.I. Chip, find out the reason why!”

Leylin could tell that this probably had to do with his Warlock bloodline. Ever since his body had taken in the ancient blood of the Giant Kemoyin Serpent, his body had been continuously merging with the blood, also transforming his physique.

The change in his body when he advanced into a Rank 1 Warlock had been minimal. There was also still a large amount of blood that was constantly merging with his body, which unknowingly gave him many benefits.

[Mission establishing, obtaining authorisation! Beginning microscopic analysis. Scanning in progress!]

The A.I. Chip quickly cast a light blue diagram in front of Leylin.

It was a diagram of a human’s DNA helix structure.

The difference between him and regular humans was that on Leylin’s diagram, there were many barbs on his helixes. These barbs vaguely formed the shape of a mysterious rune.

This rune was somewhat similar to the rune that Leylin saw while transplanting the bloodline. Furthermore, it seemed to expand continuously, as if wanted to cover the entire model of Leylin’s DNA.

[Abnormality in genetic information found in Host’s body. Endocrine secretion is different from normal humans. Cell activity increased, increasing effect of expelling poison!]

At the bottom of the diagram, the A.I. Chip came up with a conclusion.

From the A.I. Chip’s conclusion, it could be seen that upon receiving the bloodline, Leylin’s body was constantly getting stronger. His body’s ability to expel poison had also exceeded most rank 1 Magi, to the point that it was able to dispel the residual impurities caused by the usage of the crystals.

[Beep! Based on analysis of the Host’s DNA, the Giant Kemoyin Serpent’s bloodline is getting stronger, and will soon undergo a transition. Estimated time: 1 Year, 09 Months.]

The A.I. Chip prompted Leylin with another frame.

“Bloodline transition?”

Leylin suddenly thought back to the records in the Book of Giant Serpent.

If a Warlock’s bloodline was extremely concentrated, and if the level of the bloodline exceeded that of the Warlock by a large margin, the power of the bloodline would remain stagnant within the Warlock’s body, and accumulate until it underwent a transition!

For every transition in the bloodline, the Warlock’s body would undergo a drastic change!

What Leylin had transplanted was the purified bloodline of the ancient creature, the Giant Kemoyin Serpent. If one were to quantify its level, it would be at least a rank 4 Morning Star Magus.

As for Leylin, he was only a rank 1 Magus as of now! The concentration of the bloodline was too high, so it could only be dormant within his body. After Leylin’s elemental essence conversion and spiritual force had reached a certain threshold, it would then enhance him with a deeper harmonization.

“It seems that the ancient creatures’ bloodlines are mysterious yet powerful, which far exceeds my expectations!”

Leylin who was walking up suddenly halted.

“There’s still 1 year and 9 months huh?”

The second transition would bring immense benefits to Leylin. The most obvious change would be the leap in power!

“If that is the case, a lot of my plans from before should now be modified!”

Leylin’s eyes flashed, “A.I. Chip, are there any methods to hasten the arrival of the second transition?”

[Mission established! Searching within the database!]

The A.I. Chip quickly began to compute. [Lacking in data, unable to proceed! Beginning simulation!] [Possible methods — 1: Using Bloodline Crystals. 2: Obtaining a spell formation that can strengthen the bloodline…]

That was also one of the benefits of the A.I. Chip being upgraded. When important data was missing, it could establish conjectures, and provide a case scenario with the highest rate of success to the Host.

“Weren’t these two items already extinct within the south coast years ago?”

Leylin was somewhat speechless, “Is my only option to wait this out?”

After walking to the top of the spiral staircase, Leylin opened a wooden door that had a metal hoop and came to the study room of the villa.

“It seems that I have to look for some servants and the like!”

Leylin sized up the empty villa.

There were multiple rooms here, as well as a professional kitchen and stable. By the looks of it, these had been prepared for a Magus’ servants.

After most Magi advanced, they would usually find themselves a few servants or followers, and some might even accept apprentices to service them.

It was a very rare situation for Magi who had advanced to still live alone, as Leylin did.

“I guess I should make changes to the original plan!”

Leylin looked around the villa. “It’s a good opportunity to stay here for a while and take care of matters such as getting servants.”

Originally, Leylin had been planning to undergo a series of expeditions to acquire resources for his advancement after settling down in the Nightless City.

However, from the looks of it, since he already knew that his strength would be greatly boosted in 2 years’ time, he could afford to give it some time and wait it out.

For Magi, two years were not a very long period of time. As for Leylin, who had the bloodline of an ancient creature, his lifespan was higher than most Magi.

“Since I have decided to stay in Nightless City for a while, I should not be idling around. I have to create potions for sale and join other guilds to obtain protection and high-grade information. These can all be carried out at the same time!”

Thoughts ran through Leylin’s mind as he suddenly remembered his neighbour, the red-haired geezer.

This neighbour of his would definitely be helpful in this area.

Chapter 155: Jeffrey’s Purifying Potion

“Silence!”

Seeing the chaotic scene, Tyne, who had stayed quiet all this while, suddenly spoke.

In a split second, tremendous spiritual power swept through the hall like a storm.

“This is the assessment to enter my Four Seasons Garden. If you have no wish to participate, the door’s right there. Please feel free to leave.”

Tyne pointed to the small door at the side.

It instantly became unnaturally quiet.

“Good! Are there none who want to withdraw? In that case, let the examinations begin!” Wade glanced at the Magi under him, nodded, and a golden hourglass appeared in the middle of the room. Grain by grain, the sand started to fall.

Seeing that it was time to begin, the magicians quickly ran to their workbenches and started to handle the materials they had.

Leylin found himself a space in the corner, and since there were many workbenches within the hall, nobody was going to fight him for this place. At the moment, he was still relaxed enough to be judging the performance of the acolytes.

Since these Magi had all chosen Four Seasons Garden, it was natural that they had achieved a certain level of attainment in Potioneering. All of the magicians began to operate the equipment on the workbench in a skilled manner, motions quick and methodological.

“From the looks of it, I’ll have to reveal a bit of my skills…”

Leylin grinned and got to work…

“Hmm?”

Tyne, who had been sweeping his gaze over the applicants, suddenly made a sound of surprise.

“What happened?” Wade asked his friend in a hushed tone.

“That Magus! His brewing methods are extremely… perfect!” Tyne came up with the word after a long pause.

“Look! Even though the other magicians are skilled, they tend to make mistakes. However, there isn’t the slightest bit of a lapse in his hands or in his movements. Everything is so stable as if it’s a textbook example but in real life.”

“Hmm… You’re right! If you hadn’t brought it up, I would have missed it!”

Wade watched the young man in the corner who was engrossed in handling a green plant.

The young man was currently using his right hand to heat up the beaker, the fingers on his left hand constantly emitting yellow flames. When combined together, the colour became a striking red.

“This is the Flame Combining Method unique to the dark Magi domain, and is a high level technique used in Potioneering. To think that he’s so proficient in this method…”

Wade wore an expression of admiration on his face. “It looks like we’ve found ourselves a promising seedling. Let me see what his name is…”

Wade immediately went through the stack of application forms and quickly found the young man’s name on the last piece of parchment.

“So he’s called Leylin? He comes from the Abyssal Bone Forest Academy in the Poolfield Kingdom, and has offended the local Lilytell family!”

“If that’s all there is, it seems like we’re going to be welcoming another comrade soon!”

Tyne’s usually emotionless face twisted in a smile.

For the magicians in the light Magi domain, they were uncaring of the fact that Leylin had offended those in the dark Magi region. After all, these two areas were at odds with each other in the first place.

What they were most afraid of was if Leylin had offended any of the local large-scale Magi organisations. That was the most troublesome.

At times, in order to maintain the guise of unity and solidarity, they had no choice but to reject talented Magi who were on the light Magi organisations’ wanted lists.

The magicians were focusing on completing their own potions, and seemed not to have heard the two Magi, who were engrossed in conversation.

All of a sudden, a Magus dressed in a black cloak made a sound. His hand trembled, and the chemical within the test tube that was already transparent instantly became cloudy.

“Bastard! You’re looking to die!”

The black-cloaked Magus roared, countless black rays gathering in his hands as he dashed towards a blonde female Magus at another side.

“Stop right there!” Wade bellowed, his body shimmering with light. A rune nearby the experiment tables shone, trapping the Magus within the area.

“My lord, she…” he protested.

“I didn’t see her doing anything, I only saw you trying to attack a fellow Magus participating in the assessment!” Wade snorted.

“If this happens again, you’ll lose the right to participate.”

The black-robed Magus seemed extremely dissatisfied as he clenched his fist. After tarrying for several minutes, he then dispelled the radiation of energy waves in anger.

“I am going to kill you!”

He glared viciously at the blonde Magus. Afterwards, he picked up another set of ingredients and began his brewing again.

“This is… An attack on the sly?”

Leylin’s hands did not stop moving yet his emotions began to surge.

Just then, the A.I. Chip’s scan detected a tiny trace of an extremely covert spiritual force from the female blonde Magus that had attacked the black robed Magus.

Potioneering was a highly delicate process, and any tiny slip up could cause the whole brewing process to fail.

The black robed Magus had been interrupted at a crucial moment, and the potion he was brewing was naturally destroyed in an instant.

Although a spiritual attack was slight, a semi-converted elemental Magus would definitely be able to sense it.

However, these two examiners prevented the black-robed Magus from seeking revenge.

“Could it be that the test allows one to strike covertly, but it cannot cross a certain margin nor be too obvious?”

Leylin surmised.

With this said, the difficulty of the test had increased again. Leylin was stunned by the harshness and reality of this test from the Four Seasons Garden.

“However, on the other hand, the stricter the test is, the greater the benefits obtained later on!”

Right now, he was fuelled by a fervent desire.

*Bang!* *Bang!*

The commotion from just now seemed to have caused some sort of chain reaction, and in a short moment, another two Magi slipped up.

There was a cold glint in Leylin’s eyes.

Using the A.I. Chip, he could distinctly feel that there were two minute waves of spiritual force aimed towards him.

Their target was the Potion in his hand that was close to completion!

“A two pronged attack?”

Leylin laughed. To talk about the minute control of the spiritual force, Leylin who had the A.I. Chip to help him would not be afraid of anyone!

“A.I. Chip, begin secondary task and destroy the spiritual forces together with me!”

Leylin commanded inwardly. Very soon, a layer of spiritual force that had a trace of Darkness aura met the two similar spiritual force head on.

*Ka-Cha!* *Ka-Cha!*

At the point of contact between the spiritual forces. Leylin’s spiritual force had rapidly overlapped, turning into the form of a small snake. Its tiny strength continued to stack, and after several rounds, its might momentarily multiplied by several times!

*Boom!*

The two opposing spiritual forces were destroyed the moment they came in contact with Leylin’s spiritual force.

Not only that, Leylin’s spiritual force still followed the pathway of the two spiritual forces and began a fierce counterattack.

“Urgh!”

“Argh!”

Two sudden cries were sounded in the hall suddenly.

The potions of the black robed Magus and female blonde Magus immediately turned to ashes. Furthermore, two streams of blood flowed down from their noses.

“Interesting! Earlier, I felt that the acting of the black robed Magus was somewhat poor, but now, have they been colluding?”

Leylin smirked. His elemental essence conversion had been significantly boosted. Also, with the help of the A.I. Chip, these two were unaware, and had actually taken a small hit from him.

They most likely had to recuperate for a period of time before fully recovering from the spiritual force attack from earlier.

”My Lord! I forfeit!” The black-cloaked man glanced at Leylin in fright, and promptly lowered his head, afraid to look him in the eye any longer.

“Me too!” The blonde Magus yelled.

“Permitted!” Tyne answered.

The two Magi quickly gave Tyne a bow, and darted out of the hall.

Unexpectedly, neither of them had any complaints or glared at anyone.

“At least these two know their place!”

Leylin thought nothing of their behaviour.

Magicians respected power. In the earlier exchange, he could tell that the two Magi’s elemental essence conversions were not higher than 10%, so they most likely had only just advanced.

They posed no threat to the current Leylin.

It seemed they were well aware of this fact, and quickly withdrew from the assessment, even being afraid that Leylin would pursue the matter.

“Did you see that? What an interesting performance!”

Wade grinned as he spoke to Tyne.

“Yes, his elemental essence conversion is of a rather high level. His ability to manipulate spiritual force is also amazing!”

Tyne nodded, his expression stern.

“And I was still worried that he was a spy from some organisation! I’m afraid nobody would be willing to use someone like him as a spy!”

“So this is your conclusion?” Wade blinked. This was the first time Tyne had such a good impression of somebody.

“No! This is just my hypothesis!” Tyne’s usually expressionless face suddenly had a mischievous smile.

“You!”

As Tyne’s colleague, Wade naturally knew that his counterpart’s frosty indifference was just an act. In fact, Tyne had a mischievous mindset.

As for Wade, who looked more normal between the two, he often had to take the blame for Tyne’s behaviour.

“The Jeffrey’s Purifying Potion! I’ve completed it!”

At this moment, Leylin indicated his completion by waving his hands.

This voice was extremely abrupt in the originally silent hall. In a moment, many gazes from magicians glanced at Leylin.

Firmly held in Leylin’s hand was a test-tube with a milky white substance.

Wade came in front of Leylin, and carefully took the potion from him. He then began to scribble on a form.

“Very well! You can leave now. Ten days later, come to the recruitment area at the communal centre, and await for your results!”

Wade gave Leylin an extremely warm smile.

“Many thanks!”

Leylin smiled and bowed before leaving from a side door.

He understood that the test had been successfully passed. As long as there were no problems when they reexamined his current status, the Four Seasons Garden would never deny his entry.

Outside of the communal area were the wide streets of Zone 2 in Nightless City. The bustling activity on the streets continued, as people continued to pass by.

Anyone who had registered and provided their paperwork were allowed to stay in Zone 2, so Leylin was even able to see some regular humans here.

Chapter 156: Pass

Regular humans who lived in the domain of light Magi had better lives than those in the dark Magi domain.

Furthermore, the revered magicians even allowed them to obtain resident rights in Zone 2 as long as they continuously worked hard for it.

However, from what Leylin saw, it was only a different form of management.

Regular humans were treated at the same level as wild grasses in the dark Magi domain, and they did not receive management very often. The only thing was that they would be harvested in times of need.

As for the light Magi, they treated these humans as pieces of property; hence, they could afford to invest huge amounts of time and effort to manage them in order to reap greater benefits.

Even in the most open minded domain of the light Magi, magicians always had a position far above regular humans. Furthermore, this gap in status surpassed the gap between regular humans and nobles.

Leylin saw many situations in which regular humans, even those that seemed to be nobility, respectfully moved aside and gave a deep bow when they saw an acolyte.

Leylin paid no mind to these situations, however. The test today was rather taxing, and he was prepared to enjoy a hearty feast, then proceed to Crew’s house to inquire about some matters.

The old geezer was very talkative, and Leylin wasn’t planning on asking him anything confidential, so he was naturally willing to entertain Leylin.

* Crash! *

“Ah!”

Suddenly, a little girl in a white dress, who was chasing something like a rubber ball, bumped into Leylin’s leg.

Rather than Leylin, who stayed in the same spot, the little girl fell backwards onto the ground.

She opened her eyes wide, and when she saw Leylin in his leather armour, she promptly began to cry in fear.

The congested street instantly became quiet, and regular people quickly backed away. Even a few acolytes yelped, “official Magus,” and phrases along those lines, and bowed while drawing back.

“My lord! Please forgive my daughter for unwittingly offending you!”

At the moment, a slightly plump noble prostrated himself in front of Leylin. He had cold sweat dripping down his quivering body.

In the Nightless City, the authority of the official Magi were extremely high. Even if they were to casually kill several humans, they would, at most, only be fined a set amount of magic crystals.

If Leylin’s mood wasn’t good, he could just kill these two people here, and they wouldn’t be able to do anything but accept their fate.

The plump noble kowtowed as he pulled the little girl to kneel as well. “Quickly, seek forgiveness from the Lord!”

This atmosphere that seemed like a befalling calamity had also influenced the little girl. She held back her sobs and blankly stared on.

“It’s alright!”

Leylin picked up the rubber ball on the roadside and handed it to the little girl. He even ruffled her hair with his right hand.

“It’s no big deal! No need to worry!”

“Thank you, Lord!” “Thank you, Lord!”

With a feeling of a renewed life, the fatty’s words were choked back. Even the little girl that he had brought along seemed to heave a sigh of relief.

“Do not be this impudent in the future anymore!”

Leylin nonchalantly lectured the fatty before leaving the scene in large strides, as the revered gazes of the passerby stared on.

“Do not be this disobedient in future anymore. Fortunately, this time, it was a kind magician. If it wasn’t…”

The fatty wiped off the sweat on his forehead as he scolded the girl.

As for the white-robed girl, she looked at the direction Leylin headed towards with admiration.

……

Nine days later, in a spacious room.

An old Magus with a head of white hair and gilded spectacles was looking at the pieces of information he was holding in his hand.

Within a transparent crystal ball, lines of text appeared.

“Leylin Farlier! From the Chernobyl Islands. Entered Abyssal Bone Forest Academy in the year 20987 of the Saint Yuan Calendar!” Next to these words, there was also a picture of a boy who was around thirteen or fourteen years old, and very similar in appearance to the current Leylin.

On another crystal ball nearby, there was a detailed record of Leylin’s experiences in the Abyssal Bone Forest Academy. As long as the information was made available to the public, it was all written there. There was even an article regarding the matter of how he had offended the Lilytell family.

“Hm! For the sake of a couple remnants? Seems reasonable!”

The old Magus nodded.

“Look, should we ask him to hand over the research materials he obtained from the ruins?” A Magus with a third eye on his forehead said.

“No, all official Magi have their own secrets. We need to learn to be lenient and tolerant, or else all of the magicians in the organisation would end up only acting for their personal benefits, leading to the segregation of groups!

There were several Magi who had journeyed throughout the south coast and managed to break through. If Four Seasons Garden demanded Leylin hand over his research, it would definitely draw the ire of other Magi, which would definitely provide no benefits for them.

“However, based on Wade’s information, that Magus called Leylin had a slightly different aura than regular Magi. He might have broken through with some ancient methods…”

The Three-Eyed Magus was somewhat unresigned.

“Those alternative paths that a Magus might take may not have the advantages that you think they might…”

The old Magus looked at Three-Eyes beside him, and could not help but remind him.

“Time is the best judge. In the long history of competition, several tens of thousands of years have already passed. Branded Swordsmen, Elemental Bards, and Divine Warriors have all become extinct with the passage of time. Only we, who are the most traditional of magicians, have been preserved. Does this not explain everything?”

The old Magus’ eyes shone with wisdom.

“For some subclasses, although they might have favorable conditions when they advance, most of their routes on the path of advancement become blocked. It’s not even close to us, who can see continuous progress with constant cultivation in meditation techniques.

“Moreover, one must believe in time and the power of influencing through good will! Learn to embrace them!”

The old Magus smiled with confidence.

“We should not treat him as an enemy, but as a friend. After some time, he will naturally sense our good will. Moreover, the bountiful reserves of our Four Seasons Garden will definitely contain something that he needs!”

The old Magus merely adopted a soft approach instead of a hard one. Even with such an approach, it did not mean that he had given up on obtaining the information.

“Other than the Lilytell Family, is the Magus called Leylin really not a criminal wanted by anyone else?”

The old Magus asked again.

“I’ve checked multiple times, Mentor!” Wade bowed, “After Leylin went to the south coast, he usually stayed within the compounds of the Abyssal Bone Forest Academy to study. He had little contact with other powers, and nine days ago, he…”

Next, Wade gave a brief summary of how Leylin let go of the father and daughter a few days ago.

“Look, he’s still on the side of the light!”

The old Magus smiled as he spoke to the three-eyed Magus.

“Hmph! It’s just for show!” The three-eyed Magus made a sound of contempt.

“We always look at their actions, and not their heart!” the old Magus said a proverb.

“Even if it’s a show, it also shows his willingness to enter a white Magus’ faction! That’s a lot better than those unrepentant dark Magi!”

“In that case, do you mean…?”

Three-Eyes bowed slightly.

“Tell the Potioneering team that we have found them someone with potential…”

……

Naturally, Leylin would not know of such events. However, he more or less grasped the general situation.

With the strength of the Four Seasons Garden, it was very likely that all of his experiments from a young age until now would be displayed in front of a table that would be vetting him!

Furthermore, they would most likely infer that he had killed Bosain for the inheritance and was now on the run.

However, he was not worried at all.

The great Magus Serholm had utterly destroyed the Dylan Gardens. Since the dead party could not verify anything, they would at most reckon that he had obtained some subclass Magus information, and could have only advanced to an official Magus with some luck, so his future progress would be extremely limited.

Moreover, he was now an official Magus. Other guilds would definitely have official Magi who advanced under similar circumstances, and if they were to try to get to the truth, they would not be able to gain the trust of these Magi who had advanced in special scenarios. At the very end, they were still forces of the light Magi, so no matter how they thought inwardly, they had to show a good reputation on the outside.

As long as Leylin was able to hide the meditation technique of the great Magus Serholm and the A.I. Chip’s purification of bloodlines, he was not afraid of letting them find out about other things.

Just as he expected, the moment he reached the reception area, he could see that Wade, who he had previously met, was already there waiting for him.

“Nice to meet you, Magus Leylin!” Wade smiled as he bowed towards Leylin.

“Congratulations on passing the test. From here on, you are a member of the Four Seasons Garden!” Wade gave a passionate smile.

“I am also honoured to enter such a great organisation as the Four Seasons Garden!”

Leylin had a look of excitement on his face.

“There are still a few contracts and procedures we need to go through regarding your entry. Please follow me!”

Wade walked in front and led the way, bring Leylin out of Nightless City.

Seeing the look of doubt on Leylin’s face, Wade explained, “Even though Four Seasons Garden has a few laboratories and a reception area in Zone 5, our headquarters is in the outskirts of Nightless City.”

“I see!” Leylin nodded, following Wade to a region near the gates to the city.

In front of Leylin was a large square, and in the middle, there were several wooden crosses, to which creatures of all shapes and sizes were tied.

“This is one of the Four Seasons Garden’s contacts, from which you can choose a specialized mount!”

Wade pointed at a giant magical creature that had just landed from the air.

“Although you can rent them, I suggest that you buy one for your personal use as transportation!”

Wade walked to a small wooden hut beside the plaza and greeted the person inside through the window.

“Madre, give me two Dragon Crown Nighthawks, as I wish to go to the headquarters!”

“I got it, I got it. You told me already!” The man behind the window impatiently answered, and tossed out two green metal sheets.

Chapter 158: Decarte

“Good, now let’s speak about your allocations…”

Reynold told Leylin.

“According to Wade, you have an amazing talent and ability in Potioneering. We cannot allow such a talent to be neglected. After some consideration, we are prepared to arrange you into the Potioneering team. Do you have any objections?”

“I couldn’t wish for anything better!” Leylin smiled.

Since there were Potioneering teams, there should be other alchemy teams, battle teams and more. Leylin only wanted to enter the organisation to get a salary and gather some resources. He definitely would not be willing to endanger his life fighting battles for them.

As for being able to join the Potioneering team, the requirements should be related to Potioneering, which was something he specialised in.

It seemed that intentionally having exposed his innate skill and strength from before had helped him in his promotion.

“Alright! Wade, bring Leylin to the Decarte of the Potioneering team, and then come back. In regards to the Moonflower Flame incident, I think there are better ways to deal with it……”

“Yes, teacher!” Wade gave a bow, and took Leylin away with him.

“What do you think? My tutor is a good person, right?”

Wade asked Leylin with a sense of pride and boasting. Being in front of Leylin, who was now a fellow comrade, he was visibly much more relaxed.

“He is a wise and amiable senior!” This time, Leylin naturally would not sing a different tune.

“Ha ha…… everyone says that. Come, let me bring you to the Potioneering team. Decarte, over there, is overly conservative, but he still attentively cultivates truly talented young magicians….”

Wade divulged a quite a bit of information without much thought.

At the end of the turn, a magician in black robes emerged.

This magician exuded a twisted and chilling murderous aura with faint howls from vengeful spirits, causing Leylin to feel sensitive.

The most eye-catching thing about this magician was his vertical third eye in the middle of his forehead.

The vertical eye was always open, and its pupil was pitch-black. It seemed to lack feeling or sensation, causing one to not help but shiver.

“Wade, this new Magus doesn’t seem to be very polite……”

The three-eyed Magus said coldly. An icy spiritual force immediately pounced onto Leylin.

“Hmmm?!”

Leylin was caught by surprise, and immediately gathered his spiritual force to defend.

*Pop!* Fine bubbles of air in the atmosphere began to pop.

The moment their spiritual forces met, Leylin could feel that his opponent’s spiritual force contained a strong aura of fresh blood. This kind of odor was so dense that Leylin nearly suffocated as he could not dispel it.

And besides, his opponent’s level of elemental essence conversion far surpassed that of semi-converted elemental Magi. Leylin’s spiritual force collapsed under his opponent’s attack.

As if a sledgehammer had smashed into Leylin’s chest, he stumbled two steps back, and his face turned white.

The three-eyed magician looked bewilderedly at Leylin, “Your spiritual force is not bad, but it’s a pity that it was still insufficient…”

Subsequently, he did not take another look at Leylin, and proceeded past them.

It seemed that the Magus was trying to show off and demonstrate his prowess.

“Are you okay?” Wade looked a little worried for Leylin.

“No problem, my spiritual force is just a little shaken up. A few days of rest is all I need to get better!” Leylin looked in the direction of three-eyed Magus as he left, “Who is he?”

“He is Lord Caesar, a Magus personally nurtured by the Four Seasons Garden, and with valiant fighting strength. He is in charge of the hunting team, and is the role as our deputy commander!”

Wade looked at Leylin with a bitter smile on his lips.

“Lord Caesar believes that foreign magicians will only damage the Four Seasons Garden’s unity, and believes that recruiting new magicians should be banned…”

As if afraid that Leylin would worry, he added on, “Of course, my teacher, Lord Reynold, does not agree with his point of view. Furthermore, my teacher was one of the pioneers of this organisation. At the present, the Four Seasons Garden’s higher authorities are still in favour of recruiting new magicians…”

“Head of the hunting team……”

Leylin glared in the direction of Lord Caesar, and a ray of light flashed from his eyes.

“A.I. Chip, estimate the opponent’s strength!”

[Based on the spiritual force emitted by the opponent, target’s strength estimated: Rank 1 Magus with peak strength, elemental essence conversion above 80%…]

“With this kind of strength, it bears a resemblance to the elder from the Lilytell Family. By the looks of it, if I was paired to battle against him, I’d have little chance of winning…”

Tons of complicated ideas were swirling around in Leylin’s mind.

“Okay, let me bring you to the Potioneering team…”

Wade quickly changed the topic, and Leylin followed behind Wade without comment.

Along the way, Wade tried his best to speak about other topics, hoping Leylin would forget about the unhappiness from earlier on. Even though they both knew it was impossible, Leylin still acted as if he was listening attentively.

“After becoming a part of our team, you can live here permanently in a house for free. However, life here is very monotonous; we just conduct experiments after experiments. Hence, many magicians like to own housing in the Nightless City, so that they can have a vacation over there from time to time…”

Wade responsibly told Leylin what to expect. After crossing several forks in the road, they came to a stone bridge that spanned mid-air across an overhanging cliff, which led to a botanic garden.

The floor here was made of metal, and the surroundings were a tidy and clean shade of white, causing the misconception of returning to his laboratory from his past life.

On both sides of the road, there was also transparent glass.

Behind the glass were petri dishes, in which various sorts of exotic plants had been planted.

Walking Earth Grass, Giant Food Flowers, Face Vines… With just a casual sweep of his eyes, Leylin found countless precious plants. Some were even important ingredients for cultivating spiritual force, but of course, they were only effective for acolytes.

Any newly recruited rank 1 Magus would be astonished at all these things, but Leylin had seen the great Magus Serholm’s Dylan Gardens that he had personally cultivated, and all these plants were nothing compared to what he had seen before.

However, a shocked expression still flashed across his face.

“We’ve arrived. This is the Potioneering headquarters!”

Wade brought Leylin through the garden, and arrived in front of two huge stone statues that resembled monsters.

“Password!” The statue started to speak.

“Tell Decarte that I’ve brought someone here for him! And also, don’t make jokes to amuse yourself! If it happens again, I’ll tell the teachers to change all guarding systems in this facility! You should know that I have that power!”

Wade bellowed at the statue.

As if he knew that Wade wasn’t joking, the enormous stone statue monster chuckled before getting out of the way.

“These two statues seem to have been manufactured defectively. The creator mistakenly stuffed a couple of mischievous spirits into the statues. Just ignore them!”

Wade brought Leylin through, then told Leylin.

“Mischievous spirits?” Leylin stared blankly, while immediately recalling a written account from an illustrated handbook.

“Those that resemble goblins, and tease people for their own pleasure… Those spirits? This is really… it deserves our sympathy!”

“To be honest, I also have some sympathy for myself!”

While Leylin was speaking, a tunnel behind the stone statue was opened, revealing what seemed like a structure of a ginormous auditorium.

There was a huge gold chandelier suspended from the ceiling of the auditorium. There were plenty of giant candles on it, illuminating the auditorium.

In the auditorium, there were numerous unusually long white birch tables with all sorts of delicacies spread on top. There were only a few magicians, and they were sitting far away from each other. Only a few of them who seemed to have a better relationship huddled together to chat.

The voice from earlier on belonged to a middle-aged magician on the platform.

“Here, let me introduce to you, this is Lord Decarte, the head of the Potioneering team. He is a Magus at the peak of Rank 1, and on the verge of breaking through to Rank 2!”

Wade smiled as he saluted Decarte, then said to Leylin.

“Lord Decarte!”

Leylin quickly bowed.

“Hehe, I know you! I’ve seen the clip of you brewing the medicine; your technique was really admirable! From now on, we’ll be colleagues! Everyone, please give a toast to our newest comrade!”

Decarte snapped his fingers, and two cups filled with mead flew in front of him and Leylin.

“Cheers!” All of the magicians present raised their cups.

“Thanks!” Leylin took the cup. The mead’s alcohol content was not high, and it tasted like sweet liquor. Its taste was pleasant.

“Well, since I’ve sent Leylin here, I will be taking my leave!”

Wade drank his wine in one shot, “My dear teacher is still waiting!”

“Since you still have something to attend to, I shall not delay you any further. Leylin, come! Sit here!”

While Decarte was speaking, the acolytes beside him immediately arranged a new long table. Countless kinds of delicacies and fruits were continuously brought to the table, quickly piling up onto the table.

Leylin slightly bowed and arrived at his own seat.

Only at this time did he have the chance to size up Decarte, the formidable Potioneering team leader.

Decarte wore white robes, onto which green plant designs had been embroidered.

His face’s shape was common, and on his forehead was a dark green headband, making him look extremely indolent.

Around Leylin, there were also a couple of servants, who were dressed glamorously. From the aura they gave off, they were level 3 acolytes from noble families.

He took a look around. Solely in this auditorium, there were at least thirty official Magi, and countless acolytes.

This was only a Potioneering team. In terms of overall strength, it had already surpassed the Abyssal Bone Forest Academy.

The banquet carried on for about an hour and a half. After the majority of the magicians had finished eating, the acolytes brought beverages of different colours. The atmosphere in the auditorium slowly cozied up, resembling the tea parties Leylin had attended in his past life.

“Alright. This meal and welcoming ceremony are over. Let us discuss the allocation of work now…”

Decarte spoke on the platform, his voice resonating to the ears of every magician present.

Upon hearing this, the magicians put down their cups.

“Elmo! How’s the progress of the Giant Dragon Strength Potion?”

A voluptuous female magician stood up, “I am about 70% done with deducing the formula, and am currently stuck at some crucial points. I am applying for the third centrifuge and supplies from the fifth garden…”

“Good. After the banquet ends, submit an application form!” Decarte nodded in agreement.

Chapter 159: Exchange

“How about you, Martin? How is the brewing of the monthly 300 doses of Frost Potions?”

Martin was a short old man, and when his name was called, he seemed uneasy as he stood up.

“Si… Sir, you know it. I am having a shortage of manpower… Also, recently, the apparatuses have…”

“I don’t care what your reasons are, Martin. Isn’t this the third time already?” Decarte’s face darkened.

“Please… Please forgive me, Sir!” Martin’s face reddened.

“It’s timely that you’re lacking in manpower. Leylin will first be assigned to your team, and I will provide you with another 3 synthesizing machines. If you are still unable to complete your task by next month, your allowance for this year will be greatly reduced!”

“Yes, Sir!” Martin could not help but to wipe the sweat off of his face.

Leylin, who heard his name being called, got up.

Next, Decarte called on several other magicians, inquired about their progress, and made the necessary arrangements.

After the banquet, Leylin took the initiative to slow his footsteps and walk alongside Martin.

“Having you come to my team… I’m sorry…” Martin apologised.

“It’s not a problem!”

In any team, all newbies had to suffer at the beginning, and Leylin was well aware of this fact.

“Alright, let’s move on. I’ll bring you to the lab and your room. There’s also some stuff that you’ll need to know.”

Even though Martin looked quite inept, he was enthusiastically guiding Leylin through the registration processes.

“Take it. They’re the keys to your room, as well as your identity token!”

The old geezer Martin brought Leylin to a house that was constructed of black stones. Also, he handed over an old bronze key and an identity token to Leylin.

The ancient key was modelled in an old fashioned way.There were even some characters inscribed on it.

As for the identity token, it was made of a translucent metal, with Leylin’s name and other information carved onto it.

“Just with this token, you are able to go to the organisation’s resource point and obtain a portion of precious ingredients, as well as some advanced information.”

Martin explained to Leylin with patience.

“This token is extremely important, and if you lose, it there will be quite a hassle. You must definitely protect it well…”

Seeing that Leylin nodded his head to express his understanding, Martin brought Leylin to view the experiment labs and rooms.

“The experiment lab is a common shared area, and its number is dkh-328! The apparatus in it is rather decent, and enough for an official Magus. Furthermore, if you have any other special requests, you can apply for it through the organisation. As long as you have enough contribution points, the organisation will do their best to fulfill your requests….”

Leylin had heard Martin mention contribution points before. They were a method that the Four Seasons Garden used to gauge the merits of individual Magi. After finishing the appointed amount of work required, an official Magus could obtain contribution points.

These points could not only raise the status of the team but could also be used to exchange for essential resources and knowledge.

From what Leylin could tell, this was a form of currency in the Four Seasons Garden.

“Speaking of contribution points, since you have only just entered, I’m sure you don’t have enough. How about it? Do you want to accept one or two acolytes? These kinds of assignments give the most contribution points.”

Martin suggested helpfully.

“Actually, I don’t have any plans on teaching anyone anytime soon!”

Leylin smiled and refused Martin’s request.

“However, how does the academy function to protect a member’s family?”

Leylin briefly stated the issue of him offending the Lilytell Family to Martin.

Under the insurance of safety and personal benefits, Leylin would not mind leaving a lifeline for the previous Leylin’s Farlier family

After all, he was still the eldest son and heir to this family in name.

Also, if the opportunity presented itself, Leylin wished to make up for the fact that he had borrowed the body of this family’s child.

“Oh, don’t worry about it!”

Martin listened to what he said and shook his head.

“Our Four Seasons Garden is a lot more powerful than the Abyssal Bone Forest Academy. As long as we get in contact with them, the Farlier family in the Chernobyl Islands will definitely be taken good care of! Furthermore, based on the contract that you’ve signed with us, before it’s certain that you’re dead, the Lilytell family will definitely not be able to hurt your family of regular humans.”

“There’s such a rule?”

Leylin was a little curious. No matter that world he was in, it was acknowledged that harming one’s family was a very good way causing one to seek revenge, much less in the Magus world, where the regard of law was lacking.

“Is this… the fear of revenge?” Leylin guessed.

“Exactly. You’re fast!”

Martin looked pleased with Leylin. “An official Magus that has nothing to tie him down is the scariest. Especially the fact that the Lilytell Family’s members are not all magicians. There are definitely acolytes and normal human beings amongst them…”

Leylin understood that this was a mutual fear of each other.

Before his death was confirmed, as long as the Lilytell Family dared to strike at the Farlier Family, it would definitely incur the wrath and revenge of Leylin.

Also, with the strength of an official Magus, slaughtering those humans and acolytes would be as easy as eating rice and drinking water.

Even if the Lilytell Family was rather established, they would definitely not be able to handle such a loss.

Hence, the Farlier Family would completely be safe.

“What’s more, you’ve joined us!” Martin’s expression was one of pride, and perhaps conceit.

“The Four Seasons Garden’s might is not something that the likes of the Abyssal Bone Forest Academy can even begin to compare to. After hearing that you joined our side, they might have even thought of withdrawing their order for your capture!”

“I don’t really care about that!”

Leylin thought about Bosain, who he had killed. This acolyte of nobility seemed to be the sole grandson of the elder of the Lilytell Family.

In addition, they had also dispatched a rank 1 Magus to kill him, who had ended up dying by Leylin’s hand.

This enmity could not be so easily resolved.

“I’ve heard that the competition to be the next head of the Lilytell Family has reached the most crucial point. That elder is also known for being headstrong, and will not tolerate my existence. Otherwise, his image and reputation will be ruined…”

On the contrary, as Leylin thought of this, a look of anticipation appeared in his eyes.

Right now his strength was rapidly increasing. Moreover, once he underwent his second transition of his bloodline, his strength would definitely be boosted by a significant amount. At that time, it would not be a matter of whether the enemy would let Leylin leave, but whether Leylin would let them go.

……

Four months later.

Leylin wore a loose white robe, with patterns of green plants embroidered on the sleeves and collar.

This was the uniform that official Magi in the Four Seasons Garden wore.

He was presently passing through the side roads in the mountain of the Four Seasons Garden’s headquarters.

After walking through a tunnel full of little plant people, he arrived at an ancient square.

The square seemed to be constructed in the heart of the mountain and was very large. The ceiling was made of solid rock, and an innumerable amount of everlasting light spells had been added to the wall, brightening up the entire room.

This was the place in the Four Seasons Garden where he could exchange contribution points for resources.

Here, whether it was an acolyte or Magus, one could use contribution points and gain the materials and information that they wanted.

In addition, as an official Magi, Leylin was able to gain his monthly allocation for finishing his monthly tasks.

Many magicians who wished to join the Four Seasons Garden were attracted by this temptation, which was second only to having a large backer supporting them.

Leylin specifically walked towards to counter that handled the redemption of contribution points for official Magi.

The staff member in here was actually an official Magus as well. This official Magus was a female, with ocean blue hair that softly rested on her shoulders. On the sides of her lips, there were traces of gills.

“Hello, may I ask what you require?” The female Magus asked using the common language of the south coast, her voice extremely gentle and pleasing to the ears.

“This feeling…” Leylin was instead alarmed, “It’s extremely similar to the time when I was brewing the Azure Potion, where the voices of mermaids singing were heard…”

“It seems that this woman has a trace of the mermaids’ bloodline…”

Leylin’s expression on the surface was indifferent, as he looked at the woman and handed over his token. “I am here to retrieve some ingredients; is there a catalogue for them?”

“This is the catalogue of the items that you are currently able to exchange for!” The female Magus swept her eyes over Leylin’s token and seemed surprised as she looked at Leylin. After that, she pretended that it was not a big deal, and handed over a catalogue to him.

Leylin looked at the list of items on the catalogue in detail.

This list was extremely long. Not only were there many resources that were precious even in the Nightless City, there were also many pieces high-grade information, and the latest results of experiments.

Furthermore, Leylin even saw some spiritual force potions that were meant for an official Magus’ consumption. However, the contribution points required were so high that Leylin could only long for them.

“Sky Flower Welk Fruit, Dwarf Frost Runes, Elemental Crystals!”

Leylin’s fingers stopped when they traced the words of ‘elemental crystals’ on the catalogue. His previous backlash from consuming them had now disappeared, so he could once again obtain more crystallised Darkness energy particles to raise his elemental essence conversion.

Leylin fervently looked through the entry of the elemental crystals, and finally, at the end of the list of the names of energy particles, he found the name that he was searching for.

“Crystallised Darkness energy particles: able to effectively raise the elemental essence conversion of a Magus. Also has major residual effects. Use at your own risk! Available: 5850g. 1g = 1 contribution point. Limit: Regular team members can only buy a maximum of 50g per month!”

“This price?”

Leylin frowned.

Based on this method of calculation, he could purchase 50g of elemental crystals at the most, which would deplete his contribution points by about half.

He had used up 300 grams of crystals, which raised his elemental essence conversion to 35%. With another 50g, at the very most, he would be able to raise it to 40%, which just wouldn’t be enough!

Chapter 160: Four Seasons Secret Plane

“Why is the price of these crystals so expensive?”

Leylin could not help but blurt out, “Also, there’s a limit to the quantity that I can purchase?”

From the looks of it, with such a method for calculating the price, elemental crystals were one of the most expensive items in the catalogue. Their prices were only second to that of a spiritual force potion.

Leylin had stayed in the Four Seasons Garden for four months and had been allocated 10 contribution points per month. This meant that even if Leylin stayed idle, he would be able to get ten contribution points per month from the Four Seasons Garden. Furthermore, he had joined Martin’s squad, and every time he completed a mission, he would receive a fixed amount of contribution points.

However, even after adding all of these up, it was actually still not enough to buy many items.

“Although the backlash of the elemental crystals is great, it is undeniable that it can boost the strength of a Magus. Naturally, it is an item that is highly sought after.”

The female Magus seemed to have heard these questions countless of times, so she did not hesitate with her reply.

“Give me 50 grams of elemental crystals, and on top of that, add these two pieces of high-grade information!”

Leylin paused and thought, before pointing to the catalogue and saying to the female Magus.

He knew that he had made a mistake; the Four Seasons Garden’s monthly allocation of resources could not be stacked up, but was instead fixed for every month.

That was to say, Leylin could obtain up to 50 grams of elemental crystals per month, but he was not able to wait and receive several months’ worth of allocations at the same time.

Moreover, even if he knew beforehand that the monthly allocations could not be accumulated, he, who had just joined, did not have that many contribution points allocated to him in the first place.

“A total of 80 contribution points!”

The female Magus took Leylin’s badge and waved it above a black machine. Bright red lights flashed.

Following that, she then retrieved the items that Leylin had requested from behind the counter.

“Thank you!”

Leylin stuff the items in his robes and left the plaza with a heavy heart.

“Leylin! Leylin!”

A short magus, with a height of merely one meter and a skull like a gnome, hurriedly ran to Leylin.

“You’re just in time. Follow me, Martin was just looking for you!”

From what Leylin knew about this short Magus, he had also been temporarily assigned to Martin’s group. The two of them had accomplished a significant amount of missions together and had a decent relationship with each other.

“Is anything wrong?”

Leylin was a little curious.

As the leader, Martin would usually lead and plan the task. In other areas, however, Martin had little presence.

“It seems like this is related to this month’s task!” Leylin said. The short Magus revealed a delightful smile.

“Ever since Leylin joined Team 3, our rate of success has been steadily increasing, allowing Martin to gain favour with Lord Decarte! In addition, since our group has been performing exceedingly well, Decarte has started assigning us other more challenging tasks with higher quality rewards.”

“This time, it probably has to do with this matter……”

“Other tasks?” Leylin was a little curious.

Ever since he had joined Team 3 under Martin, the tasks that had been assigned to him had always been the brewing of frost potions and the like.

In this complicated and taxing task, the presence of the A.I. Chip had begun to show its advantages. Leylin’s completion rate was exceptionally stunning.

Thus, although Leylin consciously hid some of his progress, deliberately committing mistakes, his contribution to the small team was remarkable, gaining him the respect of many of the members.

Leylin followed behind the short Magus, passing through a couple of long and narrow forks, and eventually arriving at Team 3’s meeting point.

*Pong!* The iron door opened up at once.

“Leylin!”

Martin was slumped over at a long table and using a red pen to write, but after noticing Leylin, he briefly put his existing work on hold, his face revealing a pleasant smile.

To him, Leylin was basically his savior.

With Leylin’s entry into the team, he had been able to complete his own task, assuredly securing his own resources this year, and also helping his team accomplish some marvelous tasks.

It was only now that he believed that Leylin was his lucky star.

There were other members of Team 3 in the spacious room. Upon seeing Leylin, their faces displayed amicable smiles.

“Great! Now that everyone is present, I shall talk about this month’s task!”

Martin happily took out a scroll wrapped with a golden ribbon out from his robe, steadily opening it in front of Leylin and the others.

“Our task this month is to maintain a specific area within the secret plane. Reward: 50 contribution points each!”

*Clamour*

Even though they were aware that the task this time around would be very good, the Magi situated below were in chaos.

“It’s actually to enter the secret plane! This is really…” The short Magus had a very excited look on his face.

At the corner, Leylin revealed his surprise too. “Such a huge reward, and also, a secret plane?”

A secret plane was a domain that ancient Magi had constructed in order to house resources or conduct experiments. It was isolated by spells, and by the looks of it, the Four Seasons Garden possessed such a place as well.

“I almost forgot, Leylin, you have just joined not long ago, and probably are still unaware of the secret plane!”

Martin closed and rebound the scroll, smiling as he walked towards Leylin.

“Leylin, from what you know, what is the one thing that a Magus values the most?”

“Talent and resources!” Leylin answered without hesitation. This was the common consensus from all Magi in the south coast.

“Not bad. A Magus’s aptitude is set from birth, and is impossible to change, and the only way to make up for it thereafter is in the resources aspect!”

“With sufficient resources, even a Magus with an average aptitude can possibly reach the footsteps of a gifted Magus… …”

Martin showed a face of awe.

“Thus, once ancient Magi advanced, they would search for an area that had a high concentration of elemental energy particles, and construct a secret plane to nurture and grow resources… For this reason, it is the root of many ancient Magi remnants that you see now!”

“As for the current generation of Magi, they are far from the overpowering might of ancient Magi, who could cast isolation spells on their own, and set up spells that could stretch and compress space… some needed resources like space rocks for the construction, which cannot be found by the current age Magi!”

“Thus, at the current south coast, the inner circles of magisteriums have joined forces to open up and cultivate a part of a secret plane as a mainstream activity…”

“Perhaps, there are a few lucky ones. Those who are so lucky that they can cause jealousy, obtaining ancient remnants and inheritances and controlling a secret plane. That is really a story of instant success…”

Martin’s face was tinged with envy.

Of course, Leylin knew what a secret plane represented, as the knowledge that he had previously gathered at the Dylan Gardens had been deeply etched into his memory.

Simply owning a part of a secret plane would mean the provision of limitless resources!

For a Magi who especially required resources, this was an irresistible offer.

However, the capability of a Magus was limited, and one unable to build a new secret plane on his or her own. Only when working together could Magi build a secret plane.

Leylin had predicted the existence of similar places in the Abyssal Bone Forest Academy, but because his level had been lower back then, and he had advanced into a Magus after leaving the Academy, he was unable to prove this point.

“Leylin, you have only been here for a few months, and yet, you are entering into the secret plane. The upper management seem to have a lot of confidence in you, huh!”

Martin patted Leylin on his back in a friendly manner.

“Not at all! Not at all!” Leylin gave a modest expression, appearing rather shy.

“Ha Ha… …Let’s go!”

Martin laughed and took the lead, and Leylin himself followed closely behind him.

The entrance to the Four Seasons Garden’s secret plane was near the headquarters so that it would be easy to deploy forces to guard the entrance.

Leylin and the rest followed behind Martin, and after following five to six roads, they reached the entrance to the secret plane.

On the way there, Leylin used the A.I. Chip, and felt the five or six energy waves scanning over his group.

Furthermore, the Magi guiding the entrance were of semi-converted elemental strength and beyond.

These types of stringent and vigilant checks caught Leylin by surprise.

Standing in front of them, the stern looking Magi examined the scroll that Martin was holding once more. After which, Martin turned back and shouted to Leylin and the rest, “Get ready, the entrance is about to open!”

The entrance to the secret plane was a door made out of a big slab of stone, and the borders of the big door were embossed with differing intricate designs.

On a platform beside the entrance, there was a Magus sitting cross-legged, whose countenance was concealed. Extremely mysterious and strong energy waves radiated from his body.

“This is the guardian of the academy! Hurry up and greet him!” Martin led the group of magicians and bowed first.

“This is… At least a rank 2 Magus’ energy waves. It seems like the importance of this secret plane has far surpassed my guesses!” Leylin’s eyes flashed as he bowed like the others.

“Since the inspection is now over, let us enter!”

The guardian waved his arm and chanted an incantation.

*Weng Weng!* The stone door moved, and a white light radiated from behind the door, giving off a feeling of energy waves emanating from the void.

Having had previous experience in exploring secret planes, Leylin was familiar with the undulations that indicated the opening of the plane.

At the same time, a bright light was produced from the scroll in Martin’s hands, and enveloped the entire group.

When the white lights met and fused, it produced a blinding glare.

As the glare eventually vanished, Martin, as well as the other magicians, were revealed to have disappeared.

“Ugh!”

Leylin rubbed his eyes, which were stinging in pain. “This is really uncomfortable!”

He found himself standing on top of another platform, on which many acolytes were walking around.

Unlike the previous scenery, the surroundings were a sea of green.

The sky was a pure blue, and the surrounding air was extremely fresh.

“Are we within the secret plane? It seems quite large!”

Leylin stroked his chin. “A.I. Chip, analyse the surroundings!”

[Beep! Scanning in process! Compared to the air in the outer world, the density of energy particles within the secret plane is higher by 34.7%!]

The A.I. Chip displayed a chart in front of Leylin, quickly giving him the data that he required.

Chapter 162: A Meeting

No matter how great the Four Seasons Garden’s secret plane was, it did not belong to him. Therefore, Leylin did not want to reveal his trump cards for the sake of it.

Also, as a newly advanced Magus, it was just a pipe dream for him to own a secret plane all to himself.

Apart from these couple stray thoughts, Leylin did not have any better methods that he wanted to employ.

……

Seven days later, the crisp caw of a Nighthawk sounded. Leylin sat on the back of a Dragon Crown Nighthawk while flying back to the Nightless City.

The missions to maintain the secret plane were indeed some of the most popular missions.

Leylin and Oak only spent seven days to cleanse the eastern part of the secret plane. Not only was the disease cured, they managed to drive away droves of ferocious beasts.

After which, Leylin and the others who, had nothing else left to do, were sent out of the secret plane. On each of their tokens, there was a huge number of contribution points added.

“I can try my earlier plan now. Also, I need to find several more servants. If I were to do everything myself, it would be a waste of my time…” Leylin thought.

After a span of four months, the backlash from consuming the Darkness crystals disappeared. However, the Four Seasons Garden’s supply was far from enough, so Leylin could only shift his attention to that old witch in the Nightless City.

He remembered that the old witch’s shop had a number of good items.

The sea of people in the Nightless City was the same as before. Leylin flew directly to the passage that hosted the revered magicians and showed his ring to the guards, before entering the city under the respectful bows of the guards.

Suddenly, Leylin’s robes shook. A green light forcefully radiated through his robes.

“En?”

Leylin furrowed his brow, and withdrew a pocket sized diary.

A green secret imprint flashed with light, and from it, the voice of an old lady sounded. “Hey Leylin, are you here yet?”

From the tone of the voice, Leylin could detect a sense of urgency.

Ever since he had handed over a copy of his research on spirits from when he was an acolyte to the old witch, she had proved to have an extreme interest in it. Furthermore, she even given her secret imprint to Leylin.

During these past few months, she seemed to have gotten some progress in her experiment, but she was caught in a bottleneck. Hence, she had been continuously sending messages to Leylin.

It was a pity, however, that Leylin had been inside the Four Seasons Garden brewing potions to exchange for contribution points, so he hadn’t paid her any heed.

However, this old witch was extremely patient, and had been sending Leylin a message every few days.

“What is it? Didn’t I say that I would try my best to come over as quickly as possible?”

Leylin said to the secret imprint.

At the same time, his footsteps halted, and changed directions towards a deserted alley. He also applied a layer of isolation magic on his body.

“This time, I have amassed many items. Do you remember the crystallised Darkness energy particles? I have a total of 500 grams here, and I swear that you won’t regret it…”

Knowing Leylin’s temperament, the old witch hurriedly tossed out her bargaining chip.

“500 grams?” Leylin’s brows relaxed, and the original feeling of tension disappeared.

With that many Darkness crystals,combined with the ones he had been saving, it would definitely bring his elemental essence conversion up by another notch.

However, the Darkness crystals were not almighty. According to Leylin’s estimation and the A.I. Chip’s calculations, if these crystals were to bring his elemental essence conversion up to 70%, then it would already be a godsend.

What’s more, the backlash would be extremely terrifying. If his vitality was not superior to other normal magicians, he wouldn’t dare to be this crazy.

“Yeah, this time I spared no expense, and even owe some old freaks a couple of favours now… Do you remember our previous transaction? Give me the latter half of the information, and all of these crystals will be yours. Also, there is some prospect of the things that you mentioned to me before happening. As for the details, wait until you come to my shop…”

The old witch’s voice gradually faded, but Leylin could tell that she had a certain amount of confidence.

“Okay, wait for me. I’ll be right there!” Leylin closed the diary, and hastened his footsteps.

Within Nightless City, Elm Street #231!

“Hehehe… You actually got here so quickly. It seems like you’re also anxious to get the items I have!”

Seeing Leylin entering the shop, the witch immediately closed the main doors. It seemed that she was prepared to stop operating her business for the rest of the day.

“You and I are both Magi, but if not for the fact that we both had something the other party wanted, we would not be gathered like this. Don’t bother trying to play these mind games!”

Leylin carefully scrutinised the old witch’s appearance.

She looked more aged as compared to before. Furthermore, her hair was shrivelling and falling out. It seemed like she had gotten older by thirty to forty years.

“What has happened to you?”

Leylin casually asked.

“It’s nothing much, just a backlash from an experiment!” The old witch obviously did not intend to elaborate.

“All 500 grams of Darkness crystals are here!” The old witch shook her head and placed a black bottle on the counter. Her body was extremely thin, as if she could collapse and die any given moment.

Inside the bottle, there was a layer of half solid and half liquid translucent crystals—the same as what Leylin had seen before.

“Before this, how about the thing I had entrusted you to look for previously? Are there really any prospects now?”

He had made a request to the old witch before, and that matter was no ordinary task.

“Of course, people who are similar are the most sensitive to one another. From your aura, I completely believe in your identity as a dark Magus. Furthermore, the guild behind me is very willing to have you join us…”

The old witch panted and sat on a chair made of vines while talking.

What Leylin had asked of the old witch from before was naturally to seek out an organisation operated by dark Magi.

Even within the Nightless City, which was controlled by the light Magi, there would definitely still be the existence of shadows. These were the grounds where the dark Magi would operate!

After all, Leylin was still a dark Magus through and through. To him, slowly gathering resources like other Magi, and spending time and effort to seek a chance to break through, was far too inefficient for him!

Furthermore, Leylin did not own a secret plane, and with his current wealth, he would definitely not be able to establish one. As a result, he could only work for an organisation in exchange for resources. Such a cumbersome process was unbearable to him.

As for the crudest way of obtaining resources, it was always done through bloodthirsty means. How could a slow and steady accumulation beat the instant gaining of resources through plundering? Although this method had a certain degree of risk, after doing some calculations, Leylin felt that it was within his risk threshold.

In fact, this was the most common thought of the dark Magi.

One could nurture a secret plane on any given day, but once there was an immediate increased need for resources, looting or plundering would have to be done.

As for the previous encounter, Leylin realised that this old witch was not just a dark Magus. Her shop was most likely a contact point for the disposal of stolen goods, and a meeting place for the dark Magi.

Hence, he had a notion about what was to come.

After all, with his current capabilities, he would not be able to plunder a secret plane, so he would need the help of other magicians.

“En! When will you bring me to see your head?” Leylin asked.

“What about my reward?” The old witch refused.

“First, look at this!” Leylin tossed a scroll to her after thinking.

The old witch caught the scroll, and her eyes squinted. “En! It seems to be an introduction to a type of spiritual force potion. The ingredients required are really rare; you actually need a spirit…”

“Guk Kuk…” Suddenly, as if something got stuck in the old witch’s throat, she let off a gag, her face filled with disbelief.

“This is… A spiritual force formula of the ancient Magi! The primary steps have actually been filled in…”

She looked at Leylin in alarm. “Give me the rest of this information, and the deal will be sealed! I can even give you other types of compensation, and my treasures will be for your taking!”

Towards the old witch’s suggestion, Leylin scoffed. “Are you kidding? A copy of a spiritual force potion of the ancient Magi is only worth this much?”

“Then what do you want?”

The old witch’s face darkened, and a dark spiritual force energy wave emanated from her body.

*Whoosh!* As if a strong wind had passed through, the items in the shop began to shake.

“You wish to attack? Don’t forget that we’re in the Nightless City right now!”

Leylin reminded her as he smiled gently. After which, his eyes flashed, and an immense wave of spiritual force with an inconceivable darkness enveloped the shop.

*Bang!*

The two forces clashed, and several explosions occurred in the air. The glass bottles in the surroundings cracked open, and several organs and fresh blood seeped from them.

“You actually have such a huge improvement in your spiritual force?” The old witch staggered back two steps, apparently shocked.

“Not only that, look at this too!” Leylin withdrew the identification badge of the Four Seasons Garden, and flashed it at the witch.

“The identity token of the Four Seasons Garden! To think that you had already joined them!”

The old witch was evidently more afraid now.

“Hey hey! Is this Elm Street #231, Marie’s Emporium? I detected strong spiritual force energy waves from your shop earlier; do you need any assistance?”

A milky white light from a secret imprint floated on the old witch’s counter.

“No… It’s nothing. Just a leakage of a failed experiment from earlier…” The old witch looked Leylin in the eye, and said to the secret imprint.

The other party was silent for a moment. “Then I will make this record. Moreover, you have flouted clause 762 of the Nightless City’s security law; please come to the communal centre to pay your fines before the 13th…”

Evidently, the other party had his suspicions, but as the perpetrator of this event, the old witch did not voice any problems, so the other party did not bother to pursue the matter any further.

“I know!” The old witch answered the other party in a superficial manner, before shutting off the secret imprint.

In the Magus world, strength alone was not everything. One needed to have some kind of backing as well.

Chapter 163: Collaboration

Not only did Leylin display his immense might in front of the old witch, he even revealed that he had the backing of the Four Seasons Garden. Hence, the old witch now had no choice but to take him seriously.

As for the possibility of the other party catching hold of Leylin’s weak point?

Right now Leylin had not joined any dark Magi organisations, so why would he be afraid of that?

Also, after successfully joining the organisation that the old witch was in, everyone would be in the same boat. Leylin also had other plans, and would never allow this old witch to reveal them to others.

*Crash!*

A heap of high-grade magic crystals that radiated huge energy waves was emptied on the table, along with a dozen black magic crystal cards.

These magic crystal cards were made of the essence of 1000 magic crystals, which was the origin for many formations source of energy. Hence, they were extremely sought after.

“All of my magic crystals are here. Every item in this shop, as long as you want them, can be yours. If only you could give me that potion’s formula.”

An earnest and pleading expression appeared on the old witch’s face. It seemed that she needed this potion’s formula very badly.

This turn of events left Leylin somewhat shocked.

From what he thought, this old witch would definitely be enthralled by it, but not to such a crazy degree.

However, this situation was naturally more favourable towards him now.

Leylin appeared indifferent as he swept up the magic crystal cards and crystallised Darkness energy particles and stored them in his robes.

“How precious is the formula of a potion that can increase the spiritual force of even official Magi? It isn’t even easy for me to get this kind of item!”

Leylin said nonchalantly, and despair was drawn on the old witch’s face.

“Although the formula cannot be given, we can still cooperate!” Right when the old witch was about to burst in rage, Leylin gently spoke again, causing the old witch relax the energy particles that she had gathered.

“Cooperate? How are we going to do that?”

“You’re an expert in the field of spirits, and the raw ingredients for this spiritual potion are all spirits! You’ll provide the ingredients and do all of the other preparatory work, and I’ll be in charge of brewing the potion. As for the potions that are successful, I’ll get 60% of them, and you’ll get the remaining 40%!”

Leylin suggested.

It was obvious that this proposal seemed to hit the old witch’s soft spot.

In terms of potential, she couldn’t take down the present Leylin, and the power backing Leylin was also one that caused her some amount of fear. In addition, this potion was extremely important to her.

“The ratio is too little. I’ll be obtaining the spirits and doing all the prep work, which is much more dangerous. If I ever get caught by the light Magi, I’ll definitely be chased to the ends of the world!”

The old witch emphasised the fact that she’d be in the most danger.

“That’s the best you’ll get! It won’t get any higher than this!” Leylin wore a deadpan expression. “After all, the formula is in my hands. As long as you agree, we can immediately sign a contract and summon the Trial’s Eye to bear witness to it!”

“…Very well!” The old witch was silent for a long while, before forcing the words out of her mouth.

After picking another time to meet, Leylin left the area with a smile about his lips.

He had been planning on collaborating with her since after their first meeting.

The spiritual force potion that he had shown earlier was naturally the ancient potion formula for the Tears of Mary.

Back when he was an acolyte, he had already completed a simplified version of it—the Blood Vengeance Potion.

After he had advanced into a Rank 1 Warlock and upgraded the A.I. Chip, Leylin finally possessed the capabilities to restore the original incomplete formula of the potion.

This potion was indeed befitting of use by the ancient Magi. According to the A.I. Chip’s simple calculation, the Tears of Mary currently proved to be extremely beneficial for Leylin to speedily increase his spiritual force.

A large amount of spirits that had to be harvested, combined with the early stages of preparatory work, was extremely complicated and savage. The brutality contained was leagues above that of brewing the Blood Vengeance Potion! If the light Magi were to find out, Leylin’s only outcome would be a chase to the death, and even interrogation regarding the formula.

Leylin did not have the time and effort to take on such a risk.

Moreover, due to the potion formula’s special nature, the magicians who could handle the preparatory work had to have to strength of an official Magus and a deep understanding regarding the aspect of spirits.

Right now, the old witch was the only one that fulfilled this criterion.

Within the Four Seasons Garden, there were sure to be Magi who were able to fulfill these requirements, but Leylin wouldn’t even consider it.

This spiritual potion, which was suitable for official Magi, was much more costly than those suitable for acolytes. Furthermore, it was an ancient potion! Leylin wasn’t so stupid as to think that he could keep possession of this formula. It would definitely be seized in the name of the organisation.

Even though the organisation was sure to give him some benefits, would it outweigh the advantages of having sole possession of the formula?

A potion that could raise one’s spiritual power was a temptation that no official Magus would be able to resist.

As a result, with Leylin’s persuasion, the old witch quickly agreed.

In addition, the two of them made an unbreakable vow, to which the Trial’s Eye bore witness.

The old witch was even forced to swear not to leak any information about Leylin or the potion formula.

This was, of course, at Leylin’s request. This way, even if someone found out the old witch’s secret, they would not be able to trace it back to Leylin.

In fact, Leylin pushed all the risk of material gathering onto the old witch!

Hence, he did not hesitate to give her 40% of the potions that would be brewed!

As for the formula of the potion, Leylin had given the old witch most of the contents of the first half. As for the few most crucial steps, it was solely controlled by him.

As long as he held on to those key steps, Leylin didn’t need to worry about the old witch possibly rebelling against him.

These last few procedures were not only extremely tedious but also required the help of the A.I. Chip to achieve true success. Even if others had gotten the complete formula, they might not be able to brew the potion successfully.

As for the witch who needed the potion, she had no choice but to toil for Leylin, taking on the extreme risk of harvesting souls, and also completing the bloody preparation of the early stages of the brewing process.

After signing the contract, Leylin and the old witch were, to some extent, in the same boat, so the matter of being referred to a dark guild would naturally be followed up.

“But that old witch’s reaction was a little strange. She agreed so easily in order to obtain the potion. I was prepared to give her more materials, but she actually agreed to my conditions so quickly, almost as if the potion wasn’t for herself, but for someone else…”

The wheels in Leylin’s head were constantly turning as he ambled along.

“No, this is better for me. If I have misgivings about this arrangement, then I will have something that I can use as blackmail material…”

Under the setting sun’s light, Leylin’s shadow was drawn out onto the streets, looking somewhat malevolent, as if it were a devil…

In the shop from before.

The old witch stood there silently until she confirmed Leylin’s departure. After that, she walked to the counter and pressed on a hidden area.

*Boom!*

A mechanical sound was heard, and the wall at the back of the shop was pushed backwards, revealing a flight of steps that headed downwards.

The old witch held onto her cloak as she slowly walked down.

The staircase was extremely short, ending after just a couple of steps.

This was a basement, and it was positioned right below the old witch’s shop. Moreover, there were many runes inscribed onto the walls of the basement room.

There were a few human bones scattered in the corners of the room as well.

There were many traces of scars on these bones, which could only let one imagine the torture and suffering that the owners went through while they were alive.

A frosty aura continuously encircled the room.

If Leylin was here, he would definitely recognise this familiar feeling. It was similar to the lab back in the Extreme Night City, where he was trying to create vengeful spirits.

*Sssii!* The old witch lit a candle in the centre of the room.

This candle was a transparent white, yet the flame was a dark green. The old witch’s horrendous countenance looked even more malicious under the flame.

“Mother…”

Whoosh! A black tornado swept across the basement, and after a flash of black gas, there was suddenly a translucent figure in the basement.

This figure belonged to a young girl wearing a simple dress. Her shadow was extremely faint as if she was on the verge of dissipating.

“My daughter!” A kindly, yet heartbroken expression appeared on the old witch’s face.

“What happened just now? Why did I feel a strong and vicious energy burst out upstairs?” The girl’s expression was one of suspicion.

“No! It’s nothing, just a slight dispute while I was doing business…”

The old witch looked tense. “Did it hurt you?”

“I’m alright, it’s only that…” The girl crouched on the floor and hugged her knees. “Don’t bother with me anymore; it has already costed you large amounts of resources to protect my existence. If not for me, wouldn’t you have long since advanced?”

“My dear daughter!” The old witch’s eyes reddened, and she wanted to hug her daughter, yet her two hands could only weave through the girl’s ghostly figure.

Following which, the girl’s arms turned even more illusory, as if they were going to scatter any moment.

“Oh! No! Why is this even faster than before?”

Fright appeared on the old witch’s face, and she frantically withdrew various items from her robes and placed them on the floor, forming a tiny spell formation.

In the center of the formation, there was a spirit trapped within a crystal ball.

“Almighty Defiling Mother, I hereby sacrifice the fear of this spirit in return for your blessings…”

The old witch continued to chant in an extremely awkward sounding incantation, all while pointing at the spirit.

“Ah…” The sound of anguish and terror travelled outwards from within the crystal ball, threads of silvery-white gas constantly being drawn out from the spirit’s body.

The silvery-white gas quickly supplemented the girl’s body, and her almost dissipated body gradually became more stable.

“It’s starting again! I don’t want to do this… It’s too… too cruel…” The girl quietly sobbed.

“I found a potion today, and the formula is said to have been used by ancient Magi to raise their spiritual power. It’ll definitely be effective for you! Stay strong! Stay strong for a little while longer, and mother will definitely help you regain your physical body.”

The old witch continuously consoled her.

Chapter 166: A Successful Retreat

Leylin turned around and saw the baldy’s snake shoot an ice bullet, which shattered the innate defense spell of his opponent.

At the same time, the precious boa of his charged, revealing razor sharp fangs and sinking them into the light Magus’ neck.

Baldy’s opponent was a rather young looking Magus with blonde hair and blue eyes. He had an extremely cheery disposition.

It was a pity, however, that right now, this light Magus had death written all over his face. With the continuous constriction of the boa, his life was drained away.

After killing the light Magus, the baldy’s Venom Snake threw Leylin a provocative look.

However, Leylin acted as if he saw nothing, and dashed right into the division of the Ennea Ivory Ring Tower.

“Right now, he wants to be petty about such things and not steal treasures? This Magus is definitely somewhat mental!”

Leylin hurriedly ran past the doors and arrived at a place that seemed to be a library.

“These are all information meant for acolytes, so I’ll forgo them. A.I. Chip, scan!” Leylin’s eyes hurriedly swept the area. This library consisted of two floors, and the total area was rather huge. However, Leylin had read most of the books found here before, so they were not of much value to him.

[Beep! Mission establishing, beginning scan…]

After which, a light blue image was formed and appeared in Leylin’s vision.

Through this image, Leylin could easily discover that between the two floors, there was an extremely tiny passage.

Right now, there was no one in the library, and books and chairs were strewn across the floor. It seemed that the people who were here had escaped quickly.

Leylin strode past the lobby and came to the hidden spot.

“It’s in here huh?”

Leylin looked at the wall before his hands punched into it without hesitation!

*Boom!* Dust flew around in the room, and an extremely narrow passage was revealed at the collapsed portion of the wall.

“Hmm?”

The passage was extremely short, and at the back, there was a small room. There were several shelves upon which some memory crystal balls sat on. Moreover, in the room sat three quivering acolytes.

“Ennea Ivory Ring Tower huh? George isn’t here!”

Leylin gave a quick scan and slightly waved his Crimson Palm.

A blurry red light filled the small room.

The three acolyte’s eyes turned red, and they immediately lost consciousness, their bodies still trembling as signs of life became less obvious. From the looks of it, they wouldn’t live past today.

In front of an official Magus like Leylin, these regular acolytes’ lives were like those of ants. With just a slight misstep, he might accidentally kill a few of them.

Leylin paid no mind as he stepped across the acolytes’ bodies, which were still involuntarily trembling, and came to the front of one of the wooden shelves.

“Elementary Meditation Techniques” “Potioneering Foundations…” “Rune Theories” “Study of Particles”

The crystal balls on the wooden shelves were more valuable items, which could immediately transmit information into a magician’s mind without them forgetting anything.

Leylin’s eyes swept past the crystal balls and noticed that they contained information meant for acolytes, which was not of much use to him. However, there was a clutter of black crystal balls in the middle of all of them, with various tags showing the high-grade information stored within. This caused Leylin to grin…

A dozen seconds later, Leylin walked out from the library, which combusted in flames just seconds later.

At this moment, the whole division was in chaos, with magic spells being continuously fired across the battlefield.

After killing most of the official Magus enforcers, most of the division’s defenses fell apart.

Some were even acolytes who couldn’t resist the attacks of a group of dark Magi!

The dark Magi wilfully plundered resources as they deemed fit, destroying everything they could see before them, and letting loose their inner cravings for darkness.

Leylin watched the scene with a blank expression, using the A.I. Chip to scan the entire branch.

He didn’t have much time, and there was at most a few minutes before Nightless City’s allied forces arrived. No matter how insane Leylin was, he wouldn’t dare to contend with a large number of light Magi.

“From the structure, this isn’t a division of the academy. Rather, this is more similar to a research organisation, with a lot fewer people here…”

Leylin traversed an area with disorganised architecture and idly looked around.

“I found it!”

An excited voice rang out. “Guys, come here! I’ve found the entrance to the secret plane!”

“Hm?”

“That’s great!”

Multiple equally eager voices came for all around the region, and the dark Magi from before all gathered in a small garden.

Here, the large Rodent Magus was constantly rubbing his black claws, his beard sticking up, and his tiny eyes greedily fixated upon an oval object in the sky.

That object seemed to be a mirror with silver rays of light surrounding it. In the centre was a deep and dark spiral.

“I’m sorry, my magic can only show you the entrance to the secret plane. It will take some time to forcefully gain entry!”

The large Rodent immediately asked, “Which of you captured any opposing Magi? Interrogate them and get the password and method to enter!”

“Look for Old Devil, she’s an expert in this field!”

The zombie-like Magus was carrying the naked corpse of a female acolyte, gnawing her flesh from time to time as if savouring a delicacy.

“Hehe… That Magus’ spirit was extracted smoothly by me earlier; it seems like this will be a great harvest!”

The old witch cackled and walked towards the silver circular hole, while chanting an extremely awkward sounding incantation.

*Weng Weng!*

The void emitted energy waves as the circular entrance became enlarged, revealing the dark space of what seemed to be a storage.

“Haha… We have struck the jackpot…” The giant mouse rushed in like a whirlwind, with the following dark Magi following behind.

“I’ll stay behind to keep watch!” The old witch tossed several powder-like substances on the ground. “Anyway, we have to divide them in the end…”

Leylin exchanged a meaningful look with the old witch as he went into the secret plane.

This secret plane was extremely small—about the size of a large warehouse. There was only one passage for people to walk about. On both sides of the warehouse, there were many labeled items and ingredients.

“Hurry! Pick the most valuable items and go, and burn the rest that we don’t need!”

Zombie tossed the female corpse aside and looked at the door of the warehouse, before stepping in with a snort.

Leylin looked at the dark Magi who were happily shoving items into their pockets, and could not help but shake his head.

In the Magus world, those magic artifacts which had spatial capabilities were extremely precious. At most, Leylin had only heard of them in legends and folklore. Until now, he had never seen any Magus owning an item like that.

Hence, most Magi could only carry the most valuable items with them. Every time they went on a mission, they would be carrying many sacks, with some even having horse carriages that were filled with empty chests.

As for right now, there were too many items in this warehouse. Leylin and the others could only choose the most valuable ones, and as for other large items, these dark Magi, who were already consumed by greed, could only choose to destroy them.

“If I had a spatial ring or something like that in future, then it would be much more convenient!”

Leylin rushed into a section where the shelves were filled with various ingredients, as well as heaps of magic crystals that had been tossed in a corner like trash.

Leylin quickly stuffed the precious materials into his own pockets. He immediately ignored the low-grade magic crystals, and only the high-grade magic crystals and magic crystal cards caught his eye.

At this moment, he was still indulging in his fantasies.

“Of course, rather than getting any spatial ring, the best thing to do would be to occupy this territory. That would be real profit without any investment!”

Leylin was a little regretful about this, but he could only bury his delusions into the bottom of his heart.

[Beep! 4 Minute 37 Seconds have passed in the countdown, reaching close to the value set by the Host!]

The A.I. Chip’s voice intoned.

“There’s no more time! Retreat!” Leylin’s eyes reflected his resolution, and he speedily left the warehouse.

“Nightless City’s forces are arriving. Run!”

After Leylin left the secret plane, he heard Rodent’s flustered voice.

“Go!”

Leylin and the old witch nodded, and transformed into two streaks of shadows, which disappeared into the air.

After the retreat of all the dark Magi, Leylin turned back to observe the sight of black flames emitting from Ennea Ivory Ring Tower.

Some of the Magi from the Nightless City who were using rank 1 flying magic descended from the sky.

……

A giant beast dashed past the land.

Looking on, this beast was over 50 metres tall and 200 metres long. Its appearance closely resembled a large hippopotamus, and its jaws occupied almost half of its body size.

With every step that this gargantuan beast took, deep imprints would be made on the ground. Also, there were also tremors, as if mini earthquakes were occurring.

The surrounding animals would scatter and flee after seeing this beast, not daring to stay a moment longer.

Within this beast, the group of dark Magi from earlier were gathered inside of a large hall.

The Magus wrapped in green fog, who went by the name of “Giant,” stood unscathed in the middle, and his aura had not even decreased by much. It was evident that he had disposed of his opponent with much ease.

“Alright! Since all of us here have made our vows and have undergone the judgment of the Trial’s Eye, take out 50% worth of the items that you have plundered!”

Giant spoke in a cold voice.

Despite the chaos of the Magi below, under the constraints of the power of the higher ups, as well as their oaths, they hastily piled some magic crystals and materials in the centre of the hall.

Soon enough, the materials and magic crystals formed a small mountain.

“This all amounts to at least ten million magic crystals!” Leylin’s eyes flashed as he mentally calculated.

“Moreover, this is only 50%. Which is to say, the division of the Ennea Ivory Ring Tower has lost close to twenty million magic crystals, along with the destruction of other items… The Ennea Ivory Ring Tower is going to go nuts this time…”

After giving it some thought, he was a little curious and asked the old witch beside him in a low voice.

“Do we really have to give up 50% of our profits? Isn’t that too much?”

Chapter 167: To Maraud

“You thought… the magic crystals are all for Giant?”

The old witch snuck a glance at Giant, who was saying something, and answered Leylin under her breath.

“Am I wrong?” Leylin was a little astonished.

“Of course not. Even though Giant is pretty impressive, he’s no rank 2 Magus. Out of this pile, he’ll get at most 40% of it!” She pointed to the little mountain in the middle of the room.

“As for the rest, they’ll all go to ‘Boss’!” The old witch was vague.

“Boss?!” Hearing this phrase started Leylin’s imagination.

Magi only respected power. For even the old witch to call someone ‘Boss’, this must mean that this person, Boss, was at least a rank 2 Magus, right?

“Who else? Who do you think is the one warding off the light Magi’s divination magic?”

She retorted with a manic laugh.

“According to what I know, there are at least two to three dark Magi organisations like us. As for their backers, there will also be various people controlling from behind the scenes…”

As they were in a mutual alliance through the previous agreement with the potions, the old witch was evidently placing more trust in Leylin, hence she just told him some information that had been withheld from him.

“Marauding the light Magi’s secret plane is definitely not carried out on a whim by the dark Magi. On the contrary, these operations are systematic and are all premeditated!”

A notion quickly flew through Leylin’s mind and occupied his thoughts.

“Who knows, there might be several powerhouses behind the dark Magi domain that also have a hand in this!” Leylin grinned.

“This seems to be getting more and more interesting…”

However, this had nothing to do with Leylin. His current goal was to join in the dark Magi organisation’s looting operations and obtain large amounts of resources.

Just the efforts from tonight had brought in a revenue of five to six hundred thousand magic crystals! This was obviously more convenient and faster than doing missions for the Four Seasons Garden.

Of course, the risk was no small matter and if he were to be found out, he’d be chased to the ends of the world and be killed.

This was also why every member who joined concealed their identity, and even the few leaders of the organisation had no idea of the real identities of their members.

“Alright! Collect your own share! Remember not to squander them quickly. It’s better to spend them only after some time!”

“Also, after this mission, those mad dogs from the Ennea Ivory Ring Tower will definitely go around biting people blindly in a rouse to find our locations. So remember to stay low…”

Giant who was wrapped in green fog continued to explain of some matters as he waved his hands, “It’s alright now, you guys can leave. Our exchange meetings must also be halted for a while, as for the concrete details it will be made known again…”

……

Baldy Venom Snake had had half of his face melted and the other side filled with many bumps. He was continuously combing through the black forest.

And, with a big black boa lay coiled on his body, he presented a rather horrifying appearance.

*Bang!*

Suddenly, Baldy’s face changed as he rolled to the side.

At the same time, an explosion caved in the ground on which he had previously stood. A purple flame blazed in the surroundings, creating a hundred square meter radius of charred zone.

“Blood Rogue! It must be you! Get your ass out here!” Baldy Venom Snake snarled.

A layer of stiff hair grew on his body, altering his appearance to that of a gorilla.

What he received in answer were multiple fireballs that appeared from within the shadows.

*Boom!*

The speed of the black fireballs was incredibly quick. Before he even had the chance to react, they had reached his body and exploded in front of him.

The bald Venom Snake’s chest was charred. Black hair kept falling off, and the pit of his stomach was hollowed in. There was even the piercing sound of bones breaking, and his body flew out as if he had been hit by the head of a train.

The boa that had been hung around his shoulders was immediately burnt by the flames, turning into white ashes, scattering onto the floor bit by bit.

“Such a mighty spell?” The bald Venom Snake did not even have time to lament for his precious pet. He was frightened silly by Leylin’s Latent Fireball.

“This spell has to be a model that is modified by various large Magi organisation or had its might amplified. Who exactly are you?”

Venom Snake looked at Leylin who slowly walked out from the darkness, suspicions streaked across his face.

“Who I am is not important. What’s important is that you will definitely die here today!” Leylin had even used his Latent Fireball, so naturally he revealed the determination to kill this baldy.

“Aren’t you afraid of the organisation tracing it to you?”

Venom Snake lay on the floor as if he had lost his mobility and was not able to get up.

“I have only signed a contract not to divulge the organisation’s secrets, but not one that doesn’t allow me to pursue a personal vendetta against my enemies!”

Leylin waved his hands forward and countless phantom hands appeared from the void, grabbing a small tree behind the baldy and crushing it to pieces. A yellow bug was retrieved from within the tree.

*Pu!* The yellow bug was smashed into bits in Leylin’s hands.

“Don’t do such useless things anymore!” Leylin stepped in closer.

“You’re leaving me with no choice! Second transfiguration!” The baldy bellowed.

*Crash!* In the blink of an eye, the muscles on his body grew and dense black hair grew out once again. Behind his back, two strips of flesh constantly raised, bursting out of his clothes. They turned into two furry claws.

His teeth became sharp, eyeballs completely red.

From the looks of it, he had turned into a mutated gorilla with four arms.

With the transformation of the bald Venom Snake, a strong energy wave was constantly emitted from his body.

“Activate!” Against this creature which was brandishing its fangs and claws, Leylin only smiled and chanted an incantation.

“Ding!” A crisp noise sounded and several green vines and muddy shafts emerged from the ground, turning into a prison like shape, suppressing the beast within.

“I gave you time not to let you prepare a spell, but for me to lay a trap!”

Leylin spoke leisurely, “You must have had the limbs of a powerful creature transplanted into your body to achieve such a transfiguration, huh? Moreover, it seems to be compatible with your innate defense spell…”

“A pity however that you only transplanted the forelimbs of the Vajra Gorilla. As for creatures like these, they are suppressed by the energy particles of the Earth and Plant elements…”

All this were naturally the simulations done throughout the battle by the A.I. Chip.

After adopting the A.I. Chip’s suggestion Leylin completely controlled the pace of the battle. He had to admit that it all felt pretty good.

“Urghhh…” The gorilla creature in the cage continued to beat on its chest, showing the rage it was in.

Following which, many small plants and rock spears appeared from the ground within the cage, piercing through the creature’s body.

“Aooo…” The gorilla continued to roar in anguish, as his entire fur coat was dyed a crimson red.

*Bang!* A large explosion sounded.

Only two furry arms remained where the black gorilla had been, and the bald Venom Snake had disappeared without a trace.

Looking at this scene, Leylin was not surprised but smiled in a satisfied manner.

“He had even used the substitution spell that can only be used once a day?”

Following which, the sound of a spirit explosion was heard. The trees parted and the old witch carried Venom Snake who had fainted in her hands.

“How is it? Is it still going smoothly?” Leylin inquired.

“Not bad. There was still an amulet on his body limited to a one-time usage that caught me by surprise!” The old witch’s green eyes shone.

“This is a good opportunity since an official Magus’ spirit is extremely difficult to obtain!”

“Also, you’ll get half of the items here and I’ll take the other half!” Leylin had already gone through the bald Venom Snake‘s belongings from his crippled body. In addition, He gave half of Venom Snake’s sack of loot to the old witch.

He was still prepared to maintain the trust between the two of them since they were going to be collaborating for a long time.

The old witch’s gaze revealed some fear while she looked at Leylin. Even though she was confident she could defeat the bald Venom Snake, she wouldn’t be able to do it so easily, and definitely not in this place. Such precise pre-calculations were beyond her.

Leylin was even able to predict the opponent’s escape route, and that was what shocked her the most.

“But by killing Venom Snake, aren’t you afraid the organisation will…” The old witch reminded him.

“Stop trying to scare me!” Leylin laughed, not at all bothered.

“Dark Magi are just a group of indifferent, self-serving people. Why would they seek trouble with me for a dead person? Furthermore, the grudge I had with Venom Snake was apparent to the others, so who could say anything about it?”

“It seems like you have already planned everything!” The old witch looked at Leylin, her expression complicated.

Leylin smiled without a reply.

It was indeed true that he had planned to kill Venom Snake a long time ago.

There were two motives behind it. First was to establish his might! He was a newbie who had just joined the organisation, so he would definitely undergo some suppression by others. In many organisations, the bullying newbies was a form of tradition. Through such means, Leylin could quickly show his prowess as a deterrence and to protect himself.

Of course, he only dared to do such a thing within dark Magi organisations. If it were inside a light Magi organisation, no matter how powerful he was he would be beaten heavily. Who knows if he might even take the rap and be labelled as someone who had tried to sow discord amongst the unity of the light Magi?

As a result, while he was in Four Seasons Garden, Leylin had always kept a low profile and did his work without any complaints. Until now, his leader and teammates still viewed him in a positive light.

As for the second motive — which was Leylin’s main objective — it was only for the benefits!

From today’s operation of plundering the secret plane, Leylin managed to obtain five to six hundred thousand magic crystals. On top of that, he had also gotten Venom Snake’s portion, and the total value came up to around a million, thus doubling his loot.

Wasn’t Leylin’s reason for joining a dark Magi organisation to obtain enough resources? Since that was his reason, why wouldn’t he attack others?

Chapter 168: In Retrospect

Of course, even within dark Magi organisations, there were rules and regulations.

If Leylin kept doing this, it would result in others ganging up on him and eliminating him under the pretext of self-defense.

That was why Leylin needed to first cause some conflict, and then be able to act with a good reason to do so.

Honestly speaking, even if Venom Snake had not challenged him, he was also planning on instigating some of the weaker Magi and then blow the whole thing out of proportion.

Afterwards, he would use revenge as an excuse to righteously kill and then seize their treasures!

But that was it.

Leylin assessed that after this affair, other dark Magi would be slightly dissatisfied with his actions, so he couldn’t let this get too far.

“You’re really…” The old witch was suddenly regretful, “I haven’t seen a youngster that’s as cool headed but also crazy in a very long time…”

“Nope! I’m just someone with the will to live!” Leylin said with a brilliant smile.

“What about you? When will you get your goods?”

The moment this was brought up, the old witch’s face stiffened. This was the only reason why she was working with Leylin and had been dragged along in the end.

“Today’s harvest was pretty good, especially since we got two souls from official Magi. It shouldn’t take long before we can finalize the product!”

“Notify me once it’s finished, I’ll be at Nightless City these few days!” Leylin nodded.

Following which, he approached the bald Venom Snake and undid the concealment spell, revealing the face of a middle aged man that had a venerable countenance.

“It’s him!” The old witch cried out in alarm from behind him.

“You know him?” This aroused Leylin’s interest.

“No, I’ve only seen him a couple of times!” The old witch appeared rather rueful.

“He’s the head of a small light Magi faction, and he’s got a good reputation! Apparently, he’s quite skilled in transformation spells. I didn’t know he was actually a dark Magus!”

“This is quite normal! Dark Magi like to assume a righteous personality, just like you and me!”

Leylin’s silhouette melted into the darkness…

In the following days. Leylin lived a very pleasant life in Nightless City.

It couldn’t be denied that Nightless City was an unusually large Magi City, in which Leylin was able to enjoy all kinds of services tailored for a Magus’ pleasure.

Splash! Boiling tea water flowed out of an exquisite silver teapot into a tea cup engraved with purple flowery designs. A rich fragrance of black tea permeated the air of the whole lounge as it wafted back and forth.

Leylin sat in an armchair to the side with a serene expression. Behind him and under each of his legs were beautiful maids in revealing clothing who were extending their lily white and seemingly boneless small hands to massage him all over his body.

“How is it? The skills of maids are quite good, right? Want me to gift you a couple…”

A red-haired old Magus, who was standing to one side, was saying as he directed another maid to feed him grapes. Around him were a number of maids who waited upon him like he was a god.

“Don’t blame me for saying this Leylin, but your villa is much too simple. It doesn’t even have a guard dog! You’ll be the laughing stock for other Magi if you don’t do anything about this…”

Crew was squinting his eyes. His face revealed an expression of rapture.

“Stop trying to sell me your maids!” Leylin revealed a bitter laugh, “But you must know a lot of merchants in this field, right? You should introduce them to me someday!”

Leylin admitted that it was strange for there not to be a single person in the whole villa. Besides, he felt that he did need some people to help around while he lived in Nightless City, such as servants and the like.

“No problem! I’ll take you to Nightless City’s slave market tomorrow. Once you’re there, all your needs will be satisfied. Besides, there are even slaves from other races!”

Crew revealed an expression that said ‘I’m glad you came to your senses’. When he mentioned different races, a lewd smile was revealed on his old face.

Seeing the expression of this old pervert, Leylin was speechless.

He conveniently grabbed something that looked like a newspaper from the table and was immediately attracted by the eye-catching title.

“Ennea Ivory Ring Tower’s division under attack! Severe losses!”

“Tragedy! Dark Magi attack the Tallinn Highlands. All Magi present have perished!”

“It’s a declaration of war! The dark Magi have initiated the third great Magi war. What are you going to do? Please listen in detail to the analysis by our special guest, Nicholas Kajitel…”

Scenes of the havoc that Leylin and the others had wreaked were splashed all over the headlines.

In addition, all of the reports came had very eye-catching headings, and some even exaggerated to say that this was provocation from the dark Magi and a forewarning that there were plans to begin the third Magi war.

“Look at this! All they’ve been reporting these days is about that incident. The Ennea Ivory Ring Tower really suffered a massive loss, this time, worth at least a hundred million magic crystals…”

Crew looked to be rejoicing at their misfortune, and Leylin briefly wondered if there was some history between Crew and the Ennea Ivory Ring Tower.

“Tsk! A hundred million crystals! What wouldn’t I do to get those many crystals?”

Leylin, too, had an expression of obsessive desire on his face, “But these dark Magi are really quite daring to even provoke the Ennea Ivory Ring Tower!”

Leylin’s facial expressions and movements were flawless as if he really had no knowledge of the incident.

“Sigh… This has happened multiple times in the past, just that nobody can tell whether it’s the Night Crows or the Zombies,” Crew continued.

The Night Crows and Zombies were dark Magi organisations that operated in the shadows of Nightless City. Before Leylin’s arrival, both groups were infamous for having committed several huge crimes with ruthless methods.

The dark Magi organisation that Leylin was a part of was not either of these groups but another —it was called the Thousand Meddling Leaves — though they were just as notorious.

“With Ennea Ivory Ring Tower’s Magi enforcers and help from Nightless City, it should be possible to capture those bold dark Magi, right?”

“I’m afraid that’s not possible!”

Crew shook his head immediately. “The powers backing the dark Magi aren’t to be trifled with. Magi specializing in divination have had their spells achieve no effect, and we suspect that there’s at least a rank 2 Magus backing and giving them orders. We believe there might be even more than one of them…”

“I see.”

Leylin nodded, his expression turning to one of longing.

“A rank 2 Magus! I wonder if I’ll ever reach that level in this lifetime.”

His look made Crew’s expression darken slightly.

Leylin was young and still had hope to achieve that.

But he was different. After consuming a large part of his lifespan, his body’s vitality could no longer withstand the strain from another advancement. Furthermore, he had chosen the simplest route and broken through with the Grime Water, increasing the difficulty of breaking through to the next rank.

“Oh! My apologies!”

Upon noticing Crew’s expression, Leylin gave a bow in apology.

“Don’t worry about it. I just got nostalgic about some events in the past.” The desolate look in his eyes faded away. “Thinking back to my decision then, I’ve missed too many opportunities. If given the chance to relive my life, I think I’d still choose to sign that contract, though.”

Leylin understood his train of thought.

For many acolytes, even if they were aware of the existence of high-grade meditation techniques, they had no choice but to break through with the Grime Water.

After all, only strictly-managed Magi organisations and large Families held possession of high-grade meditation techniques. Typically, level 3 acolytes had no social connections nor any strong background, and it was basically impossible for them to obtain those techniques.

Hence, they would rather use the Grime Water and break through, and hope that after they advanced to an official Magus, they could find a way to make up for the disadvantages of this method.

However, even if there was such a method, it was not something any ordinary Magus could come into contact with. It might not even exist in the entire South Coast, and was more likely to be found only in the central continent.

As a result, most Magi could only service their organisation for their entire life, and then retire, living aimlessly the way Crew was now doing.

“Alright! Enough about this mood-dampening topic. I’ll bring you to the slave market tomorrow to see a friend of mine. She has quite a few quality goods, like the snake girl from the previous time that remains fresh in my memories. You definitely can’t miss this chance!”

At this point, Crew’s mood seemed to have brightened.

Leylin kept Crew company and they chatted for a while, and he had an exceedingly alluring time and sumptuous dinner before leaving Crew’s villa.

*Sssii!*

At this moment, the pocket-sized diary trembled, letting off a slight glow.

“Leylin! I’ve already prepared what you wanted. When can you come over?” The old witch’s voice traveled to his ears from a green secret imprint.

“Give me a moment, I’m on my way!”

Leylin was delighted at the message, as the old witch’s efficiency was better than he had anticipated.

Elm Street #231. It wasn’t Leylin’s first time here.

The shop was located in a very remote area, and most Magi would not be able to find their way here.

After Leylin entered, the old witch closed the door and hung a sign that read “Closed”.

Leylin, unconvinced by this level of security, set up a sound-proofing spell around them.

“Rumours have been flying recently. How is it on your end? Have you been discovered at all?” Leylin asked, somewhat worried.

“Don’t worry. I’ve lived in Nightless City for over a century, and I do have some contacts…” She seemed rather pleased with herself.

“Also, these are the materials that were mentioned in the contract. I processed them using the method in the information you gave me! I did everything perfectly!”

The old witch positioned a dozen crystal soul spheres in the size of a thumb in a row, and placed it on the counter.

Within the soul, sphere were tens of expressionless spirits that seemed on the verge of dissipating. At the moment, many of them had lost their human form, which must have happened after brutal, inhuman torture.

“Has it really all been dealt with? The spirits need to have been immersed and soaked in immense suffering and hopelessness in order to achieve the best effect!”

“Hehe… I even captured a few spirits and experimented on them beforehand. On top of the basic pain that I can inflict, I also tortured their very souls. The effects are marvellous!” The old witch laughed excitedly, though it was a sound that caused others goosebumps.

Chapter 173: The Venom Wyvern

“The theory of ecosystems has long since existed. For example, many Magi find that growing wild grasses alongside Tortoise-Backed Mountain Grass will increase the yields of both by 30%!”

Leylin sat on the sofa and began to articulate upon his theories.

“All I did was expand on this ring of connection. Adding multiple factors, it would proliferate to tens or even hundreds of species, forming a large ecosystem and increasing the outputs of various resources inside the secret plane…”

Truman’s eyes seemed to be giving off light. “What a novel theory! Being able to choose the most compatible ecosystem for the millions of resources in the natural world — I admire your knowledge and background in this area!”

Leylin just gave a faint smile. He was obviously unable to analyse that much data on his own, so the A.I. Chip did most of the work.

The research that he had made public was only on a superficial level.

He was prepared to employ the many key experiments and procedures in his very own secret plane in the future and was unwilling to help Four Seasons Garden increase their output for free. After all, he was no do-gooder.

“However, I am also curious about the Lava Goldfish that you’re rearing, Truman.” Leylin remarked with an anticipatory look in his eyes.

Lava Goldfishes were a unique species in the Magus World. Usually, they thrived in lava, which made them extremely difficult to breed.

As for their fish scales, they were necessary ingredients for many alchemy procedures. The blubber and flesh were a kind of nourishment which could recover a Magus’ energy and enable them to be revitalised after a weary meditation session. Hence, it was highly sought after with an extremely high price.

“Actually, it’s no big deal. These Lava Goldfishes’ habits are very predictable. Once you understand them, then you can make a relevant section inside the secret plane…”

Of course, Truman only briefly stated the methods.

“I hope to use this information of breeding the Lava Goldfishes to exchange for your theory of ecosystem. Moreover, as the value of your information is above mine, I am willing to top up 5000 more magic crystals!”

Truman made a sincere request.

“It’s no problem at all!” Leylin nodded and smiled. The purpose of releasing this information was to exchange it for resources and knowledge with other magicians.

After a year of hard work, he had finally managed to grasp the general methods in operating a secret plane. Apart from that, he also learned about some of the habitats that the most expensive plants needed to thrive in. If he was given a secret plane to govern now, it would definitely not be in deficit, and actually, make profits.

Although Leylin was a dark Magus and participated in plundering operations that the organisation he was in arranged, he never excluded the possibilities of extracting more magic crystals using a light Magus’ methods.

“Speaking of which, Leylin, you’re done with your missions for the month. Do you have any plans? I have a good friend whose experiment requires a high levelled Potions Master, so if you were to go…”

Truman sent Leylin an invitation.

Apart from their duties inside Four Seasons Garden, many magicians often had a part time job through their connections in the organisation, earning additional magic crystals and resources.

Of course, some did it purely as their interest or hobby, or merely just to help a friend out.

“My apologies! The mission for this month was extremely taxing. I wish to take this well-deserved break to recuperate in Nightless City!”

Leylin rejected Truman’s invitation tactfully.

Right now, he no longer prioritised these tiny organization’s resources or connections. Moreover, he was in the crucial period of boosting his prowess, so he did not have that much time to bother about other trivial matters.

“That’s really regretful…” Truman’s face reflected the disappointment that he felt. Only after exchanging several more words with Leylin and their specialised information did they separate.

“Lord Leylin!”

After parting with Truman, Leylin went to the landing pad of the Four Seasons Garden. The acolytes here all recognised Leylin and they bowed to greet him.

“How is Hawke’s current condition?”

Leylin walked to a cage with a giant creature within it. A pair of large red eyes stared back at him. The beast opened its jaws and revealed rows of razor sharp fangs that resembled swords, with a crimson tongue that had reverse scales.

“Lord, your mount’s appetite is great. Yesterday, it had even eaten a whole red bread pig. Its temper was rather nasty, though this could be due to it being caged for a long period of time…”

The acolyte who was in charge of these mounts was obviously skilled in his work. He was also extremely diligent as he replied Leylin.

*Creak!*

A scarlet rune appeared on Leylin’s finger, forming the shape of a key and entering the keyhole of the metal cage.

“Roar!”

With an impressive roar, a green wyvern charged out of the cage.

This creature had sharp talons and claws, and its whole body was covered in murky green scales. On its back was also a pair of large green wings. The membrane of the wings shone with a green lustre under the light.

[Venom Wyvern. Strength: 13.5, Agility: 19.8, Vitality: 11.2, Spiritual Force: 9.8. Special abilities: 1. Acidic breath: A corrosive poison will be spat on the mouth, with an area of effect of 20 metres. Average power: 16 degrees. 2. Toxic Rip: The Venom Wyvern’s claws and fangs have toxic properties, with a huge numbing effect on the spiritual force.]

The Venom Wyvern’s stats were displayed by Leylin’s A.I. Chip.

“Rawrrr!”

The gigantic Venom Wyvern continued to roar. At the same time, there was a fawning look in its eyes that was incredibly humane as it lowered its head and rubbed gently against Leylin‘s body.

“Alright! Alright! I will give you an upsize for your meals when I get back!”

Leylin could not help but laugh as he rubbed this Venom Wyvern which had the mentality of a puppy missing its owner.

“Hawke, bring me to Nightless City now!”

Leylin got onto the back of the Venom Wyvern in one leap.

“Rawrr!” The Venom Wyvern snarled and the wings on its back jolted, unfolding segment by segment until they were fully extended, and were at least three times larger than its body.

With a fierce hurricane, the Venom Wyvern spread its wings and swooped into the air.

“Hah… They’re finally gone. Just having that Venom Wyvern standing here is enough to make me feel uncomfortable,” a female acolyte who was feeding a Dragon Crown Nighthawk, gave a long sigh of relief.

“With that guy around, all these Nighthawks lost their appetites!” The female acolyte patted the Nighthawk in front of her that was eating cheerfully, seemingly just as relieved as her.

“That Venom Wyvern’s power is probably close to that of an official Magus. How strong must Magus Leylin be to be able to tame it?”

The male acolyte following behind Leylin had a very contrasting opinion from the female acolyte and his eyes reflected his envy and admiration for Leylin.

The Venom Wyvern’s flying speed was twice as fast as the Dragon Crown Nighthawk had been. It was thus much more convenient for Leylin to travel between Nightless City and the Four Seasons Garden.

Upon reaching the Nightless City’s landing pad, Leylin issued some orders for the acolytes to take care of his Venom Wyvern and gave Hawke another red bread pig before returning to his villa.

“Master!” Damien and a few Grand Knights bowed respectfully.

Leylin looked around, finding that the villa was still in the same state as it was before he had left. The human slaves that he had bought later on were carefully cleaning the staircase railing and all the pieces of artwork.

Damien was wearing a butler’s uniform, looking impeccable as he stood behind Leylin.

“Master! After you left, your neighbour, Magus Crew came over once. Also, I’ve already paid the continuity fees to the communal centre. Here is the inventory.”

After which, Damien gave a report of what he had done in this period of time.

“Okay.” Leylin paid no mind to his words and nodded along. This Damien seemed to have undergone specialised training while he was a slave and was very proficient in these matters. Leylin had branded him and there was no way that he could revolt, so Leylin could place his trust in him.

“That’s enough for now. Make me some dinner and milk tea!” Leylin ordered indifferently.

“Hawke can be used for transportation and can sweep away most acolytes, but he won’t be useful in battles with official Magi.”

After a moment, Leylin, who was lying comfortably on a couch with pretty maids servicing him with their soft little hands, reflected with a hint of regret.

In the south coast, some Magi had top grade magic creatures as pets. These pets matured quickly, to the point that after their master advanced, it was possible for their own strength to reach the level of an official Magus.

In battle, how much help would an assistant with the same rank render?

Unfortunately, no matter how much Leylin searched and gathered them, he couldn’t find these high-quality pets, and could only purchase a Venom Wyvern to use as a mount.

Magi and their pets had to agree upon a strict spirit contract, and there were some that even required them to share their life force!

Leylin was obviously not going to waste his chance on this Venom Wyvern and used the simplest and cruelest spirit brand to forcibly control it. It was going to be a temporary mount, and he was planning to substitute it with a better option at the next best opportunity.

“But it’s a shame!”

Leylin turned his hand and a crystal that was like an amber revealed itself in his palm. In the middle of the crystal was a drop of green liquid that had a unique aura emanating from it constantly.

“The Venom Wyvern’s blood essence has a trace of the bloodline of the ancient creature — the Thousand Venom Dragon!” The A.I. Chip prompted.

That was why he had purchased the Venom Wyvern.

While he was in Nightless City, Leylin had constantly been collecting creatures that might have ancient bloodlines in them and tried to purify their blood with the A.I. Chip.

However, a majority of his experiments were a failure, and the blood essence in his palm was the best result he had.

“A.I. Chip, have you found out the reason?”

Chapter 174: The Ancient Spirit Slaying Sect

In order to obtain the bloodlines of more ancient creatures, Leylin had conducted numerous experiments. However, none of them were successful.

The best result was what was in his hand — the quintessence of some ancient creature.

To most Magi, this was probably a precious treasure, but for Leylin, this was far from enough.

[Beep! After 124 practical experiments and a comparison with 9718 simulated experiments, the conjecture is that the Host’s concentration of bloodline essence is not enough. Unable to unearth deeper purification. Recommended to look for the blood essence of creatures with the power of rank 3 Magus and above as stimulus to purify bloodline.]

The A.I. Chip gave a prompt answer.

“As expected…” Leylin had already surmised this conjecture, and now it seemed to tally with the A.I. Chip’s calculations.

After a long period of time, the ancient bloodline in the mystical creatures in the south coast had been thinned out so much that if not for the amazing ability of the A.I. Chip, Leylin would not even be able to refine this blood that was full of impurities.

To obtain a pure ancient bloodline, it was necessary to gain blood samples from even stronger monsters.

The A.I. Chip had gathered that at the bare minimum, blood samples from a rank 3 creature had to be obtained.

That meant that as long as Leylin was able to obtain the blood of a monster that was rank 3 or higher, the A.I. Chip would be able to purify and extract a perfect sample of the ancient bloodline.

“But… A creature that is rank 3 or above?” Leylin smiled wryly at his thoughts, “I’d probably die just from a snort from them! I’d obtained the blood from the Black Horrall Snake that originally had the strength of a rank 3 Magus. Thankfully, its might had weakened to the equivalent of an acolyte, and that alone was a giant stroke of luck. It’s as if a tasty meat pie had fallen from the heavens! ”

The Giant Kemoyin Serpent’s bloodline that Leylin was in possession of was purified from the Black Horrall Snake previously found in the Dylan Gardens.

That Black Horrall Snake was a powerful creature that rivalled the strength of a rank 3 Magus at its adult stage!

The Black Horrall Snake back then had definitely matured into an adult. However, due to the limiters inside the secret plane, coupled with prolonged hunger — and perhaps also with the other methods from the great Magus Serholm — it caused the Black Horrall Snake’s state to deteriorate in its slumber, eventually turning pitiful enough to be attacked by a group of level 3 acolytes.

This was obviously a present that the great Magus Serholm left for his inheritor. It was an intentional setup and not a coincidence.

The great Magus Serholm was a rank 4 Warlock, and as compared to Leylin who was a rank 1 Warlock, he was the sun while Leylin was but a firefly.

“These things are dependent on luck. At most, I’ll take more notice in the future. It’s not the time to think about this now!”

Leylin pulled up his stats.

[Leylin Farlier. Rank 1 Warlock. Bloodline: Giant Kemoyin Serpent. Strength: 7.1, Agility: 6.7, Vitality: 8.5, Spiritual Force: 58.9, Magic Power: 58 (Magic Power is in synchronisation with Spiritual Force). Elemental essence conversion: 70%. Status: Healthy]

In this year, he had been continuing his trade with the old witch. Using the processed spirits she had gathered, he had obtained a large quantity of the ancient potion- Tears of Mary!

With the help of the ancient potion, Leylin’s spiritual force shot up rapidly.

Leylin had spent quite some time in the Four Seasons Garden and through the exchange of contribution points, he had gathered the formulas of potions that could increase an official Magus’ spiritual force.

However, he found that those potions’ effects were nothing compared to the ancient potion.

With its help, Leylin increased his spiritual force at a shocking rate, as if he had no limits.

Presently, he had no choice but to use concealment methods to hide his tremendous spiritual force. He stayed indoors whenever possible, avoiding areas where rank 2 Magi might appear. He didn’t want there to be any chances of others finding out.

Unfortunately, even with the A.I. Chip constantly upgrading the concealment method, it was not possible to hide his spiritual force entirely.

The moment he had a break, Leylin would rush back to Nightless City to hide and avoided all social interaction.

After reaching a certain level in terms of his spiritual force, Leylin had once again used the crystallised Darkness energy particles to push his elemental essence conversion to 70%!

However, after his elemental essence conversion reached 70%, Leylin received a notification from the A.I. Chip that his body and spirit had developed a resistance towards such crystals. Unless he found more precious resources to raise his elemental essence conversion in the future, he could only rely on meditation and time and progress at a slower rate.

“Potions made by ancient Magi are really different!”

A look of satisfaction crossed Leylin’s face. “The agreement with the old witch cannot be broken. Moreover, finding new ways to conceal my spiritual force is becoming a matter of urgency.”

In all honesty, he should be collecting the spirits himself. Directly branding the spirits of slaves who helped out would ensure that this matter was kept secret.

However, the preparatory stages for the brewing of the Tears of Mary required someone with the might of a rank 1 Magus. Moreover, it had to be a Magus who was specialised in spirits.

As for Leylin, his current attainment in the knowledge of spiritual force and spirits only allowed him to brand level 3 acolytes. It was basically impossible to brand an official Magus.

Anyway, the old witch had made her vow in front of the Trial’s Eye, so she could be trusted for the time being.

“However, the amount of spirits provided by the old witch seems to have decreased. In the past few trades, she also seemed distant and unfocused and didn’t even participate in the activities organised by the dark Magi organisation. It seems there’s something of extreme importance going on. I’d better check on her tomorrow and hope that there won’t be any trouble…”

This ally of his was recently acting strangely, inciting worry in Leylin’s heart.

“Master! Your dinner’s ready!”

Damien’s voice sounded while he was deep in thought, enjoying the service from his maids.

“Alright! I’ll be right there!”

Leylin opened his eyes, the blackness in his pupils gaining another depth in them…

After a day of entertainment and rest, Leylin was feeling refreshed. Wrapped in a black cloak, Leylin covered even his face and paid a visit to the old witch’s shop.

“What happened to you?”

The moment Leylin saw the state the old witch was in, he wrinkled his eyebrows.

The first time he’d seen her, the old witch looked like a dead person. The scent of death and decay was even more apparent now, and she looked like she was a corpse which had just crawled out of an old tomb. The undulations from her spiritual force were also extremely feeble.

This condition immediately alarmed Leylin.

For Magi, injuries on one’s physical body were insignificant, but if one’s spiritual force showed signs of weakening, that immediately meant that one’s might was decreasing.

The old witch was still Leylin’s ally, and he didn’t want his supplier to suddenly disappear.

“Nothing much! Just a recent experiment that’s approaching its crucial stage!” Her body was already as weak as it could get, and just speaking resulted in her panting. However, the light in her eyes was even more radiant, as if on the verge of burning up.

Leylin had seen such a fervent heat in a person’s gaze before– in his previous life, in the eyes of lunatics and crazy people.

“You’d better not keep anything from me. Remember, we’re allies. Haven’t we been working well together in this past year?”

Leylin obviously didn’t believe her vague explanation.

“When it’s time, I’ll definitely tell you everything.”

The old witch gave a mysterious grin. “Also, I’ve found the spiritual force concealment method that you requested the previous time.”

“What? What?!” This was so unexpected that a smile surfaced on Leylin’s face.

He had always been searching for this content on the sly and attended a few of the dark Magi’s bazaars and meets to exchange resources, but to no avail.

He wasn’t expecting much when he employed her help, and it was a pleasant surprise that she had actually gotten what he wanted.

“This is information regarding the compression of spiritual force. Take a look!” She passed a green leaf to him.

Leylin reached out and took it, and then placed it on his forehead.

A cool feeling was emitted from the leaf and permeated Leylin’s skull, going straight into the depths of his brain.

[Spiritual force data interface has been detected. To accept the connection or not?] The A.I. Chip’s voice intoned.

“Accept!” With Leylin’s command, a massive stream of information entered Leylin’s sea of consciousness. It was constantly broken down, recorded and analysed by the A.I. Chip.

“Overall, the compression of spiritual force is to stack the spiritual force together continuously, arising in a different frequency of energy waves. From there, one can achieve the purpose of concealing their spiritual force…”

After browsing through for a while, Leylin smiled in satisfaction.

“This piece of information is very useful to me, but it seems to be incomplete. Where is the rest of it? Take it out! What do you want? Magic crystals? Potions? Resources? Just give the word!”

Leylin appeared to be extremely rich and overbearing.

“Hehehe… Just with the first half of this information, your spiritual force will be untraceable to all rank 1 Magi. Once you have the second half, even a rank 2 Magus won’t be able to discover your spiritual force energy waves. Although you can definitely afford it, I wish to make a trade with you using another method…” The old witch said with a cryptic laugh and hooted.

“What method?” Leylin’s brows furrowed, guessing that it was going to be extremely troublesome.

“I will give you the first half of the information now as a gift of thanks for being my ally!” The old witch appeared to be extremely generous, “As for the second half, I need you to do something for me!”

It was obvious that the old witch was using the second half of the information as bait to have Leylin help her with a certain matter.

“I need to know the specifics.”

Leylin did not refuse, but he did not agree either.

“Hehe… Don’t worry, I won’t ask you to hold back a rank 2 Magus or anything like that. I just want you to accompany me to explore some ruins.”

The old witch revealed her true motive.

“Exploring ruins? What ruins?” Leylin probed curiously.

“The remnants of the Ancient Spirit Slaying Sect!”

Chapter 176: A Banshee

In the south coast, the storage type secret plane Leylin had previously raided and the laboratory type secret plane that the old witch found were all classified as small scale secret planes.

The area of these kind of secret planes usually didn’t exceed a 100 mu and were only used to perform experiments and to store supplies. If one does not take into account of the items stored inside and only look at the area of the secret plane, its worth would be at the bottom.

Above that were the resource type secret planes, the area of that type of secret planes is usually larger than 100,000 mu. The area is large and the topology is varied and suitable to grow resources necessary to Magi.

The highest rank of secret planes are those that have spells that can adjust the living environments of both plants and animals, and can be controlled by a single Magus!

These are only under normal circumstances, there are also places like Dylan Gardens which Leylin previously found. Even though the area was small but it was personally arranged by the fourth level warlock great Magus Serholm, thus its value couldn’t be compared to the normal planes of its kind.

“It’s a shame! If it was a resource type of secret plane, we could occupy it in secret then alter it, hehe… then we would be filthy rich!”

Brass Ring was stroking his chin as if he was caught in some fantasy.

“Keep dreaming!” The old witch sneered icily, interrupting Brass Ring’s fancy dreams.

“The bigger the area of the secret plane, the higher the cost of construction. As for the resource type secret planes which was larger than 100k mu, even for some ancient Magi organisations, there weren’t many that could afford to construct it…”

“All the present resource type secret planes that belongs to the large organisations are all remnants from the ancient Magi which have been altered slightly, that’s all! If there really was a resource type secret plane being discovered here, the likes of us wouldn’t be able to stomach it. Even if we added our whole organisation plus the Boss that is backing it, it still wouldn’t be enough!”

“Let’s go! Even if it’s just a laboratory type of secret plane, there must still be a lot of valuable stuff inside. We’re also handing over a lot contributions to the higher ups. It’s enough for you to trade for a lot of resources!” Leylin said.

For these kind of small scale secret planes, every large Magi organisation has set up missions.

No matter if it’s Four Seasons Garden or the dark Magi organisation which the old witch belonged to, they all have the power to take it over. After which there naturally will be a lot of rewards for the finders.

If this was a resource type of secret plane then Leylin would put in some thought in order to pocket it himself.

Since it’s only a laboratory type of secret plane, he didn’t put much thought into pocketing it. After all even if he was to occupy it because it’s so small he couldn’t actually alter it that much. At most he would only have a small scale secret base to hide.

“The entrance to the secret plane is on the west side of this town, inside a two story wooden building!”

The old witch seemed quite familiar with the surroundings as she brought the three of them to a two-storey building made out of wood.

Compare to the small town, this place was even more remote. Weed were growing all around the villa and there were even two mole like animals quickly scurrying by.

“Originally this place was a lively street, but since 13 years ago the residents in this place kept dying one by one. Sometimes the town residents could hear sound of a woman wailing outside their homes, that’s why the rumors spread about it being a cursed or a haunted house. The surroundings ended up being overgrown!”

The old witch opened up the rusted gates while feeling rather satisfied with herself.

“I found this place during one of my explorations, after a couple of months of investigation, I’m sure that the unusual situations around here is cause by the deterioration of the defensive spells around the entrance to the secret plane, unwillingly leaking radiation …”

“According to calculations, after 13 years the defensive spells should have totally deteriorated. Leaving the entrance to the secret plane exposed…”

“Thusly I pretend to be an ordinary person and bought this building, plus I added a facade on the outside so other Magi couldn’t discover this place.”

Leylin was listening to the old witch while he was exploring the inside of this building.

The bottom floor wasn’t that big, it only contained 2 to 3 buildings. The hall was filled with a thick layer of dust and broken furniture. In the corner was a spiral staircase filled with holes. It was the only thing connecting these two floors.

Beneath this obvious state of decline, Leylin could feel a strong aura of negative energy.

This aura was extremely malevolent, and it carried with it a smell that Leylin was familiar with.

“Spirits! And they’re spirits that have been driven crazy from being vengeful!” The corner of Leylin’s mouth curved, “This old witch really found a nice place!”

“Follow me! Be careful not to touch the black mold on the walls, those are trigger points!”

The old witch was in front leading the while, bringing the three behind as they climbed the squeaky stairs to the second floor. She seemed extremely familiar with this place.

The area on the second floor was smaller than the large hall on the first, where the corridors only allowed 2 people to walk side by side.

By chance Leylin was walking beside Jaye, because the other person was entirely wrapped in a cloak and didn’t speak much. Leylin couldn’t even distinguish the other person’s gender.

“This oil painting is the entrance to the Ancient Spirit Slaying Sect’s secret plane!”

By the end of the corridor, the old witch was pointing towards an oil painting that was hanging on the wall as she turned around and spoke to Leylin and the rest.

Leylin’s focus involuntarily shifted to the oil painting.

This oil painting depicted a richly dressed noble woman, using a delicate fan to cover half her face.

Due to time and age, there were a lot of dust on the walls. Even around the oil painting were a ring of thick dust.

The whole oil painting used green as a base color, and it didn’t seem to fit the picture.

Besides, maybe it’s because of the angle and line, but if he stared at it long enough, Leylin felt that the fan the noble woman was holding in the oil painting moved slightly.

Suddenly, the young woman inside the oil painting blinked her eyes!

“Is this oil painting alive?”

Leylin cried out involuntarily.

“You’re finally awake?” The old witch advanced as she cackled.

“Foreign intruders, speak the password!” The woman inside the oil painting blinked again as information directly entered each Magus that was present.

“Password? Your masters have all perished, and right now we’ve come to take everything inside the secret plane!”

The old witch was staring at the woman in the oil painting, “If you choose to comply, there might be a place for you inside my storage room!”

“Password incorrect!” The woman inside the painting said. Leylin was keenly aware of that the fan which the noble woman held inside her hand closed slightly.

“It’s only a being conjured by spells, yet it dares to disobey me!”

The old witch’s eyes emitted green lights, and a ring of green fireballs emerged flying directly toward the oil painting.

*Bam!*

As the green fireballs burned the oil paint, the noble woman’s fan closed entirely exposing the face behind it.

Leylin didn’t expect that under the beautiful half of the noble woman’s face was a nose and mouth composed entirely out of bones.

This appearance was as if the flesh and blood below the noble woman’s eyes had instantly disappeared.

A feeling of discrepancy and wrongness suddenly assaulted Leylin’s thoracic cavity.

*Scree!*

Following that, the shrill sound of a woman flooded the whole corridor.

The green fireballs started to crumble, turning into small spark of green fire. Following which it directly extinguished in the fluctuation of the air.

[Beep! Host is being attacked by sound waves. Resemblance to banshee wail 67%. Abnormality in muscle coordination, spiritual force circulation rate lowered by 89%…]

The A.I. Chip projected the status with red color in front of Leylin’s eyes.

“Banshee wail? Could it be that there is a genuine banshee trapped inside that oil painting?” Leylin was startled, immediately a layer of crimson membrane appeared outside his body and isolated the sound.

Even though his ears still hurt, but his body has regained his mobility.

At the same time, a couple of blood red tentacles like intestines protruded from the oil painting and they headed for Brass Ring.

“Damnable thing!” Brass Ring cursed as his body protruded countless bone spikes. The red intestines was directly pierced and was severed.

“Bone Spike Arts?!” Leylin was startled, “He actually solidified this kind of innate spells onto himself, is he a masochist?”

Bone Spike Arts was a rank 1 spell, and was quite formidable. But its activation process was quite a hassle. It needed to be grown from a Magus’ own skeleton then pierce the Magus’ own muscle before attacking his opponent.

This kind of spell was literally hurting oneself before hurting your opponent, only maniacs and masochist would pick this.

“I’ll tear you damnable thing to pieces!”. One could see that Brass Ring was quite enraged since he was forced to use his innate spell.

Presently, his whole body was covered with bone spikes. It gave one the impression that he was like a white sea urchin.

At the same time, a green light spread from below his neck to his whole body, initiating blood staunching and similar effects.

“Stop!” The old witch’s body started to emit countless translucent spirit bodies, and every one of them circulated around Brass Ring’s body, making his speed drop.

“There is a spell effect on this oil painting, if you tear it apart the whole entrance to the secret plan will also collapse!”

The old witch’s expression turned serious, “Let me do it!”

When the previous Banshee wail had struck, the bodies of both the old witch and Jaye emitted a black colored membrane. It seemed like neither of them suffered any injuries.

“Your Banshee wail was pretty good, it is a shame that the matching spell formation has been half collapsed due to the passage of time. What’s left isn’t something than can affect us official Magi…”

The old witch looked upon the Banshee within the oil painting with pity, as she stroked the surface of the painting with her hand.

Following which tiny dark purple dots originated from the old witch’s palm and spread continuously. Like someone was adding a coat of paint.

“Come forth! My baby!”

The old witch said softly, her voice sounding tender and flirtatious.

As soon as these words were uttered, the Banshee within the painting turned fearful, as if she had encountered her natural enemy.

Chapter 181: Living Organism No. 1

Leylin was watching the process of the Loathsome Evil coming together.

The spirit within the array was finally incinerated as the purple flame gradually extinguished.

Swish! The entire light ray from the spell formation completely shattered.

Leylin walked into the formation.

The smell of something burning wafted in the air, along with a repulsive stench that could make one feel nauseous.

“This odour is just like when something from the sewers is burnt!” Leylin frowned and walked to the center.

The human corpses had long since been burnt to ashes.

On the ground, in the middle of the charred and indented formation, a glistening object caught Leylin’s eye.

Lying in the pit were fragments of green crystals, sparkling and splendid like little diamonds.

Leylin covered his hand with a layer of scales and grabbed ahold of the little diamonds.

“Quite light, but very solid!” Leylin kept applying pressure using his palm to the point that his joints popped, but even with his strength of 7.1, he was still unable to do anything to the little diamonds.

“…” All of a sudden, a low chant of salutations entered Leylin’s ear, seeming to have been produced from within the green diamonds.

Filled with curiosity, Leylin brought the diamonds closer to his ear.

“Thank you, young man!”

In an instant, a dazzling white light seemed to fill the entire flower garden. In the white light, Leylin looked at tens of thousands of phantom human figures.

The countenances of these phantoms seemed familiar; they were the spirit bodies of earlier, but they had assumed their original form of a human.

The phantoms were both male and female. Some of them were dressed like Magi and acolytes. However, at this moment, they expressed gentle smiles as they slowly faded in the white light.

“En!” Leylin looked at the surroundings. As if it was due to the death of the Loathsome Evil, the green coloured plague quickly retreated, once again revealing the flower garden.

As for the spirit bodies from earlier, they had all disappeared without a trace, as if he were just dreaming.

However, Leylin knew that he wasn’t hallucinating.

At this moment, the A.I. Chip’s voice rang out.

[Scan complete! Item identified as spirit crystals! This is the essence remaining after the ignition of a huge amount of spirits!] In ancient compendiums, these were one of the many favourite currencies that many experts in different planes liked to use.

“Spirit crystals!” Leylin understood.

He had heard about this item before, but only high-level Magi could effectively use them.

It was impossible for a mere rank 1 Magus to break the surface of a spirit crystal to extract a spirit’s power from within.

“No matter what, it will definitely be useful in the future!” Leylin picked up the green coloured spirit crystals littered on the floor, carefully placing them inside a small pouch. He even used a gold thread to seal the pouch, before placing it back in his robes.

The green spirit plague had completely vanished. Many fine cracks that looked like lizards littered the black rock walls at the edge of the garden.

Leylin walked in front of the cracks, and gently knocked on the fractured wall!

*Crash!*

Numerous stones fell, and large clouds of lime were thrown into the air. There was a deep hole in the wall, which was flickering with pitch black light rays.

A black glint of light flashed through his eyes.

He quickly plucked off a strand of his hair, and his mouth began to move as he chanted mysterious incantations.

The long black hair fell to the ground and constantly expanded, eventually turning into something that resembled a black snake.

This small snake had densely packed scales and a pair of red little eyes that looked like jewels. It was pocket sized, and did not look malevolent; on the contrary, it was rather adorable.

The little snake first coiled around Leylin, hissing its tongue. It licked Leylin’s shoes and then slithered into the pitch black crevice.

Leylin shut both his eyes, maintaining a connection with the little snake through a thread of spiritual force. Images and sounds were projected before Leylin’s eyes.

The lighting in the surroundings was very dim, but it wasn’t a problem for the little black snake.

Through the eyes of the black snake, Leylin could see that the interior of the crevice looked like an ore mine with huge amounts of roots creeping in the surroundings.

The roots intertwined across the walls as if they were covering the surroundings of the cave like a fishnet.

The little snake continued to traverse into the cave. After slithering for about a kilometer, the little snake reached a yellow tree root that was like a wall that blocked its path.

“This is… a Misleading Mist Tree Root, an ancient defensive system to deter intruders!”

Leylin’s heart was filled with glee. With the appearance of such a mechanism, it showed that he was nearing the experiment lab.

“Intruder! Answer one question of mine, or else you’ll be ripped into pieces!” from the large trunk of the tree, the face of an old man emerged. The old man stared into the little snake’s eyes as if it could see Leylin, who was controlling it.

“Ask!” Leylin gave off a wave of spiritual force through the little black snake. “Please state your question!” Leylin gave off his spiritual energy force directly through the black little snake.

“What has the face of a diamond, eyes like pearls, and in the winter, the maker of this object gives it a chance to reincarnate?”

“Hmm…” Leylin lowered his head, looking to be deep in thought. Though, in actuality, he was commanding, “A.I. Chip! Search database!”

[Beep! According to the clues provided to the Host, items that fit the description are: 1. Gemstone Starfish. Similarity: 97%. 2. Ocean Bed Sunflower: 78%. 3…]

The A.I. chip instantly gave the result.

“It’s the Gemstone Starfish!” The snake said in front of the Misleading Mist Tree Root.

“Correct!” The Misleading Mist Tree Root let out an ear piercing holler. Like pulling out a radish from the ground, the tree’s roots were uplifted, revealing the pathway behind it.

“As a reward, you now have the authority to go through!” The countenance of the old man on the Misleading Mist Tree Root revealed a smile.

“A reward, huh? I don’t think so!”

The small snake shook its head and climbed through the passage.

*Pa!* In an instant, a giant tree root, like a huge palm, blocked the small snake’s path ahead.

“I have permitted the Magus behind you to go, but not a magical creature like you!” Anger welled up on the old face of the root.

“Young Magus, are you belittling me?”

“It is a part of me, so I believe it has the right to enter!” The little snake raised its head, making eye contact with the giant face.

“No! You must personally come over!” The Misleading Mist Tree Root was stubborn in this aspect.

“If that’s the case…” The little black snake lowered its head as if pondering over something.

Suddenly, the little snake coiled up and immediately darted through the passage.

*Pa!*

Suddenly, there were numerous bolts of black lightning that flashed into the originally peaceful pathway .Those flashes looked alive as they struck towards the little snake.

In the sea of sparks, the little snake was burnt to a crisp.

“It’s a trap indeed! Grade 5 and higher Black Prison Thunder, and there’s so much of it. The tree root really invested a lot in this attack…”

Outside the entrance to the garden, Leylin looked towards the mud tunnel and smiled mockingly.

This Misleading Mist Tree Root was just a trap in the first place! Even if an intruder got the answer correct, he or she would still be lured into a trap.

It was a pity that after so many years, there was something wrong with the Misleading Mist Tree Root’s intelligence. Leylin felt that something was wrong because it seemed to be much too anxious.

No matter how good a trap was, once it was found out, it was just another joke.

At this moment, a strong tremor came from the tunnel that Leylin stood in front of. There was even an ancient voice, “I’ll kill you! I’m going to kill you, intruder!”

The walls of the ore mine seemed to be propped up by the roots of the tree. As they struggled to come out, it caused a huge chain reaction.

“This creature’s vitality and strength are most likely above that of the Loathsome Evil. Moreover, as it is a plant, its life force is extremely tenacious, and it has resistances against spiritual force attacks. It’ll be much more difficult to deal with than the Loathsome Evil, so if I was to fight it on its own territory inside the ore mine, as long as it would be willing, it could bury me alive at any time!”

Leylin pondered before raising his head, grinning mischievously.

“It’s a pity, however, that such a plant organism like that has a strong weakness to something I have recently developed in the lab! I’ll use it now!”

Leylin took out a nitrogen crystallised test-tube from the sack that he carried. There were no potions inside the test-tube. There was only a black organism on the bottom with a pair or translucent wings as if it was an insect.

After looking at this item, Leylin’s expression became serious.

“I don’t know if letting this thing out will be good or bad, but I have to give it a try….”

Leylin muttered to himself.

This was an item that he had unintentionally created.

Inside the test-tube was a type of termite found only in the Magus World. Leylin had discovered it while getting rid of the pests inside the Four Seasons Garden.

As the sequence of genes was different from other termites, they were extremely strong, and hence, were taken back by Leylin, who had later discovered a secret.

These termites had an extremely strange gene that will exponentially increase their life force and reproductive capabilities.

That speed was already beyond what was natural. Judging from Leylin’s knowledge, this should have been made up of poisons and cells from another world.

After many instances of failing, Leylin could only increase the abilities of these termites with the help of the microscopic capabilities of the A.I. Chip, turning them into a weapon to deal with plant organisms!

It seemed like now was the right time to use it.

“Come! Let me see what happens when the strange items of the Magus world are coupled with modern scientific skills!”

[Host is about to release Living Organism No. 1! According to the settings, please input the parameters for self-destruction!]

At this time, the A.I. chip replied again.

“5 minutes!”

Leylin put a thread of his spiritual force into the test-tube, after which, he put several drops of another red potion into it as if making his final preparations.

After that, he looked at the shaking tunnel. The Misleading Mist Tree Root was still writhing around, trying to reach him.

“Enjoy your death now!”

Leylin sneered, opened the test tube, and directed the termite into the hole.

Chapter 182: Experiment Lab #1

“A.I. Chip! Record the data, and create a folder on the experiment’s results!”

While Leylin released the termite, he pressed on his temple with one of his hands, making a bright blue light shoot out from his eyes, and shine directly into the hole.

Under Leylin’s observation, the termite directly climbed on top of a tree root after being freed.

The termite was like a speck of dust compared to the enormous Misleading Mist Tree Root, so it didn’t arouse the attention of the massive tree.

[Living Organism No. 1 showing violent growth, and starting to propagate!]

In the graphic shown by the A.I. Chip, the termite, which was represented by a red dot, stayed on the yellow brown roots for a while, before its life force begin to increase tremendously, turning into a bright crimson red dot. Furthermore, many small dots began to appear in the graphic, scattering throughout the roots.

It seemed to have a domino effect. When the red light intensified, it grew from covering a root to instantly covering the entire wall, and drew close to the Misleading Mist Tree Root.

“What is this…Argh…”

Following which, the Misleading Mist Tree Root’s screams could be heard throughout the garden.

Leylin could still hear the dense, hair raising, terrifying screams while he was at the entrance of the hole.

As for the termites, they had now filled the entire body of the Misleading Mist Tree Root.

What seemed like billions of termites began to open their incisors, and mercilessly chomped down on the roots. Within only a couple of minutes, the Misleading Mist Tree Root was riddled with holes.

The Misleading Mist Tree Root’s screams become weaker, until it finally came to a stop.

……

*Buzz Buzz…*

The sound of flapping wings could be heard. A large cloud of termites was seen flying out from the hole. They were like locusts, devouring the remaining plants in the garden.

After devouring all of the plants, the flying termites began to buzz in fury.

[Alert! Alert! Intense energy waves emitting from the organisms’ spiritual force. Previously inputted spiritual force has failed, termites entering a frenzied state!]

As the A.I. Chip called out, all of the flying termites began to mysteriously stop as they turned to Leylin, looking at him with bloodshot eyes.

“As expected, impromptu experiments are always filled with surprises. However, it’s a pity that time is up!” Leylin was smiling.

When the A.I. Chip’s countdown timer of 5 minutes reached 0, all of the termites, which were still flaunting their might, fell to the ground, losing all signs of life.

In the blink of an eye, there was a thick layer of termite corpses on the ground.

This was the security system that Leylin had inputted. It seemed to have an excellent effect.

“These things are filled with unknown characteristics! It seems that I’ll still need a lot of experiments on it before I can use it practically…..”

After which, Leylin picked up several of the termites’ corpses to keep as specimens, before walking into the mud tunnel, which had mostly collapsed.

Very soon, he came to where the Misleading Mist Tree Root originally stood. It was a pity, however, that it was now only filled with mud and the remnants of a husk. All traces of the huge tree root’s countenance had also disappeared.

“A lot of effort must have been put into this trap!”

Leylin looked at the black tunnel that the Misleading Mist Tree Root had used as bait. The inside of the tunnel was littered with many charred termite corpses.

From the looks of it, they didn’t die from the self-destruction coded into their genes, but from the trap laid inside the tunnel.

As for where the Misleading Mist Tree Root once stood, there was another bronze coloured path.

The pathway seemed to be formed using ceramic. It looked extremely crude, but had a unique, good feeling about it.

As for the path, there was even a line of ancient Byron characters, “Tunnel to Experiment Lab #1! Top secret! Only authorized personnel allowed!”

The blood red words made Leylin shudder.

“This material……”

Leylin touched the bronze coloured ceramic wall. He felt that the material used to make this wall was extremely sturdy. Also, it gave him a similar feeling to the Blood Sobbing Alloy inside the Dylan Gardens. They were both used to isolate spiritual force energy waves.

“If this is really what I think it is, the item that is locked in here must be remarkable!”

The insecurities in Leylin’s heart reached the max.

He cocked his head and pondered, not daring to enter recklessly. Instead, he found an empty space, and took out various items from his robes, creating a strange formation. The appearance of this formation was extremely strange, looking like an inverted “J.” Afterwards, Leylin also carved a similar rune on his robes.

“It seems that I’m really fearful of death!” Leylin’s insecurities lessened after arranging the formation. He mocked himself as he entered the tunnel.

The bronze coloured pathway wasn’t long, and Leylin quickly reached its depths.

There was a small hall and in front of it, there was a black metal door, which was extremely tall, and over 4 meters wide.

On the metal door frame, there were various magic runes with the words ‘Experiment Lab #1. Supervisor: Edward’ written on it.

The words on the metal door were obviously very old, as there was some dust on it, and it looked slightly beaten.

When Leylin was in front of the doors, two figures entered his field of view

After seeing them, Leylin took the initiative to go forth. “Old Devil and Jaye, where’s Brass Ring?”

The old witch and Jaye were the ones that had appeared in front of Experiment Lab #1, while Brass Ring’s location was unknown.

“We stepped into a trap set up by the ancient Magi that caused us to become lost! In the trap, every time when we thought our partners were beside us, we had actually been separated and had gone further apart…”

The old witch replied, “When the trap activated, and the four of us entered the different pathways, I was met with a sound illusion that was arranged by the ancient Magi….After an intense battle, I found this place, and met up with Jaye. Her experiences were similar to mine…..”

Leylin nodded his head, after which he briefly stated his encounters. As for his abilities and spells, he had naturally glossed over the narration of that area.

He then said, “In this case, we should just wait for Brass Ring…”

“We don’t have to anymore! I can sense that Brass Ring is already dead!” Jaye spoke abruptly, causing Leylin to feel somewhat shocked.

This fellow, who seemed like a female, had seldom spoken ever since the group was formed. She also seemed to be rather close to the old witch, yet her energy waves were not very strong, just at the level of an average rank 1 Magus.

But now…

Leylin could not help but to look at Jaye.

Even though Jaye was still wearing a black cloak, her cloak was tattered. It seemed to bear traces of her battle.

Apart from that, the energy waves from Jaye’s body were fluctuating at an unsteady rate. Sometimes, they had the strength of a peak rank 1 Magus, while at other times, it felt like a fledgling rank 1 Magus who had just advanced. At other times, it would intensify greatly, keeping Leylin guessing.

“Jaye had learned and remembered an extremely special rank 1 spell. We were able to estimate the timing of the death of the magus, so we decided to wait for you here!”

Jaye seemed rather antisocial, and she would not speak unless it was of the utmost importance. Everything else was explained by the old witch.

“Is that right?” Leylin was a little doubtful, as the rank 1 magic of the Magus World was extremely peculiar. There was an unknown amount of Magi that built on spells that their ancestors had created or modified in order to create many different unique spells to be passed down, so Leylin wasn’t able to make a decision regarding what the Old Witch had said.

“Since you’re here, let’s take a short break before attempting to enter this Experiment Lab #1!”

The old witch seemed rather zealous. “I have a feeling that the altar I need is right inside!”

Leylin was somewhat speechless. This old witch appeared too impatient.

However, he still walked forward, and touched the black metal door.

Upon contact, an icy cold feeling could be felt as first, before a hotter temperature was felt. As for the sturdy metal door, it gave off a feeling of being indestructible.

From the runes and incantation on the door, Leylin could feel that this room was not used for experiments, but as a prison of some sort.

There was a brass keyhole at the center of the black door. The ethereal keyhole made Leylin’s hair stand on end, and he felt a bone freezing chilliness.

“I can’t fully understand the runes on this door, but I’m still able to make out the general meaning of some of the high levelled runes. There is a high levelled solidifying rune, and a metal memory rune. To break open this door, we will have to spend a lot of energy. Perhaps, we should try to find the key!”

Leylin suggested.

“There’s no need for that! It’s here with me!” The old witch cackled, withdrawing an extremely thick yellow bronze key from her robes.

This key was rather curvy, as if it was a ladle, but it was a perfect fit for the keyhole on the door.

The old witch took the bronze key, and inserted it into the door.

“Wait a minute!” At this moment, a figure appeared in front of her.

“Blood Rogue, what are you doing?” The old witch looked at Leylin, who was blocking her, rage evident on her face.

Jaye immediately stood behind the old witch at this moment. The magic rays emitted from her body caused Leylin’s eyelid to twitch.

“It’s nothing much, I just feel that the danger within has somewhat exceeded my expectations. I wish to withdraw!” Leylin was extremely calm.

“According to the information I’ve seen, this Ancient Spirit Slaying Sect has been the advocate behind the scenes of many ancient calamities. Moreover, it had been undergoing extremely dangerous spirit research…”

Leylin’s expression was extremely sincere as he continued to talk. “Therefore, I suggest that we temporarily stop this exploration, and attempt to explore again after gaining much greater powers….”

Chapter 184: The Awakening

Upon hearing her words, Leylin looked up in surprise.

Unconsciously, they had already reached the peak of the mountain of white bones.

Here, it was completely deserted except for the white altar at the peak of the mountain.

If one looked closely, it could be seen that the altar was made entirely out of human bones. These bones emitted energy fluctuations that far exceeded that of a rank 1 Magus and below, and just the aura made the air stifling, even for Leylin.

On some bones that were wider, there were strange runes handwritten in blood.

These runes were extremely complicated. Some were similar to 3D images, and Leylin had never seen any of them before.

What struck him the most was how, even though the runes had existed for over five thousand years, the blood was bright red and still looked fresh, as if ready to drip to the ground.

They were arranged in a strange manner and seemed to form a map.

Leylin took a closer look and realised that he recognised several of the areas in the secret plane. Filled with ecstasy, he immediately got the A.I. Chip to record everything down.

At the very centre of the altar, there was an odd skull used as a sacrifice.

The skull was similar to that of a human’s skull, but on the cranium, there were two black, bent horns like that of a goat.

Also, in the middle of the two horns, there was a small round hole that seemed to serve no purpose.

“Is this the spirit altar you were looking for?”

Leylin glanced at the old witch, but her eyes were already fixed on the altar. She was murmuring words in a language that he did not know, and seemed to have forgotten about the existence of the others with her.

What made Leylin more surprised was Jaye, who was beside him. Even with the cover of the huge black cloak, Leylin could tell she was shivering badly.

This discovery worried Leylin, and at the same time, a sense of unease in his heart was intensified.

“It’s here. Right here… My darling, I can now help you…”

While mumbling incessantly, the old witch produced a fragment of a piece of parchment and threw it towards the altar.

At the same time, Jaye, who had been shaking all this while, suddenly made her move!

Streams of translucent, faintly green rays of light descended from the heavens and formed a large net, aiming for Leylin. The surrounding air produced a hissing sound, and there seemed to be some undulations in the scenery around them.

“What are you doing?”

Leylin bellowed, though his expression did not undergo much changes.

It was apparent that he had been expecting something like this, and had thus made some preparations.

*Boom!*

On Leylin’s head, countless black strands of hair seemed to have lives of their own as they wriggled to counter the approaching green net.

*Pu Pu!*

The instant the half transparent green net and the black strands of hair met, large amounts of white gas emerged, and the sound of corrosion constantly erupted in the air.

With a wave of his hair, Leylin’s figure flickered and he shifted over ten metres away from his original spot.

“Madori Defensive Spell Formation!” Jaye, who was in the black cloak, was well aware that Leylin’s power surpassed hers. She had acted first in order to gain the upperhand.

While Leylin was dealing with that large net, Jaye had already fixed up a defensive formation around the spirit altar!

“Activate!” Along with Jaye’s words, translucent black rays rose around the spirit altar, keeping the altar, Jaye and the old witch protected inside.

“Latent Fireball!” With a flash of Leylin’s eyes, countless black fireballs emerged from the shadows, rushing towards the black dome!

*Bang!*

The numerous black fireballs converged and its volume expanded by more than ten times. With the added bonus of Leylin’s elemental essence conversion of 70%, its might had become exceedingly horrifying.

Under this level of attack, an ordinary Magus’ innate defensive spell would be completely destroyed within seconds!

The black flames spread, and even with Jaye within the dome trying her very best to maintain it, it was still vibrating vigorously, as if on the verge of breaking.

However, Jaye was unperturbed and chanted a few incantations.

*Buzz buzz!* From the bottom of the altar, a circle of black light emerged, merging with the defensive spell formation.

*Peng!*

With the addition of this circle of light, the entire defensive spell formation immediately became more radiant. Its colour was black to the extreme, and it was almost impossible to see the figures behind the formation.

Flames from the Latent Fireball burnt at the surface of the dome for over ten seconds.

But when facing the reinforced defensive spell formation, they could do little but succumb and disperse.

“This…”

Seeing how Jaye seemed to be able to take advantage of the powers of the laboratory, Leylin hastily moved a few steps backwards.

The old witch was sure to have hidden a lot of information from him. Thinking back to the spirit explosion that she had previously used and what had happened with the Loathsome Evil, Leylin was certain that the old witch had found out about these ruins much earlier, contrasting with what she had said. She must have already reaped a bountiful harvest from within the ruins before this expedition.

“Give up! This is the core of the secret plane. After borrowing a portion of its strength, it’s impossible to break through this defensive formation unless your power has reached such heights that you’re able to destroy this entire secret plane!”

From within the black dome, Jaye’s faint voice was transmitted over. However, there was no hint of joy in her gaze and her eyes were not on Leylin but rather on the witch. There were dozens of complicated emotions on her face- anticipation, joy, and also… fear!

Upon coming into contact with the altar, the yellowed fragmented piece of parchment burst into flames.

These flames were a light yellow and extremely pure. They started off as small as a bean and gradually crept to engulf the entire parchment, the flames turning light blue.

At the same time, the altar seemed to come to life and began to tremble.

From the gaps between the bones of the altar, fresh red blood trickled down. Dark rays were emitted from the eye sockets of many skulls.

“Old witch! You’d better calm down. It’s obvious that there’s an extremely strong and evil being trapped within the altar. I don’t care if you made a pact or some contract with it, but the strong won’t bother making transactions with the weak.”

Outside the spell formation, Leylin recalled what he had seen and hastily spoke.

“Of course, I know what’s in there! I knew about it 157 years ago! If not for it being in hibernation, and the conditions to awaken it being too harsh, I would have summoned it a long time ago… As long as I summon it, I can…”

The old witch’s facial muscles twisted, her expression crazed as she gestured wildly.

This exposed her knowledge about the ruins.

“You need to think this through. This is an evolved being that escaped out of the Loathsome Evil’s body and is much more sinister and vicious. It’s something the likes of you definitely can’t control.”

As Leylin persuaded her, he’d already left his original position and backed away to where they had climbed up, a ring of Darkness energy particles around his two legs.

“I know better than you how vicious it can get! Even though I can’t control it, I know how it was assembled and basically everything there is to know about it. As long as we give enough offerings, with the power of this spirit altar, I can definitely…”

Her eyes were crazed as she spread out her arms and yelled, “Come out! The collective body of vengeance, the manipulator of spirits and bodies! The supreme king, Gargamel!”

“Gargamel?!” Leylin’s heart lurched.

Before he had come here, he had seen plenty of records regarding the Ancient Spirit Slaying Sect and naturally knew about this Gargamel. It was a being that the sect had worshipped.

They believed that a spirit was the last resting place for all beings, and the Gargamel was the one in charge of all these spirits!

It was apparent that this was a Gargamel that had already taken shape after the Ancient Spirit Slaying Sect’s immense efforts in cultivating it! However, for some reason, this Gargamel had been sealed here by the Magi of the sect.

The old witch had obviously received the inheritance from the Ancient Spirit Slaying Sect and obtained many benefits. She had also been working hard to unseal the Gargamel.

Leylin believed he had a rough understanding of this whole situation.

The black ring of light around his legs flashed and, wrapped in energy particles, his body’s speed reached its limits and he instantly disappeared away from the mountain.

Even though he had no idea why the old witch had swindled him and Brass Ring into coming here, it definitely wasn’t anything good!

Leylin felt it was better if he retreated as soon as possible.

As long as he was out of this secret plane, even if the old witch and Jaye attacked together, Leylin was certain he could take care of them.

“A smart move, but it’s a pity that it’s too late…” Jaye, who was nearby, gave a low sigh.

At this very moment, the piece of parchment on the altar had already been burnt to ashes and, with a cry from the old witch, streams of black gases streamed out of the gaps within the bones of the altar.

*Weng Weng!*

An ancient devil was awake once more.

An aura that caused one’s heart to palpitate in fear arrived on top of the mountain of white bones.

Ice-cold! Evil!

Leylin felt as if he had returned to his childhood, powerless while surrounded by a group of direwolves.

He hated being made aware of how fragile his life was.

Just with the leakage of this aura, the secret plane vibrated slightly.

A vast amount of black gas converged and gradually solidified, forming a gigantic translucent figure.

The figure brought the skull on top of the altar to its face, treating it as a mask. Its two completely red eyes seemed to be looking down on every one of the Magi present as if they were mere ants.

Leylin’s heart plummeted, and he could not gather any strength.

“Jiik!” The black figure bellowed towards the heavens.

With the tremendous sound waves, the black defensive spell formation that had caused Leylin much trouble instantaneously gave way, and the old witch and Jaye were forced aside from the pressure.

*Pu!*

As the old witch flew backwards, mouthfuls of blood spurted out like water gurgling in a spring.

Chapter 187: Emergency Situation

The speed at which Leylin escaped was extremely quick, and after just half a day, the tall, thick walls of the Nightless City were within sight.

At this point, his right hand had already completely healed. The frightening vitality of a Warlock was proving its worth.

Only after entering the Nightless City did Leylin breathe a huge sigh of relief.

The Gargamel was the result of the concentration of evil intentions by the Ancient Spirit Slayer Sect. Although it was unknown why that Gargamel had been sealed there by the Magi of the sect, based on the calculations from the battle with it, Leylin could say that this monster’s strength was equivalent to that of a rank 2 Magus!

Although Leylin couldn’t hold his own against it, there were a couple rank 2 Magi in the south coast that could. At the very least, the leaders of large scale Magus organisations and powers definitely had at least this level of power.

At that moment, within the Nightless City, the trading centre of the south coast, there were quite a few Magi with this kind of strength.

Leylin was sure that if the Gargamel were to chase after him, the Nightless City was sure to have the means to stop it!

However, he had another plan in mind.

The old witch was trapped in the secret plane together with that terrifying culmination of evil. From the looks of it, her chances of survival were meagre.

However, it was a fact that she held the position of elder in the dark Magus organisation that Leylin was affiliated with—Thousand Meddling Hands. Her status was obviously higher than that of an average member, and she was also able to contact the hidden rank 2 Magus heading the group!

With her death, there would be loose ends that needed to be tied up.

If possible, Leylin would obviously want to take possession of everything the old witch owned.

In a light Magus organisation, this would naturally be impossible. However, in the case of Thousand Meddling Leaves, as long as he revealed a bit of his might, it would be enough to subdue the ambitious Magi who wished to take over this position.

“Hello? Is this Leylin?”

At this moment, a secret imprint that resembled a four-coloured ring emerged from Leylin’s waist. A man’s voice was transmitted from it.

“Hello, Lord Decarte!”

Leylin could make out the owner of this imprint. It was the head of the Potioneering team, Decarte! His tone naturally became respectful.

Previously, all of the missions that Decarte needed Leylin to complete had been issued to him by Leylin’s current leader, Martin

“Ugh, the secret imprint seemed to have had some sort of interference, and I couldn’t contact you at all. Did you go somewhere far away?”

Decarte’s questions were transmitted to him from the secret imprint.

“Yes. I’d accepted a friend’s invitation to explore a small ruin…” Leylin’s answer was half true.

“No wonder! Many of these ruins left behind by Magi will automatically block out all forms of communication. In there, a secret imprint is merely a useless decoration…” No matter if Decarte actually believed him or not, the voice from the secret imprint sounded convinced.

“My apologies for making my lord worry about me. Might I ask what you require of me?” Leylin was puzzled as he spoke to the imprint.

“Yes, there’s something that I need. A few elders and the head have issued orders that Four Seasons Garden has entered the highest state of alert. All Magi will have their vacations cancelled! Upon receiving this message, you must report to the headquarters within 24 hours! All who do not do so will be viewed as traitors, and will be punished by the law enforcers!”

Decarte broke out the earth-shattering news.

“What?”

Leylin was in shock, causing him to take a few steps back.

The Four Seasons Garden wasn’t stupid, and issuing such an order could only imply one thing. Something was going to happen to the entire south coast.

“I’ll be there in time! Can you tell me what has happened?”

Leylin sucked in a few breaths of air and calmed himself down before inquiring.

“The whole situation is a little complicated. You can ask Martin about it when you’re back. There’s only one thing I can tell you—war! A war is approaching…”

“I don’t have any more time left. Just remember to come here as quickly as possible! In war, the weak ones who don’t have organisations to rely on are usually the first to die!”

*Pop!* With his last word, the secret imprint dispersed into countless bright sparks, drifting through the air around Leylin.

Decarte’s sounded serious, which caused Leylin’s heart to sink.

When compared to these strong organisations, the conflict at the Abyssal Bone Forest Academy was but a small matter.

To have caused the Four Seasons Garden’s Potioneering team head to be so flustered, there was only one possibility—that an incoming war was going to rock the Magus World!

Leylin suddenly remembered some information about Magus’ history.

After the ancient times had passed, it was the current period. During this current period, two huge wars had occurred. These two events had affected the Magi, and basically all species in the entire south coast. The Magi suffered massive casualties, and the humans were obviously more affected, with numerous empires annihilated.

These two wars were named the First and Second Great Magus Wars!

Now, it seemed the Third Great Magus War was about to begin!

Leylin’s scrunched up his brows and wrinkled his forehead.

For him, it was entirely possible to accumulate information and resources, and with the A.I. Chip, he would be able to constantly break through his bottlenecks and improve further.

As a result, Leylin had hoped to be able to develop in a more peaceful and stable environment until he would reach a bottleneck.

In the previous great wars, acolytes were cannon fodder. Even official Magi fell and died in swarms, resulting in the alternate name of the wars: the Magus World’s Death Grinder.

Leylin wasn’t sure that he would be lucky enough to escape unscathed!

Wars of this scale affected the entire south coast, and nobody had been able to escape. As long as one was a Magus, he or she would be involved in it.

Unless… If he left the south coast and passed through several extremely dangerous regions, and set off for a new place, he would be safe.

“I shouldn’t scare myself. It might just be a conflict between the Four Seasons Garden and another Magus organisation!”

Leylin, who had been standing by the city gates, suddenly smiled gently and walked right inside.

He’d thought it through. No matter what happened, it had absolutely nothing to do with him.

After all, he was a member of Four Seasons Garden’s Potioneering team! Unless Caesar’s entire hunting team was annihilated, research personnel like him wouldn’t need to be on the battlefield.

If this was a war with other Magus organisations, with the Four Seasons Garden’s background, it would be impossible to be thoroughly annihilated. If he were to defect now, it would be an extremely foolish decision that would offend the Four Seasons Garden for no reason.

If the Third Great Magus War was to happen, the entire south coast would become a battlefield, and no area would be safe.

Decarte’s words were a reminder as well as a warning.

Great wars never began with both sides going all out. It would start with them using small groups and neutral parties to eliminate all other elements, and then they would be able to fight freely, without fear of others taking advantage of the situation.

Wandering Magi and indecisive small organisations were definitely the first to be used!

Leylin didn’t want to lose his backing and live a life where a crisis was always imminent.

As a result, it was necessary for him to return to the Four Seasons Garden.

Leylin was confident that he had hidden his skills well. In the eyes of the Magi in the Four Seasons Garden, Leylin was merely a newly advanced Magus who was talented in Potioneering and training!

If the leaders of Four Seasons Garden were stupid enough to get Leylin to be cannon fodder, then at the most, he would just leave and cut all connections between them.

Leylin was confident he would be able to leave the Four Seasons Garden’s headquarters without alerting the rank 2 Magi there.

After thinking this entire matter through, Leylin achieved a calm state of mind. Only then did he have the mood to survey his surroundings.

At this moment, Leylin discovered a difference in the Nightless City!

The Nightless City’s large gates had all been opened wide. Giants, which were usually rarely seen, could be seen wearing animal hides that did not fit them, and holding huge wooden stakes. They were entering the city in twos and threes.

With every step they took, the ground slightly shook.

The number of people in the Nightless City had increased by around 50%, causing a few passages to become congested.

However, whether they were regular humans, acolytes, or even some official Magi, their expressions were dark. In particular, there were a few official Magi who had a deep sense of distrust in their eyes when they saw unfamiliar Magi.

In the first zone of the Nightless City, shops that used to be bustling despite their unorganized placement saw a sharp decrease in price of raw materials. Defensive items, potions, and the like, on the other hand, were experiencing an increase in price. Many shops had already put up signs saying they were sold out.

Though Leylin had expected this, seeing this scene in person definitely had an effect on his mood.

All this was evidence of the scale of the impending war that would affect the entire Magus World. Leylin would definitely not be able to escape this!

Leylin’s footsteps seemed to become a bit heavier as he passed through several gates and entered the third zone of the Nightless City.

In the region where the villas were located, the originally lively place was somewhat deserted. There were no signs of the cheerful Magi who used to hang around the various gardens. Several flowers that used to be tended to in the flower terrace were listlessly lowering their heads, with some even showing signs of wilting, which gave off a bleak atmosphere.

“Master!”

Once he returned to his own villa, Damien, the level 3 acolyte who worked as his butler, welcomed him.

“I’m fine! Did anything strange happen in the Nightless City recently? Tell me everything you know!” Leylin immediately asked while he threw his cloak to Damien.

“Yes! Damien was just about to do so!”

There was a worried expression on his face.

“A day before, rumours about the start of a third Magus war started spreading around the Nightless City. At the beginning, nobody took it to heart, but as time passed, the fact that no organisation stood up to refute this claim has Nightless City in a frenzy…”

Chapter 188: Branding Experiment

Damien expressed a slightly apprehensive expression.

“Many Magi simply left. Huge numbers of people are in the streets buying items to increase their powers. It’s as though they are trying to use up all of the magic crystals at their disposal…”

“That strange phenomenon only gradually abated after the public center dispatched people to patrol the streets…..”

“Moreover, your good friend Magus Crew also moved out this afternoon. Before he left, he left a message for you!”

“What message?”

“The night is approaching. Be careful in everything you do!” Damien said something that sounded like a proverb.

“What does that mean?” Leylin frowned. “When did that Crew start to like being a prophetic Magus? The things he says are never clear!”

Leylin pondered for a moment, and finally told Damien, “From the information I’ve gathered, there will probably be a relatively large war that is imminent……”

Even though he already had some guesses, when Damien heard this information, his body trembled uncontrollably. He was originally caught and became a slave because of a war. Even though he was under a spirit branding, that bitter experience was just like a brand that was deeply engraved in his memories, making it impossible for him to forget.

“That’s right, call Number 1 to 5 over here!”

Leylin casually instructed Damien, who rapidly suppressed his shaking body, and withdrew at an extremely fast pace.

After a few minutes, five armoured Grand Knights with greatswords appeared before Leylin and knelt to perform a perfect Knight’s greeting!

“Master!”

The extremely thick armour didn’t affect their movements in the slightest way, and every movement of those five people carried a killing intent. It could be seen at a glance that they were strong veteran Grand Knights that had experienced countless battles.

“You may rise!” Leylin commented softly as he looked at those five people.

They were naturally the five Grand Knight slaves that he had purchased at the slave market in addition to Damien.

With the spirit branding, Leylin could order these five Grand Knights to die and they would obey without any hesitation.

They originally had names, but for convenience’s sake, Leylin gave all of them new names with numbers, starting from 1 to 5.

Leylin had put in considerable amounts of effort on the five Grand Knights. He constantly fixed their conditions during the past year. He didn’t even mind spending a lot of his resources to brew precious potions for them to consume.

Currently, the five experimental bodies’ were unconsciously giving off energy waves filled with life force. They were already beyond the Grand Knight’s rank and were beginning to advance to a higher realm.

“What are the results of the secret techniques that I taught you previously?”

Leylin asked.

“Master! After using the secret techniques along with the potions from before, Number 2, 3 and I felt life force start to flow through us, which was something that had not happened for a long time. Our vitality also became increasingly stronger.”

The big man on the far left stepped out of the line and said, “But when Number 4 and 5 used the secret techniques, the brand on their bodies shook and gave off scorching hot energies that interrupted their training……..”

This Grand Knight slave, known as Number 1, gave an extremely detailed report.

In the past year, Leylin had been constantly modifying the brands of the five through the modifications made by the A.I. Chip. This had allowed him to gain a lot of fruitful experiment results.

The ’secret techniques’ that were previously taught to those five Grand Knights were just improvised data from the information about Branded Swordsman.

“Is that so?” Leylin’s gaze became stern. “Remove your clothes!”

The five slaves removed their body armour without any thoughts after hearing their master’s order.

*Crash!* Metal armour made a racket as they hit the ground. The Grand Knights had removed the heavy armour in just a couple of seconds, revealing completely unclothed bodies.

Moreover, Number 4 and 5 were female Grand Knights, but they weren’t at all embarrassed as they stood before Leylin with their well-developed bodies and private parts completely exposed.

Those five had the strength of Grand Knights. Their bodyline was supple, but was well developed. Every inch of their flesh hid an astonishing explosive power.

Their bodies were akin to perfectly sculpted statues.

However, there were elements that offset their aesthetic appearance from being perfect.

Leylin didn’t cared about the two Grand Knight beauties; his gaze was completely focused on the interweaving brand on their body.

Leylin scrutinised their bodies.

He noticed that the bodies of his Grand Knight subordinates were covered with deep, black brands.. Near these brands were some twisting scars. It seemed as if a branding iron was the source of the brands and scars.

With close observation, the brands looked like a centipede climbing. while their chest and lower abdomen regions formed an extremely peculiar rune.

Some of the brands seemed to be broken and were unable to link together.

“A.I. Chip! Scan those brands and compare the current conditions of these Grand Knights to the previous observations in a new file!” Leylin thought.

As he said this, a blue light shone in his eyes and swept horizontally across those slaves.

[Beep! Mission established! Commencing the scanning!] The A.I. Chip followed the tasks that Leylin ordered.

Rows of numbers and three 3-D images appeared before Leylin and were constantly being updated.

“En! It seemed that the training method that I created isn’t bad. These Knights’ physical qualities have had drastic improvements and are also able to train their life force. Their previous stagnant powers are starting to rapidly improve!”

Leylin was extremely satisfied after looking at the results of the three male Grand Knights.

“The training method of the Branded Swordsman conflicts with the brands on their bodies?”

Leylin carefully looked through the A.I. Chip’s results while constantly walking around the slaves in order to attentively observe the position of the brands.

“Where is the source of the previous problem? Is it here?”

Leylin placed his hands below the lower abdomen of Number 4 without ascribing and thoughts to what he was doing. After having placed his hand there, he felt a warm sensation and could feel that underneath the smooth and supple skin, there were muscles that were slightly twitching now.

“Yes…Yes, that’s the place, Master!” said Number 4 with a slightly shaky voice. This female Grand Knight had a good appearance and an exceptionally curved, bountiful body

“If that’s the case!” Leylin caressed his lower jaw.

“A.I. Chip! Amend the parameters for the two female knights to the p-grade content and change the index to the third grade before testing again!”

This kind of calculation was an easy task for the A.I. Chip. After a short moment, the A.I. Chip had already concluded its calculation and reported it to Leylin.

[Beep! According to the calculation, the brandings of the swordsman are different for males and females. The markings must follow a carved inscription!]

After looking at the A.I. Chip’s conclusion, Leylin’s expression did not change since he had expected such a result.

“So it really was the case! Kroft had gotten hold of a part of the Branded Swordsman information, but there is an extreme lack of information concerning the brandings. The runes inscribed on males had been deduced by the A.I. Chip. Moreover, those marks aren’t suitable for females, which resulted in the two female Knights being unable to train!”

“It seems that I must purchase a large quantity of male Grand Knight slaves to try to create a Branded Swordsman!”

Leylin planned to himself.

To him, using males or females didn’t have any differences. He just needed to head to different sections of the slave Market for them.

However, regarding the most crucial rune inscriptions for the Branded Swordsman, he could only amend the model to suit males. While it was not impossible to create something out of nothing for a female version of the model, it would take a lot of time. Leylin didn’t want to spend the A.I. Chip’s precious calculation skills on this matter.

“Since this is the case, there’s only one troublesome problem in manufacturing Branded Swordsman, which is the problem in combining the markings’ powers.”

Leylin rubbed his lower jaw with flames burning in his eyes.

The ancient Branded Swordsman were similar to the bloodline Warlocks and elemental bards, which were among the stronger professions of the sub branch of the magi. Their specialties were their physical defence and offensive powers, which were regarded as their enemies’ nightmares.

Moreover, the combination of the Branded Swordsman and magicians was an eternal nightmare for many worlds.

If the Branded Swordsman could perform crowd control, then the Magi behind them would have the time to prepare the formidable power of magic in order to change a given situation.

Moreover, the power of an official Branded Swordsman was equivalent to that of at least a rank 1 Magus!

Leylin just needed to form an army with Branded Swordsmen. The quantity didn’t need to be large; 20 of them would be sufficient. With such forces, Leylin would no longer have an opponent at the rank 1 Magus level and he was also confident enough to be able to fight against a rank 2 Magus!

“However, regarding the problem of the powers, the runes of the Branded Swordsman is the pivotal point. Even if it was the A.I. Chip, it could not guarantee perfection without countless experiments and accumulation of data. Moreover, there’s also a problem in controlling the Branded Swordsmen after they evolve to a higher realm…”

Leylin lowered his head as he muttered to himself irresolutely.

He was only a rank 1 Magus now, so he could at most control level 3 acolytes and Grand Knights.

However, in a similar fashion as the Magi and Warlocks, the ancient Branded Swordsmen could break through the ordinary realm to reach an extraordinary one.

This power wasn’t something that Leylin could currently control by using the spirit brand.

Thus, a safer and more effective controlling method had to be researched and implemented on those Branded Swordsman!

Only with this method could the loyalty of his soldiers be guaranteed!

Chapter 193: Turin Language

Similar to Abyssal Bone Forest Academy, there were restricted areas in the Four Seasons Garden’s library.

The place Leylin wanted to go to was the Four Seasons Garden’s secret storage room.

In this private room, large amounts of knowledge regarding various subjects were open to official Magi. The fees were extremely expensive, and even the current Leylin was in pain over the costly price.

Although he could copy the information with the A.I. Chip, that still took time.

Leylin had calculated that even if he used up all his contribution points, it would barely give him enough time to record half of the information available in the room.

He had originally planned to amass enough contribution points first and then record all the information at one go.

But now…

Leylin went straight to the second floor of the library and waved his transparent crystal card at an old bookshelf.

*Kreeeen!* The bookshelf moved backwards, revealing a small passage.

Behind the passage was a small library with strangely shaped books placed on the rows of black wooden bookshelves within.

Some of the books even had pairs of arms and legs, and if not for the iron chains restraining them, they might just stealthily escape.

As he had a goal in mind, Leylin ignored them.

“A.I. Chip! Scan the catalogue. Search keywords: Ancient Spirit Slaying Sect, Emergency Passages…”

To find the content he needed from within this extremely extensive library, a lot of time would be wasted. Luckily for him, Leylin had the A.I. Chip, and within a few minutes, he found the information he wanted.

“I see…”

Following the A.I. Chip’s instructions, Leylin came to a corner and flipped through a very old book.

It was extremely thick and heavy, and the cover was an ashen grey. The A.I. Chip judged that this book was made of a very special ancient stone material.

This method of bookmaking belonged to an interesting group of tiny sub-humans—the Stone Men!

This was a race that had an appearance extremely similar to that of humans, but the main difference was the thick layer of calcite on their skin, which looked very much like someone casting a stone-skin spell.

Leylin read through this large book made of stone. On one of the pages, a strange spell formation had been carefully recorded.

“It’s this one! It’s more than 90% similar to the spell formation in the secret plane of the Ancient Spirit Slaying Sect!” Leylin’s expression brightened up.

Right before his eyes, the A.I. Chip brought up a picture of the ancient spell formation that he had obtained from the secret plane. He then compared it to the spell formation that was recorded down, and came to a conclusion that the two had a similarity of over 90%!

“That’s astonishing!”

Leylin continued analysing it, looking increasingly cautious.

Only now did he realise the true purpose of that spell formation—teleportation!

In the secret room that Leylin had found a corpse in while escaping, there still existed an ancient teleportation formation!

This type of teleportation formation could instantaneously teleport a few Magi to a distance further than several times the length of the south coast. However, due to the geologic faults and the extinction of crucial ingredients, the current south coast no longer had traces of these formations.

The Stone Men then were the best slaves that the ancient Magi used to construct the teleportation formations. It was because of this reason that there were records of this race.

“So in the space between levels in the emergency passage, there’s actually an ancient teleportation formation?”

Just the thought of it made Leylin breathe more quickly.

The south coast was surrounded by regions filled with varying levels of danger. In some places, rank 2 or 3 Magi would only be sending themselves to their death if they went there!

It was because of the existence of such dangers that the Magi in the south coast would rather have an internal strife every once in a while to reduce the number of Magi than venture outwards. They were unwilling to expand the territory and gain more resources.

Even if Leylin wanted to leave the south coast and look for traces of the central mainland, he had no way to leave!

However, with the appearance of the ancient teleportation spell formation, Leylin saw a glimmer of hope!

If he had tremendous luck and found a new land, how much profit would Leylin receive as the controller of the transportation pathway to there?

“No, I can’t do this! Calm down! Calm down! Whether this ancient teleportation formation can still be used or not, and where it leads to are all unknown. To make effective use of it, I have to answer all of these questions!”

Leylin stroked his chin and calmed his emotions.

He then produced a tattered diary from within his robes. “I might be able to find an answer with information from this diary.”

In the secret compartment within the emergency passage, not only did Leylin find the ancient teleportation formation, but he also found what seemed to be the remains of a high-ranking Magus of the Ancient Spirit Slaying Sect. In addition, he also found some miscellaneous items and this diary on the deceased Magus’ body.

The first thing Leylin did upon returning was to order the A.I. Chip to record all of the information in this tattered diary.

Unfortunately, the language used in the diary was not one that the A.I. Chip was able to interpret. This made it difficult for Leylin to decipher the information within!

“Those strange people in black gowns who like to enslave spirits preferred to use an odd language and characters to issue commands. As long as we didn’t understand, we would be punished cruelly, which forced us to learn the name of that damned Turin Language!”

In the Stone Men’s books, Leylin found this written account.

“No wonder the A.I. Chip couldn’t interpret the contents of the diary. So it was the Turin Language!” Leylin suddenly understood.

The Turin Language was an exclusive language used in ancient times, which used special sound waves and light rays to transmit information. Even its characters contrasted hugely compared to other existing languages.

There were no records of this Turin Language in the A.I. Chip’s database.

“Turin Language?”

Leylin went around the bookshelf, and in a corner, he finally found a few books that seemed to be written in the Turin Language. There was even a book that gave a concise introduction to interpreting this language.

“A.I. Chip, scan it!”

In his excitement, Leylin hurriedly opened one of the books and ordered the A.I. Chip to record it down…

“My Lord, it’s already time for dinner. Are you planning to enjoy a dinner party here? Your contribution points are almost completely used up at this point…”

Leylin was immersed in the sea of knowledge and was using the A.I. Chip to translate and restore the information in the diary.

In summary, there was a crazy Magus who kept using spirits to create the Gargamel. In the end, the experiment backfired on him. This was truly a tragic story.

What made Leylin most gleeful were the few images similar to the ancient teleportation formation that he found at the back of the diary.

Based on the images, as well as some speculations on the A.I. Chip’s part, Leylin would be able to test whether the formation was still workable.

Now in a marvellous mood, Leylin didn’t bother with the old manager and glanced at his crystal card. “I got it. I’ll be right out!”

Disregarding the old man, who was bowing so deeply his head touched the floor, Leylin jogged out of the library.

“A.I. Chip! Based on the information from just now, how complete was the previously recorded ancient teleportation formation?”

Leylin asked a little nervously.

[Beep! Mission established, sorting through information regarding teleportation, and comparing…]

The A.I. Chip’s mechanical voice sounded.

On the virtual screen in front of Leylin, large numbers of words and images flashed past, with the formation that had been previously recorded placed in the very centre.

[Beep! Comparison results: Completion of teleportation formation: 98.8%. Situation on other end of formation unknown, unable to calculate!]

The A.I. Chip’s answer made Leylin grin even more brightly.

Though there was still a troublesome Gargamel in the secret plane, Leylin felt that it would be in a hurry to escape. The secret compartment was hidden well, and there was a high chance that it was still well preserved.

The most important thing was the source of energy!

“Even ancient teleportation formations needed a source of power! A.I. Chip, what does this formation need to be usable?”

Leylin asked.

[Magic crystal essence, or some object that contains a dense amount of energy particles!] The A.I. Chip intoned.

“Magic crystal essence huh? The magic crystal cards aren’t enough?” Leylin asked.

[Beep! The energy contained within is not enough, will require a purifying process to condense the energy. Projected ingredients: 10,000 magic crystal cards or more!]

The A.I. Chip’s reply made Leylin’s legs wobble.

“Ten thousand magic crystal cards? A single card has a value of over a thousand magic crystals! Ten thousand magic crystal cards would mean that I will need over ten million magic crystals?!”

After a year of amassing resources from the light and dark Magi, the magic crystals and materials he had amassed only amounted to a value of less than five million!

And this A.I. Chip said that it needed twice that amount!

In addition, the A.I. Chip only needed magic crystal cards. Leylin needed to exchange large amounts of resources, magic items, knowledge, potions, and the like for magic crystals. This exchange would result in him racking up huge losses due to his pressing need for them.

“So many magic crystals… I’m afraid there will only be that amount stored in a few large scale Magus organisations’ resource-based secret planes.”

Leylin then shook his head. “This isn’t the time to think about that. There isn’t anything that requires me to risk my life, and even if it’s the Third Great Magus War, it is still limited to within the Eternal River Plains’ secret plane, and won’t have much of an impact on the outside world!”

Currently, in the Third Great Magus War, the main reason for the fighting was a dispute over the rights to the Eternal River Plains’ secret plane, so the various disputes and conflicts had been taking place within it.

According to Leylin’s guess, this slice of the cake was way too big, and no single organisation would be capable of devouring it whole. It would definitely be shared with the various large magisteriums and guilds.

As for what Four Seasons Garden and the other guilds had to do, it was to do their best to fight for a larger share!

Chapter 194: Blackmail

While freely strolling through the streets, Leylin heard an odd sound travel into his ears.

“We’re in such a dangerous situation, and yet you’re still so relaxed… It looks like I need to make a suggestion to Decarte for him to give you a more challenging job.”

The tone of this voice was icy, giving Leylin the impression he had attracted the attention of a ravenous wolf.

Leylin gave a helpless laugh and scratched his nose, after which he turned back and gave a bow. “Lord Caesar!”

In front of him was a Magus clothed in a black robe. There were several blood-red threads that decorated the robe, and bloodlust constantly emanated from him.

What was most unforgettable was the eye on his forehead!

This three-eyed Magus was naturally Caesar of the hunting team. He was an elitist, and firmly believed in one’s origin, so after Leylin entered Four Seasons Garden, he just didn’t like Leylin and constantly caused him trouble.

“Wasn’t his entire hunting team deployed into the Eternal River Plains’ secret plane? Did something happen that required him to rush back and report?”

While Leylin made his conjectures, he explained himself to Caesar. “ I, your subordinate, have completed all missions required for me to receive my monthly allocations, and have decided to take a walk to settle my mind.”

“I see! Hehe, you’re very capable. There might be a position that suits you better…”

Unexpectedly, Caesar did not inconvenience him, and only said something profound before leaving.

Leylin was left standing on the road, deep in thought.

“What did he mean by that?”

Soon enough, Leylin found out the meaning to Caesar’s words.

During dinner, a banquet was held in the hall. Members of the Potioneering team gathered in the hall and enjoyed a sumptuous meal.

Hazelnut chicken, roasted suckling pig, honey wine, and other delicious commonplace dishes were everywhere, arranged like trash on every corner.

At the centre of the table, there were also various delicacies that were only available in the Magus World.

Bubble fish! Dolosen Snake! Butter Yak! In addition, a lot of treasured ingredients that Leylin didn’t even know the names of were arranged neatly there.

The alluring smell of fine wine spread in the air, tempting everyone’s palate.

“There must have been much blood shed by the acolytes in preparing these dishes.”

Leylin picked up a piece of baked bubble fish, and while his taste buds enjoyed the new experience, he heaved an inward sigh of content.

This bubble fish was a high energy creature in the Magus World with a strength of a level 2 or 3 acolyte.

The Four Seasons Garden’s magic kitchen specifically issued requests for acolytes to gather the fish.

Behind this feast, there were the blood, sweat, and tears of countless acolytes who had gone on dangerous expeditions. The results of their efforts, which had garnered them some insignificant returns, eventually turned into gourmet food on the official Magi’s tables!

“It’s for this reason that I hope to become the person who will deprive others, and not get deprived myself!”

Leylin had a resolute look in his eyes while still maintaining a kind smile about his lips. He took another roasted pig trotter and put it on his plate.

With the nearing of his bloodline’s second transition, Leylin could feel abnormalities in his usual condition.

The most obvious one was a heightened appetite, particularly for the flesh of considerably strong, high-energy creatures.

After the sumptuous dinner, Decarte knocked on a golden cup on the table.

*Ding-ling!*

The entire room instantly turned silent. Leylin and the other Magi stood, waiting for the Potioneering team’s leader to issue missions and inform them of any arrangements.

“Everyone! Before we get into the important matters, let me announce something!”

Decarte looked at the Magi present and cleared his throat.

“Today, the hunting team’s Caesar looked for me, hoping to have a few Potion Masters join him! You must know that in the Eternal River Plains’ secret plane, there are frequent battles, resulting in a lack of healers. Many Potion Masters can use potions to achieve the same effect as healers.”

Hearing Decarte’s words, Leylin’s heart suddenly lurched.

“Now, I’ll announce the list of people to be sent there. They are Wilkenson, Saladin… and lastly, Leylin!”

As expected, Decarte increased his volume and read out Leylin’s name last.

In that instant, Leylin felt countless pairs of eyes staring at him.

Within these gazes were thoughts of curiosity, worry, and most prominently, schadenfreude.

His ostensible team leader was sighing heavily by the side. After Leylin left, with Martin’s abilities, it would be impossible to tackle the heavy workload that resulted from the war. However, Martin did not have the courage to dispute it, since this was the decision of the Potioneering team’s leader.

“Oh, my heavens! Leylin! What do we do?”

His partner, Oak, seemed to be completely stunned and gaped at Leylin.

“Don’t worry! Even if I am sent to the battlefield, I’ll most likely be working at the back, and won’t be in any real danger!” Seeing that there was someone who genuinely worried for him, a smile appeared on Leylin’s face.

In reality, was there any place on a battlefield that was absolutely safe, especially when he was directly under that three-eyed Magus, Caesar?

The moment he heard Decarte announce his name, Leylin immediately thought about Caesar’s cryptic smile.

“The aforementioned Magi have five days to prepare, after which they will be required to go to Four Seasons Garden’s branch at the Eternal River Plains’ secret plane and report. Otherwise, you will be seen as a traitor!”

Decarte seemed to be warning them at the end.

After offending the Abyssal Bone Forest Academy and the Lilytell family, which were both large dark Magi powers, Leylin had no wish to become enemies with an even stronger white Magi organisation.

If it came to that, he would no longer have a place on the south coast.

……

A day later, Leylin hastily organised everything and brought his two Great Knight servants along. They set off for the Eternal River Plains.

The sun shone mercilessly in the sky.

Smoke and dust flew above the ground, and not far away, the air seemed to be distorted.

This torrid heat meant there were almost no people walking on the main street.

*Thud Thud Thud!* At this moment, three quick horses hurtled past destroying the calmness and quiet atmosphere on this road.

“Master! There’s some shade in front. Shall we take a break there?”

Number 2 reined in his horse and asked Leylin, who was riding behind him.

“Let us take a rest. Although we can still manage, the poor horses can’t anymore!”

Leylin pointed to the horses, which were on the verge of frothing at the mouth.

Behind him, there were a few idle horses, on top of which were boxes and the other luggage they needed had been tied down. They looked listless, with their ears pressed to their heads, and the light in their eyes dim.

If Leylin was travelling alone, he naturally could travel on the Venom Wyvern.

However, he had to bring his two Grand Knight subordinates and even had to haul around a large amount of luggage. With this large amount of things, it naturally exceeded the burden that the Venom Wyvern could carry.

The Nightless City didn’t have any airships that could directly transport people to the Eternal River Plains’ secret plane, so Leylin could only rely on the most primitive method, which was traveling on horseback.

As for the Venom Wyvern, Leylin commanded it to scout the area in the sky and accompany them on their journey.

“Master! Here’s some water!”

Leylin found a clean rock for himself to sit on. Number 3, who was behind him, passed him a large leather pouch.

“En!” Leylin drank from it.

Although the temperature did not impact his vitality very much, the ice cold water washing down his throat gave him a very refreshing sensation.

“Hmmm?”

Suddenly, a gray fog covered the area surrounding the shade of the trees they were under.

Under the dim light, the various branches of the trees looked like the hands of monsters, as if wanting to grab hold of Leylin and the group.

At the same time, a drowsy feeling began to enshroud the three of them.

“Who is it?” Number 2 and Number 3 expanded their muscles and were ready to emit energy waves.

Leylin’s icy glare stopped them, and they stiffly collapsed onto the floor.

“Hei Hei… Blood Rogue, these two Grand Knights of yours have been modified well! They can actually defend against my hypnosis!” The voice of a little boy travelled over.

Leylin’s brows furrowed as he heard the name ‘Blood Rogue’.

He was still dressed as a normal Magus, yet this dark Magus from the Thousand Meddling Hands had actually seen through his disguise. From the looks of it, despite his efforts to conceal his identity, part of what he had done had been too high profile, resulting in the discovery of his identity.

It was very likely that even the Four Seasons Garden had similar suspicions about him!

It was because of this that Decarte was glad to see Caesar deploy Leylin elsewhere, and even chairman Reynold did not have any objections.

“Boy! What’s the matter?”

Since he had been found out, Leylin asked bluntly.

“Hehe… This is about Old Devil. She is an elder of the organisation after all, and it’s not known whether she is currently alive or dead. ‘Boss’ had instructed us to investigate thoroughly. According to what I know, her final appearance was to invite you and Brass Ring to participate in an expedition…”

“You’re correct! However, Brass Ring had perished inside! As for Old Devil, she is currently not able to leave! As for the secret plane’s location, I have no comments about that!”

Leylin did not believe that they would be this concerned about her whereabouts. It was more likely that they were coveting Old Devil’s position as an elder!

As expected, after hearing Leylin’s answer, the boy snickered. “You’re the Blood Rogue, after all! The way you work is straightforward and clear-cut! Let’s stop talking about Old Devil and move on. I currently bring you a mission from Boss!”

With the mention of this boss, the boy sounded more serious.

“What’s the meaning of this? Since when does the Thousand Meddling Hands force missions on their members?” Leylin wrinkled his brows. From the looks of it, the all-powerful dark Magus behind the Thousand Meddling Hands had finally been lured to the surface.

“Of course, there wasn’t anything like this before! However, it’s all different now! I believe that you will definitely do something for the organisation in order to protect your identity. Am I right, Leylin—or shall I say, Blood Rogue!”

The boy began to threaten him, a hint of arrogance apparent in his tone.

Chapter 196: Acquaintances

“I signed the contract under the witness of the Trial’s Eye, promising not to do anything that would harm Four Seasons Garden’s interests! If I go back on that agreement, I would undergo judgment…”

This was Leylin’s largest concern.

If he had the choice, he didn’t want to harm Four Seasons Garden since they had treated him quite well from the beginning.

“That’s easily solved! Here is a solution of Filthy Birds’ wings. As long as you have it, you can nullify your contract with the Four Seasons Garden!”

Giant threw a bottle of grey solution towards Leylin.

“You even have items that are already extinct!” Leylin caught the bottle and let the A.I. Chip test the authenticity of the item. The results made him gasp.

With such a degree of preparation, it wouldn’t be a stretch to say that this had been premeditated long ago.

“Hehe… This isn’t mine but belongs to the ‘Boss’ behind me. He especially left this for you from his own collection!”

Giant did not claim the credit for himself and used a straightforward tone, which made Leylin slightly fearful.

“So, what’s your answer?”

“Acknowledging the strength of others is the instinct of all dark Magi. I first need to verify your strength!” Leylin pondered for a moment and then spoke.

“You will see…” Giant’s voice began to be less discernible.

Large amounts of green mist shrouded the surrounding area, enveloping Leylin within.

Some time later, the mist dispersed and Leylin left, his expression serious. He seemed to be worrying about many things.

“I never thought it’d be him…”

Following which, Leylin calmed himself and returned to his accommodations, as if nothing had happened.

After a night passed, Leylin continued on his journey.

The Eternal River Plains were situated at the border between the light and dark Magi’s territories. Security there was the most chaotic.

Here, even within the city, armed confrontations, robbery, murder, and other crimes happened daily. At times, there would even be the occasional battle between Magi!

In this situation, the guards of the city were more like professional corpse carriers and were in charge of clearing the roads everyday.

After Eternal River Plains’ secret plane had been discovered, a large number of Magi flowed in, causing even more chaos in this place.

On the way, just the number of people who were looking to seek revenge was above 15. This meant that every once in awhile, there would be someone with such a motivation.

If not for Leylin and his group wearing clothing that gave them an air of mystery, even Magi like them might meet with some trouble.

After walking out of a city of regular humans, Leylin suddenly started, seeming to have seen some familiar figures.

“Master, what’s wrong? Is there something wrong with those acolytes?”

Number 2 and 3 approached him and enquired.

“It’s nothing!” Leylin answered casually. Even if it was them, they were from two different worlds. Leylin wasn’t planning on maintaining any contact with them, and passing them by. This might be the best for them.

Sometimes, however, fate was such a strange thing that could not be hindered.

Just as Leylin was hastening his travelling and leaving the gates, he bumped into those acolytes from earlier.

“Leylin! Hi! Leylin! Is that you?” Within the group of acolytes, a tall young man standing in the front was yelling excitedly.

They had been quite a distance away previously, but now that they met, the acolyte opposite to Leylin had instantly recognised him.

“Long time no see!” Leylin watched the acolytes, who were moving forward attentively, and couldn’t help but give a gentle smile in greeting.

After strengthening his body, Leylin’s physique and sight had vastly improved. He could easily see that out of all the acolytes, the one who had shouted was very tall and a had a head of long golden hair, thick eyebrows, large eyes, and a high nose bridge.

There was also a female acolyte with an exquisitely curvy body, silver hair and eyes like rubies. She constantly emanated an exotic charm.

Leylin immediately recognised these two acolytes. They were the people he hadn’t seen in ages—George and Bessita!

“But isn’t George an acolyte at the Ennea Ivory Ring Tower? Why is he together with Bessita, who’s from Wetland Gardens Academy?”

This thought went through his mind for a split second before he was interrupted, as George had brought Bessita and the others to approach him.

“Leylin, it’s really you! I thought I’d gotten the wrong person!”

George was a good friend that he’d made on that first journey in the beginning, and just like before, he affectionately gave Leylin a bear hug.

Bessita, on the other hand, was twiddling her fingers at the side, seemingly embarrassed.

At the beginning, she had caused much trouble for Leylin. Of course, after Leylin had viciously beat up her ‘flower guardian’ as a threat to her, this woman had become very silent.

However, she was still able to pass the magician aptitude test and enter the Wetland Gardens Academy.

“Hi, Leylin.” Bessita looked to be rather indifferent.

“Come here! Leylin, let me introduce you. This is Alexander!” George pointed at a youth with reddish-brown hair.

“This here is Lana! And the beauty in pink clothing is our long distance attacker— Shiera!”

After that, George introduced the two female acolytes beside him. Lana was alright, but Sheira aggressively pinched the flesh on George’s waist. He immediately let out exaggerated sounds of pain; it looked as if these two had a less innocent relationship.

Leylin couldn’t help but glance at Sheila more closely. She wore pink hunter gear that exposed a pair of milky white thighs. She was tall and carried a green wooden bow, looking to be a good match with George.

Even Leylin had to admit that George had pretty good taste.

“Leylin, why aren’t you introducing your two friends here to us?” After saying that, George mock punched Leylin’s chest, which stunned him a little.

He looked at his own attire and then responded.

For the sake of convenience while travelling, Leylin and his two Grand Knights had on civilian clothing. After obtaining the old witch’s spirit force compression method, he would also habitually conceal his energy waves, which indicated that he was an official Magus.

His two spiritually bound slaves were treated the same way.

Hence, George and the others, who were still acolytes, obviously were unable to discover Leylin’s concealment and treated him as a regular acolyte.

“These are my two friends. We met on the way and appeared to be going to the same place. They aren’t very talkative and are a little antisocial!”

Leylin threw a sculpture of a wyvern into Number 2 and Number 3’s hands. “Take this and leave first. We’ll meet at our destination!”

Upon receiving their master’s secret instructions, Number 2 and Number 3 nodded and left on horseback.

“Leylin, it’s best if you’re warier when interacting with them. I always feel uncomfortable around them…”

George looked at the figures of Number 2 and Number 3 as they left, and he whispered to Leylin.

“Don’t worry, I know my limits!”

Leylin nodded.

“Haha… Let’s not talk about this anymore. Leylin, we haven’t met in six or seven years, huh? This time, we have to drink to our heart’s content!”

George naturally put an arm around Leylin’s shoulder, and one could hear his excessive and proud laughter from miles away. “Guess what? Two years ago, I advanced and became a level 3 acolyte! Even my mentor complimented me for this! But it’s not much; it can’t be helped that I only have a fourth-grade aptitude.”

Due to this chance meeting, Leylin and George dispelled all thoughts of leaving the city and returned inside. They found a small bar and prepared to reminisce.

After two beers, Leylin had gleaned everything he wanted to know from George.

George was obviously still a student of Ennea Ivory Ring Tower, and so was his girlfriend, Sheira.

Bessita, Lana, and that guy called Alexander were all acolytes from the Wetland Gardens Academy.

The reason for their trip here was to complete missions issued by their respective academies. George and Bessita knew each other well, so the two little teams naturally travelled together.

“We’re in deep trouble. We were actually allocated a defence mission in which we must enter, as well as establish a presence in the Eternal River Plain’s secret plane!” George had a look of prolonged suffering on his face, and when they got to this topic, even Sheira and Bessita looked gloomy.

The secret plane was under the control of official Magi, and a few acolytes like them wouldn’t be able to create a tiny disarray within. They were but cannon fodder, and could die at any time.

Leylin glanced at these people. In this group of five that had temporarily been banded together, George and Bessita were level 3 acolytes, and the other three had reached level 2. In general, their total power was similar to the group of five acolytes that he had destroyed outside the Zither Moon Town.

“Oh, right! How about you, Leylin? Your aura seems pretty strong. You must be a level 3 acolyte, right?”

George seemed to be asking without any intent. Bessita, who was using a straw to drink her beverage, visibly strained to hear his answer.

“I was lucky enough to advance to a level 3 acolyte a few months ago!” Leylin chuckled.

“It’s not easy to advance to a level 3 acolyte! Come! Let us drink to our future as Magi!”

George hid none of his thoughts and yelled, attracting the attention of the surrounding people.

“Cheers!” Six glasses of beer clinked together.

After a bout of drinking, George asked, “Leylin, where are you now? In the Abyssal Bone Forest Academy? Only after entering my academy did I find out that the Abyssal Bone Forest Academy was a dark Magus academy that was at odds with us. It’s even forbidden for us to communicate with them.”

“What? Abyssal Bone Forest?! That Abyssal Bone Forest Academy?”

The moment the words came out of George’s mouth, Lana and Alexander were like kittens who had had their tails stepped on, and jumped in shock.

Sheira didn’t say anything, but the gaze in her eyes was more guarded when looking at Leylin.

“Alright! Alright! Don’t be this tense! Leylin and I are good friends; he is different from other dark Magi…”

Only then did George realise the slip of his tongue, as he stood and awkwardly gave a closure on the topic.

Chapter 197: George and Bessita

Leylin rubbed his nose upon seeing the cautious expressions of the few people around him.

In the Magus world, dark Magi and light Magi were archenemies. And in the Eternal River Plains, which was surrounded by the opposing forces on each side, not attacking after finding out Leylin was a dark Magus showed the immense trust they had in George.

“I left the domain of the dark Magi a few years ago and now live in Nightless City.”

Leylin thought and spoke a half-truth, “I’m currently studying at Four Seasons Garden.”

“See? I knew it! Leylin, you’re brave and honest. How could someone like you be a cruel dark Magus?”

George laughed out gleefully.

Shiera and the others appeared very embarrassed.

The number of Magi that had been killed by Leylin was not public knowledge, but those Magi would have been furious after hearing George’s words.

“Oh, by the way, Leylin, are you going to the secret plane?”

The Eternal River’s secret plane was a major event that triggered an earth-shaking response among the Magi of the south coast. The information regarding the secret plane had spread very quickly, and George and the others were not entirely clueless about it.

Leylin saw George’s anxious look and the other acolytes’ trading gazes, and he immediately understood.

It seemed that George thought Leylin to be one of the acolytes, who were naive and wanted to try their luck within the secret plane.

Of course, this wasn’t surprising since after news about the secret plane spread, acolytes and Magi alike from all over started to convene at this location.

The whole journey was laced with danger. Some died en route, and others would struggle at the entrance and be unable to enter, while others were lured or coerced by the larger powers and became cannon fodder.

There was an extremely small minority of acolytes who would be successful in acquiring some resources from the secret plane and return to Nightless City and other Magi cities. This resulted in a reaction from the magicians in the cities, which in turn incited more acolytes to adventure into the plane.

It was clear that George and the others also considered Leylin to be just like these acolytes.

“Leylin…” George turned silent, seeming to be carefully considering his next words. “The danger inside the secret plane is not something that we acolytes can handle. Only the official Magi, who are the main forces inside the plane, can stay within for long durations of time.”

“Many of my friends suffered inside. You’re still young and need not…”

“Just let him go!” Bessita suddenly spoke up.

“If he’s lucky, he can get some resources and even advance!”

George furrowed his brows. How could one count on such a thing as luck? Bessita was speaking of it too lightly.

“Actually, I was issued a mission by the academy. I have no choice but to go inside the secret plane.” Leylin sardonically stated.

“I see… No wonder then. I warned you only because it doesn’t seem to be in your nature to undertake such a dangerous task.” George patted his close friend’s shoulder in empathy and forced a smile.

“In this situation, we are probably all in the same boat and might even be assigned to the same location. After all, within the secret plane, the light Magi have gathered and created an alliance.”

After hearing that Leylin had been forced to come to the secret plane just like them, Shiera, Alexander, and the others revealed expressions of sympathy. Leylin’s situation was one they could empathise with.

These kinds of missions were usually suicidal by nature. Only those who had no backing or acolytes who had offended important people would be dispatched by their academies to complete these missions.

When he turned, he saw a hint of an expression on Bessita’s face. Something that seemed like… delight?

“Is this girl still brooding over what happened last time?”

Leylin inwardly grinned and actually found this a novelty.

At his current level, he had already left Bessita far in the dust.

Many Magi had died at Leylin’s hands; what trouble could a lowly acolyte cause?

No matter how she bared her fangs and made threatening gestures at Leylin, she was akin to a small kitten playing with him.

“Since we’re all going the same way, how about you join us too, Leylin?”

At this moment, George put forth a proposal.

“Sure!” Leylin gauged that he still had quite a bit of time and, considering the speed at which George and his friends were travelling, he could reach the Eternal River Plain’s secret plane well before the deadline. Thus, he agreed.

His relationship with George was quite good, so he could help out if the need arose.

Besides, there were still some matters that needed to be resolved between him and Bessita.

“Very good. Since Leylin’s a level 3 acolyte as well, our combined battle strength has increased by a lot. Even if we meet a bandit, there’s no need to be afraid.” George seemed very excited.

The other acolytes did not refute him.

“Bandit? You’re actually afraid of bandits?” Leylin asked, rather stunned. In his mind, the so-called bandits were just peasant farmers with grass pitchforks and fishing spears.

“Oh, you don’t know about this?” George seemed to be even more amazed than Leylin. “I can’t believe you came this far when you’re so overwhelming ignorant about the whole situation!”

Immediately, George carefully explained to Leylin, “If it was a bandit group composed of only ordinary humans, then there’s no need for us to worry. Shiera can single-handedly kill all those who come. However, the situation at the Eternal River Plains is different. Due to the number of acolytes travelling there alone, bandit groups that specifically target magicians have appeared. There are even rumours that official Magi are behind these bandit groups.”

Due to large increase in the number of magicians travelling to the Eternal River Plains’ secret plane, the public security in that area was extremely chaotic. Some scattered dark magicians naturally had the idea to fight for the resources.

However, as these dark magicians were mostly acolytes, their strength was inadequate when compared to Leylin.

If they were official Magi, the greedy dark magicians would be unwilling to attack, but if they were mere acolytes, then the they would not be as hesitant. Compared to the light Magi, who had grown in a protected environment like flowers in a greenhouse, acolytes on the dark side who had matured under the law of the jungle were obviously more powerful in battle. With their superior fighting instincts and their manipulation of timing when attacking, they were far more capable than their light acolyte peers.

Most of the acolytes in the area, especially those who were leaving, might be carrying some precious resources from the Eternal River Plains’ secret plane. If bandits ran into any of these acolytes, it would be enough for them to make a fortune!

There were several dark magician acolytes that had these thoughts.

Hence, the way to the Eternal River Plains’ secret plane was full of danger.

Many acolytes who were dreaming of panning for gold usually died before reaching the secret plane.

Leylin thought back to how he had not run into any big bandit groups during his journey.

Occasionally, he had encountered a few inexperienced local thieves that had been dealt with by Number 2 and Number 3.

These two men had already advanced after receiving the incomplete runes of Branded Swordsmen and all ordinary men or acolytes were easily dealt with with a few sword attacks.

“So that’s what’s happening. It seems that I’ve been rather lucky.” Leylin massaged his temples and laughed.

“I can’t help saying this, but man, your luck is too good! However, this has just been the outlying areas. As we continue to travel further into the Eternal River Plains, there will be more of these kinds of bandits. As the light Magi will focus all their energy on the secret plane, some entrances might have a generous amount of warnings placed, but other regions will just be disregarded…”

George had a good grasp of Leylin’s character and knew that this friend of his was not what he seemed to be on the surface. He was sure to have some trump cards.

He wasn’t wrong either, since Leylin knew how to adapt to circumstances and act accordingly.

The stronger Leylin was, the more secure his band of comrades would be. If he continued asking further, it would only result in Leylin being pressured to leave, which did not work well for their situation.

It was but a mere assumption, but since Leylin could advance to a level 3 acolyte so quickly and receive solo missions, that meant he definitely had a great trump card. Poor George didn’t even consider the possibility that Leylin had already advanced to an official Magus.

After all, there was a wide chasm between a level 3 acolyte and the realm of official Magi.

Even if it was the most amazing genius, promoting to the Magus realm before 30 years of age was in itself a most outstanding speed of advancement.

George, who knew that Leylin only had a third-grade aptitude, did not bother considering that all.

“Good! Now that you’re a member of our group, let’s enjoy a toast.” George, as always, was very welcoming and put an arm around Leylin’s shoulder, patting Leylin’s chest with his other arm.

“At least we’re not lacking good wine nor beautiful women. Do you see that red-clothed beauty beside the bar counter? She’s making bedroom eyes at you. If you just go up and speak to her, I bet she’ll she’ll be yours tonight! And then… heh!”

George hadn’t said much and had already reverted to his lecherous nature. Beside him, Shiera’s face changed and the next moment, George let out a sharp scream and begged for forgiveness.

“Haha…”

Seeing this, the acolytes from the Wetland Gardens Academy and Leylin were unable to keep a straight face.

Leylin obviously did not hit on anyone in the end, since George had been joking around to liven up the atmosphere.

The result of this drinking session was surprisingly good. At least, after seeing Leylin produce the insignia of Four Seasons Garden, the relations between Leylin, Alexander and the rest of the acolytes all turned for the better.

Bessita appeared to be very happy to welcome Leylin as their new comrade.

The group rested in the small town for a while, before setting off early in the morning and resuming their journey.

The missions assigned by Ennea Ivory Ring Tower and Wetland Gardens Academy all had time limits. George and the others had to report to a designated area within a stipulated time. If not, they would be labeled as criminals and be on their school’s wanted list.

They were mere acolytes! If something like this were to happen, they would be finished for the rest of their lives!

Hence, after receiving the mission, they could only obey the arrangements of the organisation no matter how unwilling they were. There was little choice but to enter the Eternal River Plains’ secret plane and accept the unknown fate their future held.

Chapter 199: Plant Type-Transfiguration

*Weng!*

The silver white light was extremely thin, and as it sliced at the beast formed from rock, not a single undulation was produced.

*Bang!*

The stone beast suddenly halted in mid-air, and with a gentle booming sound, the beast cracked, and was reduced to fragments of rock that rained down.

“The Wetland Gardens Academy’s ‘Broadsword Jamu’ is indeed formidable!”

The leader chuckled, seeming to be very familiar with Jamu.

“Who in the world are you?” Jamu frowned. Not only did these bandits have acolytes in the group, the bandits’ leader even had a magic artifact and knew so much about him. No matter how he thought about it, this leader wasn’t just any random bandit looking for a target!

He could smell something fishy and quite possibly dangerous going on here.

“Do you really think I’d tell you?” The bandit leader answered nonchalantly. “There should at least be a transmitting spell formation on you. The moment I expose anything about myself, the Wetland Gardens Academy will automatically have a record of it. Am I wrong?”

While he spoke, rays of black light emerged in the area surrounding him.

The black lights converged, forming warriors in armour. Their skulls were jet black.

“These are my darkness fighting troop that I especially prepared for you! Each dark warrior’s might is at at least 15 degrees! How about it? Enjoy the experience!”

Amidst the manic laughter, the black armoured warriors roared and rushed forward, trapping Jamu between them.

Seeing the more than ten dark warriors, Jamu’s face fell.

Although this large magic artifact of his was very powerful, its energy consumption rate was equally enormous. It was obvious that this bandit was intending to use cannon fodder and force him to use up his magic and spiritual force.

No matter how amazing an acolyte was, once his or her magic and spiritual force were depleted, he or she would only be trampled on.

“Kill off the other acolytes. All items will belong to you!”

The black robed bandit leader hid behind the rows of dark warriors to stay protected and pointed towards Leylin and the other acolytes.

“Kill!” His underlings, the dark Magus acolytes, roared and rushed towards Leylin.

“Damn it! Try to prolong the fight. Once Senior Jamu takes care of the opposing leader, we’ll be safe!”

Bessita clenched her teeth and spoke to the acolytes behind her.

At the same time, she glanced towards Leylin’s direction.

“Let’s form an alliance! Otherwise, none of us will be able to survive!”

“Hmph!” George knew her suggestion was reasonable, but couldn’t help but snort in reply.

He wasn’t stupid and naturally knew what had just happened.

He really didn’t want to form an alliance with such a woman.

However, his rational side told him that this was the best way to get out of this difficult situation.

“George!” Sheira cast a worried glance at George. She had already readied her bow, which had been on her shoulder, and positioned it at her front.

“Leylin! Let’s do it!” George saw that the bandits were quickly closing in and unwillingly bellowed.

The muscles on his body bulged bit by bit, and in an instant, he turned into a giant that was more than three metres tall. At the same time, his skin had turned green, matching with the veins on his muscles that looked like connected earthworms. Leylin suddenly thought of the Incredible Hulk, a figure he was familiar with in his previous life.

“Roar!” After transforming into the green giant, George pounded on his naked chest and bellowed out a thundering roar.

He stomped on the ground, and with huge momentum, shot towards the incoming bandits like a lead bullet which had left a gun barrel.

*Pa!*

With a wave of George’s giant palm, a bandit was sent flying. Blood splattered all over, and the sound of bones breaking could be heard. Even the piercing screeches of horror were overshadowed by this grisly sight and sound.

“What amazing power! Besides some flaws in speed and rationality, every other aspect is perfect!” Leylin watched George, who was freely utilizing his might, from a corner, his blue eyes flashing.

He never expected George to have majored in transfiguration!

However, this decision was easy to relate to, as Magi usually held high positions, and prioritised lengthening their lifespan.

For the average magician, advancing to the level of a Magus to gain a longer lifespan was much too difficult. Hence, by transplanting the organs of various powerful creatures and modifying one’s body, one would be able to strengthen and increase his or her vitality. This had gradually become the norm amongst magicians.

The study of transmutation had thus become very popular amongst many.

Strictly speaking, the changes that a Warlock would undergo could actually be considered an extension of transmutation as well. At the very least, they were rather similar at the beginning stages.

Hence, when Leylin was at the Four Seasons Garden, he had concentrated on collecting all knowledge related to transmutation. With the aid of the A.I. Chip, his knowledge in transmutation was at a level close to official Magi who had spent most of their life researching on this subject.

With just a look, Leylin could identify the creature George had used.

“Out of all the plants that can be transfigured, a Green Metal Tree? This is a popular choice amongst acolytes since it’s easy to work with and augments offensive prowess. Its defensive properties are not bad, and there are many ways in which one can advance. There aren’t too many restrictions!”

At this moment, the green giant that George had transformed into was in the center of the battlefield, grabbing an unlucky individual’s thigh. The poor man was used as a huge club and was swung around by George at any bandits who neared him.

This “human weapon” brushed against the ground from time to time, producing traces of bright red bloodstains. From the looks of it, the acolyte that George had caught was in a rather terrible situation.

*Chi! Chi!*

Meanwhile, there were several green arrows being shot by Sheira’s bow from behind George. She covered for George and helped him fend off attackers.

“Hm. They have good rapport!” Leylin nodded, looking incredibly relaxed.

Around him, there was a layer of invisible waves that could manipulate one’s mind. All acolytes who entered the domain he had set up would unconsciously choose to ignore him, and would instead fight amongst themselves.

Such a strange situation had obviously attracted the attentions of many.

“Look at him! The enemies aren’t going after him at all. He has got to be a spy!”

The three acolytes behind Jamu saw this odd situation, and immediately yelled.

“Uhh…” Leylin touched his nose.

His laid back appearance was rather eye catching in this desperate battle.

Before George and the others could react, the winner on the side of the battlefield where Jamu was had been decided.

“You’re forcing me to do this! Burst form! Activate!”

After waving his sword in quick succession, he scattered the bunch of dark acolytes that approached and steeled his mind while looking at the numerous dark warriors around him.

He pressed a few points on his body, as if stimulating some special state.

In a split second, his blue hair exploded strand by strand, and immense energy undulations were emitted from his body.

*Weng Weng!*

The white broadsword in Jamu’s hand also produced a rumble.

“Whirlwind, Second form!” Jamu shouted.

From within the sword, a violent, green hurricane emerged!

The tremendous hurricane shrouded Jamu’s body, and he rapidly spun along with it.

The green hurricane was like a spinning top, with the surface being the edge of the broadsword. Like the wind, it swept through the battlefield, along with the hordes of dark warriors.

*Peng!* *Peng!* *Peng!* *Peng!*

The dark warriors that had been swept up in the green hurricane looked like they were caught by a large, shapeless hand and forced into a vortex. They scattered into countless black pieces that flew about in the air.

The violent hurricane instantly destroyed the dark warriors’ layers of defense and quickly approached the bandit leader.

“Night Devil!”

The bandit leader produced a black ring and yelled, the gaze in his eyes frantic for the very first time.

*Peng!*

Numerous black rays emanated from the ring and formed a large black shield in front of him. There were fine black barbed tips on the surface, with the sheen of a metallic luster.

When the attacks from the hurricane struck against the black shield, a gigantic energy shock wave engulfed the area.

*Boom!*

Along with the loud noise, the explosion left a deep crater on the surface of the ground. An entire layer of the ground had been turned up, exposing plant roots and countless stones.

Even the side of the battlefield that Leylin was on was affected!

Whether it was the bandits or the acolytes near Leylin, everyone was in a pitiful state.

After the blast wave had died down, dust flew all over like a curtain and covered the battlefield.

The two opposing forces stopped all actions, and focused their gazes on the centre of the area.

After a moment, the dust dispersed and revealed the area.

In the middle of the crater, innumerable crevices had split open like cobwebs under the two combatants’ feet. Jamu’s two hands were fixed firmly on his silver white broadsword, pressed against the surface of the black shield.

“Hah! Hah!”

Jamu was panting roughly, beads of sweat rolling down his forehead.

It was obvious that the violent explosion had taken a toll on his physical strength.

“Hehe… I acknowledge your strength, but so what? You’ve probably used up all your spiritual force at this point, no? I wonder how much energy is still left in the reserves of that large sword of yours.”

The bandit leader snickered.

With the sounds of his laughter, the black light from the shield began to suppress the sword.

The strain could be seen on Jamu’s expression as the broadsword was gradually forced backwards by the shield.

“Jamu—Senior Jamu!” The acolytes who had come with Jamu murmured worriedly, their voices breaking.

“Jamu won’t actually lose right? He’s the number 1 genius acolyte of the academy…”

Bessita’s little face had turned pale as she scanned the surroundings.

“Hehe… I’ll bring your head back, hang it in my bedroom, and treat it as my most treasured collection item!” The bandit leader snickered complacently.

“Unfortunately, you’re the one who’s going to lose! Furthermore, I’ll be the one stepping over your body as if I’m stepping over stones!”

Chapter 200: A Dark Magus!

Jamu’s face turned red and he suddenly shouted, “Third Form!”

An instant later, blood oozed from his skin.

The great amount of blood soaked into his clothes, staining it red. His whole body currently looked as if he had just been fished out of an ocean of blood.

With his blood bubbling up, a shocking amount of terrifying spiritual force was also sent out from Jamu’s body suddenly.

The large sword in Jamu’s hand immediately turned a bright red color, and its radiance momentarily grew by several metres.

*Peng!*

The bandit leader’s black metal shield was broken into pieces by the blood-red sword.

Following which, Jamu swung the sword in his hands and aimed a fierce chop at the black-garbed bandit leader.

*Sssii!*

The black-garbed bandit leader was sent flying by the attack, and the black ring-shaped magic artifact on his body shattered into pieces in mid-air. It then turned into fine dust, which drifted off with the wind.

“Good work, Jamu!”

“You truly are worthy of being called Senior Jamu!”

Witnessing this scene, all the other people from the Wetland Gardens Academy immediately began to cheer.

Jamu, on the other hand, immediately turned around with his sword aimed at the remaining bandits.

Apparently, he had planned to dispose of all these enemies in one breath; after all, the third form also placed a heavy burden on him and had other troublesome after effects.

“Jamu is the best…” Bessita said, seeing Jamu’s unusual power. She blushed, stars flashing in her eyes.

“Pieces of trash! You have forced my hand!”

Suddenly, a strange hoarse voice could be heard.

After hearing this voice, the bandits, who had been arrogant up until a moment ago, kneeled down as if they had seen God, their bodies slightly trembling.

Following this voice, a huge black palm appeared in midair and slammed at Jamu, just like someone swatting a housefly.

*Thump!*

The black palm merely swatted, yet the blood-red sword in Jamu’s hand was sent flying. Soon after, a fist struck out. Jamu’s chest caved in, and he spurted out a large amount of blood as he was thrown back.

“An offi…official Magus?”

Lying on the ground, Jamu’s expression was one of incredulity, and then he lost consciousness.

“Official Magus?” Bessita’s expression paled, and she felt limp and collapsed as if the bones in her body had been removed. “We are finished!”

Although they had heard that there was a dark official Magus hiding in one of the many bandit groups, they had not anticipated that they would encounter this particular one.

This was a high and mighty Magus! Would he even put their small group of acolytes in his eyes?

Unfortunately, the reality was cruel, and what one least expected would always happen.

The dark Magus was clothed in a black robe with golden accents, and with a black fog obscured his appearance, he instantly appeared in front of them.

*Awooooo!* George issued a loud howl and faced the dark Magus head-on.

Though powerful, George’s gigantic green form caused side effects such as losing rationality for an indeterminate period randomly. This effect was more obvious when the body was transformed.

He instinctively rushed towards the middle of the battlefield, heading for the dark Magus who was immensely pressuring him.

“George! Don’t!” shouted Shiera, with a look of despair on her face.

“A lowly acolyte dares to attack this mighty Lord Magus?”

The dark Magus sneered. A dangerous green phosphorescent claw from an unknown beast latched onto George.

*Puchi!*

Suddenly, raging black fireballs struck this strange claw.

The raging black fireballs seemed to fill the sky and dyed it a dark black.

This was merely a green claw, and though it tried to persist within the black flame, it was burned to ashes within a few seconds.

“Who was that?” The dark-gowned Magus asked in rage.

“Ai…” was the reply he heard, a soft and gentle sigh.

Immediately, Leylin’s body flashed past in a dark ray of light, appearing in front of George, who had transformed into the green giant.

At this moment, however, there was some drool flowing from one side of George’s mouth—he had completely lost his rationality. Seeing Leylin, he attempted to grab him.

The green giant’s arms had flexible and sturdy muscles, causing violent gales when they moved.

While facing this attack, Leylin calmly extended his right hand.

*Bang!*

The huge fist was directly blocked by the pale, slender palm of Leylin.

At this moment, Leylin’s body was like an infant’s when compared to that of the green giant, but even so, Leylin still resisted the green giant’s full strength attack.

This scene appeared to be all too hilarious, but not a single person present was laughing.

“An offi…official Magus?”

Alexander’s jaws snapped wide open—thus resembling a toad—and he said, “Leylin is an official Magus! My heavens…”

“How foolish were we?” Lana and the other acolytes also were gaping foolishly.

As for Bessita, this woman had basically become paralyzed on the ground—in short, she was unable to say anything!

The only one who looked happy at all was Shiera.

Currently, George was on the ground, bound by many black chains which sprouted from the ground underneath Leylin.

Following which, the transformation of George’s body seemed to be undergoing a change; it began shrinking while emitting steam. He gradually shrunk, and later regained the build of an ordinary man.

“George!” Shiera hurriedly approached and helped remove the black chains from George’s body.

George was in a coma, and his body was involuntarily twitching. He looked terrible; his face still had large patches of green, and his lips had lost their colour.

“Ley…..My Lord, I request that you save him.” Shiera clasped George’s face, a harried look on her own face.

“No need to worry!”

“This is only a biological rejection from the cells of a Green Metal Tree. It is very easy to solve.”

A milky-white beam emitted from Leylin’s palm, which was then irradiated onto George’s face.

When the milky white beam turned into thin white rays that bored through George’s nose and ears, the green patches on his face vanished at a very quick speed. A few seconds later, George assumed a serene expression, like an ordinary sleeping person.

After handling George, Leylin slowly stood up and saw the Magus in the black fog waiting at the side.

“I truly didn’t expect that I would run into an official Magus here.”

The voice of the dark Magus, whose face was wrapped in fog, sounded out. This voice belonged to neither a male nor a female; it was clearly a fake voice.

“I, too, didn’t expect that I would meet a dark Magus while taking a stroll after concealing my identity,” Leylin stated flatly.

Even though he had participated in a lot of raids and other such missions with the Thousands Meddling Hands, that was only for dealing with goals that had a degree of difficulty similar to raiding the Ennea Ivory Ring Tower.

As an official Magus, resorting to being a bandit and robbing acolytes was something he couldn’t do.

It seemed that the dark Magus who was facing Leylin was poverty-stricken. His strength, spiritual force, and the energy waves fluctuating from his body seemed comparatively weak. He must have recently broken through. His spiritual force and elemental essence conversion were also very low.

“In that case, I will give you some face and let them all off!” The dark Magus quickly spoke up.

Due to the lack of benefits, no Magus in their right mind would battle an enemy at the same level as themselves.

“Thanks!”

Leylin replied in a faint voice.

While he was considering that the enemy might go on ahead, the other dark Magus said, “Additionally, I have some exclusive information regarding the Eternal River Plains’ secret plane. Do you want to hear it?”

“News about the Eternal River Plains’ secret plane?” Doubtful, Leylin glanced at this dark Magus, sizing him up.

Based on the enemy’s strength, it would not be possible for him to have gathered any information. When he came across such lucky opportunities, Leylin generally maintained extreme caution.

“Not bad!”

However, Leylin still agreed, wanting to see what this dark Magus was trying to pull.

“You should leave first!”

The Magus in a black robe spoke to the horde of bandits, who were lucky to have survived.

“Yes, my lord!”

All of the bandits present immediately moved around wildly in their fright, and before one could blink, they had already disappeared.

Heavens! They had believed they would be raiding only a group of acolytes, and they did not think that they would unexpectedly find an official Magus within this group.

Moreover, seeing the attitude of their true leader, the other party’s strength must have truly been very terrifying.

If a person like Leylin were to be in a bad mood, killing the bandits would be as difficult as dealing with an ant.

Thus, these bandits helped the fallen acolytes get up, and disappeared like the wind, leaving a mess behind.

“You all wait here for me!”

Leylin saw that after he had spoken, all the acolytes in his group bowed their bodies, including Bessita.

These acolytes had picked up this habit within their academies. Towards a Magus, they were required to show extreme respect and caution. Otherwise, they would be severely punished.

Seeing this scene, Leylin inwardly smiled and immediately left with the black-fog-masked dark Magus.

“Can we speak here?”

After the dark Magus had reached a faraway place, Leylin shouted, making the dark Magus halt.

“Finally, what is the news that you have? If what you say is really valuable, then no matter how many magic crystals or whatever else you want in exchange, I will not be stingy with it…”

“It is not very secure here. I need to bring you to a place where no one will be able to eavesdrop.” The dark Magus began explaining.

“Is that so?” Leylin was suspicious, but he still went along with this dark Magus.

“We’re here now.”

The dark Magus led Leylin to a strange pile of scattered stones

“I set up an isolation spell formation here that will ensure that all we say will stay private, and nobody will be able to listen in on our conversation.”

The Magus, whose face was concealed by dark fog, and could not have his or her gender identified, went straight for the middle of the pile of stones. Leylin, on the other hand, hesitated and stopped in his tracks.

“What’s wrong? Do you not believe me?”

The Magus surrounded by black fog questioned.

Chapter 201: Detonation

“As much as I would like to enter, I would like to first know why I am seeing offensive and restraint runes inside the spell formation. Not even one isolation energy rune is in the formation…”

Blue light flashed in Leylin’s eyes as he stopped in front of the formation and looked at the Magus within the black fog.

“To think that you would still find out after all!”

The Magus in the dark fog smiled wryly, and his voice turned much gentler. It belonged to that of a young woman.

Leylin actually recognised this voice.

“It can’t be helped since I’ve never really swindled anyone before!”

The woman forced a laugh and dispelled the black fog that concealed her.

The fog dispersed, revealing an ordinary female face. Though she wasn’t that pretty, her eyes were extremely gentle and there seemed to be ripples within them, making her unforgettable.

On her chest was a large necklace of gems and pearls strung together, each sparkling with every colour under the sun.

“Jenna?! It’s you?” Leylin immediately recognised the identity of this Magus.

This young lady was the first Magus that he had befriended in the Nightless City, and Leylin’s impression of her at the time was not bad.

However, it seemed like this pure looking young lady was, in fact, hiding something from Leylin.

“We finally meet again, Leylin!”

This young lady, who seemed to come from a large family, smiled brilliantly.

“Let’s not talk about the things of the past. Shouldn’t you first explain the traps laid inside this spell formation?”

Leylin pointed at the spell formation with a solemn expression.

He had been travelling in secret, and even though he had been on alert, he had been followed by this young woman in disguise and did not realise it at all. He had no clue as to what methods she had used to conceal her tracks, and what intentions she harboured.

“Regarding this problem…”

Jenna lowered her head, as if ashamed. “This is…”

In a split second, a multi-coloured burst of light erupted from the necklace around Jenna’s neck, rapidly approaching Leylin.

Leylin, who had always been alert, had previously set up several spell formations on his legs to assist him in moving more quickly. They were quickly activated, and his body turned into several black shadows, that instantly disappeared.

*Rumble!*

Rainbow rays of light enveloped the ground and formed a rune on the floor. Under the light, all plants, and even the soil began to wither.

“Gotcha!” At this scene, a smile appeared on Jenna’s face.

Leylin, who was in the middle of moving, was shocked.

At that moment, a dim spell formation suddenly appeared, and lit up under his feet.

Countless white pillars of light rose, forming a cage that locked Leylin up within.

“Did she plan ahead and set this up beforehand? No! It’s something more powerful than that!”

Inside the cage, Leylin shook his robes, and several fireballs crashed into the cage, the black flames burning fiercely.

However, these pillars of white light were extremely sturdy; the Latent Fireball could only cause the light pillars to tremble. It seemed like much more power was needed to break this spell formation.

A person who was able to lay such a spell formation was not a simple character.

Leylin carefully looked at this female Magus, suddenly feeling that he had underestimated her.

No matter if it was that obvious spell formation trap that was laid as a bait to attract Leylin’s attention, or grasping the right opportunity and making an instantaneous decision to strike, it was not something any ordinary light Magus could do.

This particular prediction of where Leylin was going to land made Leylin even more afraid.

If it was the power of divination, low leveled magicians were helpless against it.

“Why?” Leylin, who was trapped in the white pillared cage, asked.

He’d only seen Jenna a few times before he entered the city. After that, they had limited contact, and no matter how he questioned himself, there wasn’t a reason for them to be in a battle to the death.

“I’m sorry, but you are the catalyst that will bring war and draw fresh blood in the south coast. To protect the peace here, I have no choice but to sacrifice you…”

Beads of tears dripped down her face. Leylin could not determine whether or not they were crocodile tears.

“So just because of some illusory prophecy, you want to get rid of me after thinking that I will bring danger to the south coast?”

Leylin’s face darkened. No matter who it was, after being confronted with such a ridiculous situation, they would also be driven mad.

Leylin had thought of many situations earlier. Was it revenge? For the benefits of an opposing faction? However, he had never even thought of such a possibility being her motive.

However, since it had already been confirmed, what Jenna had cast before was a type of prophecy spell.

“You don’t need to struggle anymore. This is a cage that I prepared especially for you using fragments of the future that I obtained. Not only is it made entirely out of light elemental particles, I’ve also included innumerable high-level spells that are fire resistant. Even with your most powerful attack, it’s impossible to break out of there!”

Jenna suddenly closed her eyes and then quickly opened them; her pupils were white.

“For the sake of world peace, please leave this place!”

Jenna said indifferently, her originally common face unexpectedly radiating a holy feel.

As the words left her mouth, the white pillared cage trapping Leylin began to close in. Countless white threads of light separated from the pillars and enveloped the interior of the cage.

These white threads were like thin silk produced by silkworms, wrapping themselves around Leylin’s body as if they wanted to wrap him in a large cocoon.

“Hehe…”

Leylin paid no heed to the threads surrounding his body and suddenly began to chuckle.

“What are you laughing about? If you have any last wishes, you can tell me. By my reputation as the Guardian family, I promise I’ll help you achieve it!”

Both of Jenna’s arms were placed on her chest, and she made a strange gesture with her hands.

“No need for it! Looking at your hypocrisy makes me want to puke!” A nauseating feeling surged up from within Leylin’s chest.

Back in his previous world, he was already strongly disgusted by things such as world guardians, protectors of the peace, and the like. In the name of righteousness, these groups would sacrifice a person for the sake of the greater good.

After having seen such a scene in the world he now lived in, an intense killing intent, something that he had never felt before, stirred within him.

“There will be a day where the world will understand our methods, and world peace will reign forever!” Jenna did not mind Leylin’s words and instead replied with a maxim.

She then pointed at the cage.

“Purify!”

*Tsssss!* The white rays of light enveloped the entire cage, and Leylin suddenly felt as if he =had been placed in a furnace. He had a strange feeling that he was going to be melted down.

He specialized in dark elemental particles, which were the direct opposite of light elemental particles. He had no idea where Jenna had gotten this spell formation, but its might was incredibly formidable and even Leylin wasn’t able to endure the pain it caused.

“I still have something to say!”

Despite the huge pressure on his body, streams of black smoke coiled around Leylin’s body, which was resisting the corrosion of the white light. This scene made Leylin look quite pitiful.

“Sinner! Speak your last words!”

Jenna advanced slowly.

“I…”

Leylin’s lips moved slightly.

“What? Have the light elemental particles already corroded him to this extent?” Jenna got even closer and pressed her ear to the side of the white pillared cage.

“You slut! You think that this world is operated by your family?”

In a moment, Leylin’s body was covered by fine black scales, and his eyes had an amber vertical pupil resting within.

Leylin bellowed, “Hoop of Imprisonment! Detonate!”

*Boom!*

In an instant, a brilliant silver light exploded from Leylin’s arm.

This metal hoop, which had been resting on Leylin’s left arm, immediately exploded upon Leylin’s command.

The giant shockwave immediately caused part of the cage to burst open. The explosion did not stop there and even extended to where Jenna was.

“Argh!”

Jenna grabbed her face as she was sent flying backwards.

The white thread, which had been restraining Leylin before, immediately exploded. Even the white pillared cage was clearly damaged.

“Eyes of Petrification!”

Leylin’s eyes were focused on the area where the cage was caved in.

*Tssss!* An ashen layer of stone began to spread on the white pillars.

“Latent Fireball!”

Leylin pressed both of his hands together, and large amounts of black flames emerged from the shadows. He pulled his palms apart.

The black flames instantly separated and were evenly distributed on his palms.

“Go!”

Leylin clenched both hands and ferociously struck at the area of the cage that had been petrified.

*Rumble!*

The white light expanded, and in a moment, reached the height of several dozen metres, as if wanting to break through the clouds. After which, it withdrew and was engulfed by the black flames.

As for the heart of the flames, a figure with tattered clothes and fine black scales walked out slowly from it.

[Host’s body has suffered from Light elemental corrosion. It has a restraining effect with the Host’s energy particles, creating a neutralising effect. The damage has increased; currently, 34% of the Host’s skin is burnt. The Host’s left arm has suffered from the explosion of a magic artifact, causing dysfunctionality. Immediate treatment recommended!]

The A.I. Chip’s prompt appeared in front of Leylin.

His current condition wasn’t all that good. Not only were there multiple burns all over his body, his left arm was slanted strangely in front of his chest, revealing a huge wound. One could even see slightly charred bone.

Leylin had brazenly blown up a middle-grade magic artifact, and since he was in a cage, he was the one who had suffered the most. Hence, even with the Fallen Star Pendant and Kemoyin’s Scales’ defensive properties increased to the maximum, he still suffered major injuries.

Chapter 203: Curse

*Boom!*

A green hurricane rapidly advanced towards Jenna and formed a green shield that protected her.

Leylin’s flaming right hand collided with the shield, producing a tremendous noise.

“Uncle- Uncle Manla!” She produced a wide smile.

Along with the loud noise of the wind, a burly, blonde man appeared in front of Leylin.

“Manla?” Leylin recognised this Magus, who had he had previously met once before.

“After receiving your transmission, I rushed over. Thank goodness I made it in time!” Manla stood in front of Jenna, glaring menacingly at Leylin.

“You actually dared to harm my niece to this extent! My family will definitely not…”

*Rumble!*

Before Manla could even finish his sentence, Leylin wasted no time and sent out numerous black fireballs towards him.

From Leylin’s perspective, since they were already enemies, it was natural for him to eradicate them all. Who would bother with listening to what they had to say?

“Be careful, Uncle Manla! He’s very strong and his elemental essence conversion has surpassed 50%!”

While Jenna was yelling out warnings, Leylin was already manipulating latent fireballs to attack Manla’s green hurricane.

Under the attack of the fireballs, which had a might of 51 degrees, Manla was basically forced to retreat step by step.

“So powerful!” An expression of shock appeared on Manla’s face.

Shortly after, like a ghost, Leylin suddenly appeared in front of him, a clawed hand encased in crimson flames grabbing towards his face.

*Pop!*

The sounds of bubbles being burst echoed and the defensive spell on the surface of Manla’s body was easily destroyed in the face of Leylin’s Crimson Palm. It was taken care of so easily, like paper being ripped apart.

Leylin’s palm didn’t stop moving and grabbed ahold of the burly man’s chest.

*Slash!* A bloody piece of flesh was ripped out by the dragging of the claw, and the surrounding skin was left slightly charred.

“This won’t do! The difference in power is too much. If we stay here, we’ll definitely die!”

Manla immediately pulled Jenna up, turned, and ran!

Rationally speaking, Manla was a semi-converted Magus whose elemental essence conversion was at least 50%. In the Magus community on the south coast, he would be considered the cream of the crop. However, he had the misfortune of meeting an evildoer like Leylin, who was much too powerful even when his spiritual force and elemental essence conversion were being suppressed. In terms of hand to hand combat, Manla couldn’t win either.

“Tiwoose Fererian!”

The moment they started to escape, Manla threw out a silver magic scroll.

Nine green tornados formed, and like a wall, they hindered Leylin from giving chase.

“You’re thinking of running?”

Darkness flashed in Leylin’s eyes, and after muttering a few incantations, he pointed forward with his right hand.

Black fog immediately converged to become a black python, which headed for the two of them.

This snake was like an illusion, passing through the green tornados. When it arrived in front of Manla, its crimson eyes were fixed on Jenna, and it bit towards her.

“What the hell is this?”

Manla produced another tornado.

*Hua la!* The black snake ducked and passed through without trouble, and then opened its mouth, viciously biting Jenna’s neck!

Two black pinholes instantly emerged on Jena’s fair neck. They transformed to form a strange, twisted rune.

“Jenna?”

There was a white light surrounding Manla’s hand as he tried to brush the snake away.

However, with a swipe of the python’s tail, it shifted and bit Manla’s arm. The same rune was branded there as well.

After these two attacks, the snake hissed and turned back into the black fog, which entered Manla and Jenna’s bodies.

“This seems to be a curse! It’s going to be troublesome!”

Manla’s face fell. He couldn’t feel anything different from the formation of the curse, but instincts told him that it was going to be inconvenient.

“Jenna, hold on!” Manla yelled crazily, the green hurricanes still spreading. His entire body seemed to turn into a gale, and disappeared into the forest.

Seeing Manla escape in that direction, Leylin did not move.

His body seemed to have shattered like porcelain, with large volumes of blood suddenly gushing out.

“It seems like I can’t endure it any longer, the injuries are too severe.” Leylin was half kneeling on the floor. He suddenly became dizzy, and his vision began to blur.

If possible, he obviously wanted to give chase and kill the two off. However, with his current physical condition, it was impossible for him to continue battling.

“However, the curse that I put up at the end… Hehe… cough, cough.”

Leylin laughed evilly but started to cough violently, spitting out large globs of black blood.

“Light elemental Magi will always be the archenemies of dark elemental Magi. Just a cage made of elemental particles was enough to reduce me to this state…”

Leylin laughed bitterly and his figure quickly turned into black smoke, disappearing into the forest.

Currently, he was in urgent need of a place to treat his injuries.

Although he’d told George and the acolytes to wait for him, Leylin couldn’t even take care of himself, much less the others, so that matter was naturally thrown to the back of his mind.

……

After ten or so hours, in a temporarily set up tent.

In the twilight, an oil lamp illuminated the area a dull yellow. Hay was spread across the floor, and Leylin sat atop of it. In his right hand was a test tube with a potion within, which he was constantly tilting towards the injuries on his left hand.

This test tube was rather large, and in the translucent liquid, one could see something that looked like a baby’s face. It was encased in the liquid, and continuously let off little bubbles.

*Tssssss!*

After the potion was dripped into the wounds, large amounts of white gas were emitted, along with the sounds of corrosion.

“Ugh!” An intense pain struck Leylin’s nerves; he seemed to have been struck by lightning, his muscles involuntarily twitching.

Leylin bit down hard, and large droplets of cold sweat dripped from his forehead.

After that intense wave of pain, his wounds started to get numb.

This numbing effect was very strong, feeling like tens of thousands of ants had crawled and gnawed on his bones. Leylin’s pale face reddened as he sucked in sharply.

At the same time, in the areas where Leylin’s left arm was injured, various veins and muscles squirmed and began to regenerate.

First, the fractures in the bone were completely healed, and the flesh and veins followed soon after. After a few minutes, Leylin tested out his left arm.

At this point, the injuries on his left arm had been completely healed. Leylin’s arm was slender and fair, but under that beautiful appearance, there were muscles that held much explosive power.

It was impossible to tell that this arm had been on the verge of breaking off just minutes prior.

Leylin tested out his left arm again with some actions and smiled in satisfaction.

“I’m lucky there was some liquid left over from the Flourishing Flower! If not, the injuries on this arm wouldn’t have been able to be taken care of so easily.”

The Flourishing Flower was an important ingredient used by Magi in operations to regenerate limbs.

No matter what kind of injury it was, as long as there were enough Flourishing Flowers, it would be very likely that one could recover.

The Flourishing Flower that Leylin was holding was something he had gained during his days as an acolyte. He had exchanged some of them in the Abyssal Bone Forest Academy for incomplete information about the Branded Swordsman.

Excluding the injuries on his arm, Leylin had also used several potions to treat his wounds. He was now able to move freely and fight in less vigorous battles.

“I’ve mostly recovered. I guess it’s time for me to go to the Marat Canyon!”

Leylin was a fairly cautious person. In the secret plane at the Eternal River Plains, it was dangerous beyond belief, to the point that even Magi were considered fodder! As a spy from the Thousand Meddling Hands, if he were ever to be discovered, he would be chased to the ends of the world!

In this situation, if he were to sustain any injuries, Leylin knew that there was little chance of him surviving, much less being lucky enough to reap benefits.

Leylin had already considered leaving and going somewhere else if his injuries couldn’t be treated.

After all, he still valued his own life over making profits.

However, the situation was not so dire. Though he had made enemies with a possibly high ranking Magus family with the abilities of divination, he didn’t think much of it.

“I believe they aren’t feeling very well right about now, yes? My curse won’t be taken apart very easily.”

Leylin smirked icily.

Though he had not been able to kill his opponents, he had successfully cursed Jenna and Manla with a spell that was unique to him.

The formation of this curse originated from a curse in the great Magus Serholm’s Book of Giant Serpent. Leylin had started the foundations of that curse and had made the appropriate changes to it.

After adding in every method he could think of, the curse was so different from the original that even the great Magus Serholm would be unable to undo it.

Like a password, it was complicated and difficult to make sense of.

If one were not the original maker of the password, and instead tried to use brute force to get through, the object protected by the password would be destroyed.

Jenna and Manla seemed to have high standings within their family, and most likely wouldn’t be given up on so easily.

Leylin’s next task was to use the power of the curse to find out who his enemies were.

As he had been followed and almost killed on the basis of some useless prediction, Leylin was quite annoyed.

However, there was still a family backing them, and he did not want to shed all sense of cordiality without making sense of the situation before him.

This was why Leylin had chosen not to chase them and had instead placed a mark on both of them.

Chapter 204: Marat Canyon

Marat Canyon was located at the end of Pome Alley.

It was a barren canyon where the area and economy were both destitute. Apart from several wretched people who lived here in extreme poverty, no other humans would bother with a place like this

However, after the discovery that there was an entrance to a secret plane in this area, everything changed.

Ever since one of the entrances to the Eternal River Plains’ secret plane was discovered here, Magi from every corner began to fight each other over the area.

Eventually, the hunting and battle teams from Four Seasons Garden, with the aid of the white Magi domain, managed to repel the dark Magi forces and claim this land as theirs.

Soon after this, unaffiliated Magi and acolytes set up a market for magic items in the surroundings.

Four Seasons Garden’s higher-ups were well aware this place wasn’t well developed and dispatched people here. They treated this Magus Market as the center of their power and created a little town, welcoming all non-dark Magi.

The first impression Leylin had when walking in this small town was that it had a lively atmosphere.

“Looking for members! All of us are level 3 acolytes! We have a healer!”

“The latest map of the secret plane for only 500 magic crystals!”

“Walking Dragon Flower! Walking Dragon Flower that’s freshly plucked from the Eternal River Plain’s secret plane for 6000 magic crystals! This is a discounted rate!”

“I am looking for a group to join! I’m a level 3 acolyte and have both offensive and defensive skills. I also know three healing rank 0 spells.”

From the entrance of the little town, various stall-keepers, adventurers and official Magi were crowded together, constantly arguing over prices till they were red in the face.

Everyone was at least an acolyte. There were no regular humans.

The whole town was like a busy food market.

After much effort Lelin arrived at Four Seasons Garden’s administrative area, which was located in the middle of the town.

Compared to the chaos outside, it was much quieter inside the administrative area, which had the battle and hunting teams guarding the area.

Leylin couldn’t help but think about the two official Magi he had seen at the entrance to the administration area.

Getting two official Magi to stand guard obviously caused the Magi and acolytes who came here to feel immense pressure.

Numerous Magi were chattering amongst themselves quietly as they walked by Leylin. All of them looked to be in a hurry.

“Welcome! May I know if you’re here to do the entrance procedures? Please provide evidence that you aren’t a dark Magus, and then present 500 magic crystals. You will then have a one-time opportunity to enter!”

Leylin came to a counter, and as soon as the personnel saw him, he quickly spoke very formally, as if he were selling tickets.

In reality, Four Seasons Garden’s higher-ups had actually capitalized on the opportunity to enter the secret plane by selling entry permits.

“I’m not a Magus from anywhere else. I belong to Four Seasons Garden’s Potioneering team and have been transferred here!”

Leylin placed his token of identification on the counter.

“Ah… My apologies, Lord Leylin!”

The personnel took a look at the symbol and name on the token and bowed.

“No worries!” Leylin looked at the several counters that had a long queue behind them and asked indifferently, “Have there been many magicians going in recently?”

“A large amount have come! Once we had allowed non-affiliated magicians to enter, the Magi and acolytes who came forth to register had filled up this area… We even had to request for several of the hunting team Magi to maintain order!”

The staff smiled wryly.

Leylin was aware of this policy.

Before he came here, he had taken a tour around the town and gathered information.

Though Four Seasons Garden had taken over this entrance, the amount of magicians who came here was no small number. If they kept hogging the entrance, it was sure to trigger someone’s dissatisfaction.

It wasn’t much if it was just acolytes, but when there were wandering official Magi involved, the situation wasn’t as easy to deal with.

If there were dark Magi purposely inciting conflict, then this cause a catastrophe!

Hence, the light Magi factions made a temporary agreement to become allies. They decided to open the entrance up to the public.

All entrances that were controlled by light Magi had rules: other than dark Magi, as long as one paid up 500 magic crystals, one would have the right to enter the secret plane!

In addition to this, there was the condition that acolytes had to give up 50% of their earnings within the secret plane to the light Magi powers guarding the entrance. Even official Magi would have a portion of their profits taken away!

Even with these fees, magicians still flocked here.

They unceasingly entered the secret plane and explored the areas without fear of death. There were some with good luck that managed to survive and leave the area with large amounts of resources. This attracted more acolytes to enter and risk their lives in the plane.

While these free labourers were dying by the dozen, Four Seasons Garden was hiding in the shadows and stealing portions of their profits. They were earning a fortune from this, and on top of that, through coercion and purchases, they now had a map of almost a million mu of the plane and received precious information firsthand.

To large light Magi organisations like the Four Seasons Garden, the resources that were currently inside the secret plane was just a small reward. What they really hankered after was the continuous production of resources that the secret plane could provide!

Hence, with the resources as the bait, large organisations such as the Four Seasons Garden were able to attract many magicians with no affiliation to risk their lives and enter the secret plane for the resources. In exchange, they would be able to obtain more information regarding the topography and ecosystem within the secret plane.

As for the unaffiliated magicians, even if they were aware of the manipulations and hidden agendas behind the entrance fees, as long as they walked the path of a Magus they had no choice but to enter this profitable scheme that the white Magi had established. As the saying goes, as one is willing to be hit, one is willing to beat.

Even Leylin had no choice but to approve the deviousness of this shrewd plan.

“I have 2 Grand Knights servants with me, they left for this place before me. Have they arrived yet?”

Leylin asked.

“Please wait a minute, I’ll check for you!” The staff hurriedly flipped through the thick book of records and accounting.

“I found it, it’s only yesterday that your two Grand Knights servants brought your mount and luggage here. Also after showing us your identification token, they were allocated to district D9 no. 23!”

The staff member bowed.

“I will report your arrival as soon I can. Regarding your task allocation, someone else will contact and inform you in detail!”

“En! Great!” Leylin nodded his head. After leaving a secret imprint with the staff as a proof of his arrival, he left the great hall through the back door.

Behind the administration area was rows of orderly wooden houses.

These houses were modelled simply, and the edges were rather rough. They looked as if their construction had been rushed.

Within these wooden houses, one could occasionally see a few Magi and acolytes wearing Four Seasons Garden accessories.

In the middle of these buildings, a huge platinum gate that was tens of metres tall was standing tall proudly like a mountain.

It stood tall there like an ancient existence. On the gate were numerous runes connected together. They seemed to be alive and kept wriggling on the gate frame.

Just the aura from the gate to the secret plane made it difficult for Leylin to breathe.

“Is this the entrance to the Eternal River Plain’s secret plane?” Leylin raised his head and surveyed this gate that seemed to be rising into the heavens, eyes full of unspeakable awe.

The preciousness of a secret plane could be told from its entrance.

Entrances to secrets planes comparable to that of the Spirit Slaying Sect’s plane could be easily destroyed by Leylin. The Gargamel that was as strong as a rank 2 Magus even had the terrifying power to break out of such planes!

However, if it were here, that Gargamel might not be able to even create a crack in the gate to the Eternal River Plain’s secret plane!

With an area of more than ten million mu, its internal structure and defences had to be unimaginably strong. Even if rank 2 or 3 Magi were to battle fiercely, the secret plane would be unaffected.

Leylin guessed that even a rank 4 Morning Star Magus would have a hard time trying to destroy this platinum gate.

Such a secret plane could be said to be a continental treasure! It was something that could help large organisations progress rapidly, or aid someone in taking over the world!

After actually seeing Eternal River Plain’s secret plane, Leylin finally understood how it could attract Magi from all over the south coast and even cause a Magus war.

“Unfortunately, no Magi organisation in the south coast is confident that it can take over the whole plane. As such, the plane has to be divided.”

Leylin sighed and turned his attention to the bottom of the large gate.

At the lower part of the large platinum gate, twenty or so Magi wearing Four Seasons Garden attire were patrolling the area like soldiers.

From these Magi, strong undulations from powerful elemental essence conversions of at least 50% were purposefully released!

Their bloodlust was also very obvious. It was apparent they weren’t idiots who were taking the resources based on luck but were actually seasoned Magi warriors!

Blue light flashed in Leylin’s eyes, and the A.I. Chip immediately scanned the several spell formations that were laid around the entrance of the secret plane. There were some defensive formations, while others were for detecting intruders.

With such tight security, even if it was Leylin who were to try infiltrate inside, he would only end up dying.

“What’s displayed might just be on the superficial level. There would at least be a rank 2 Magus holding fort around here!”

Even outside Four Seasons Garden’s secret plane, there was a rank 2 Magus standing guard outside. Leylin did not think when it came to the Eternal River Plains’ secret plane, the Four Seasons Garden would be reluctant to send a rank 2 Magus as the guardian.

Chapter 209: Optimised and Easy

The red blade collided with the green chains, causing an intense wave of force.

*Crack! Crack!*

The long red blade shattered into pieces, and a part of the chain mail armour on Ciel’s chest broke off. Several green rings had been chopped in half and fallen to the ground.

“You… You’re not any normal Magus who has just advanced!”

Ciel retreated, his expression showing his regret.

Leylin was indifferent as he charged at him.

“Wait… Wait a minute! We can discuss this! I still have many… Argh!”

Although Ciel wanted to say more, Leylin did not give him the chance to do so.

He pursued Ciel and struck again, black scales covering his clenched fist and emitting a glossy black lustre.

The first punch! Ciel’s chest was caved in, and countless green iron rings were shattered.

The second punch! Ciel’s innate defense spell was utterly destroyed. He retreated with his chest caved in and blood dripping from the corner of his lips.

“Do you have any last words?” Leylin expressionlessly approached him.

“M-My mentor will seek revenge for me!” Ciel incessantly said like a broken record.

“Boring!” Leylin prepared his third attack!

*Boom!* Ciel’s brain exploded like a watermelon, white and red liquids mixing together and spreading all over the ground.

The acolyte who had had his face branded was on the floor, staring blankly at the headless corpse that no longer had any life within it. He didn’t even have the presence of mind to wipe off the blood that had splashed on his face.

“I… I… I…”

George gaped and shook Shiera’s arm, “Was that person really a mighty semi-converted Magus? Are you sure he wasn’t an acolyte?”

“Definitely! Just a glare from him could kill us!” Shiera forced a laugh.

“Then… What kind of power must Lord Leylin have to have been able to defeat and even kill him?”

George watched Leylin, who was poking around Ciel’s corpse, with a complicated expression on his face.

“Lo… Lord…”

Only then, the acolyte standing at the side came to his senses.

Just then, there was an arrogant semi converted Magus. How did he just die like that at Lord Leylin’s hands?

“Now, how do we handle the matter of Lyhart’s desertion?”

The deserter acolyte sat mindlessly on the floor like a fool as he unconsciously repeated nonsense. The secret imprint that Ciel had left on him was extremely eye catching.

“There should be an established punishment by the alliance to punish all deserters, right? Do you actually need me to teach you that?”

Leylin shot a glance at the acolyte.

Although it was just a glance, the acolyte immediately retreated several steps, and even his calves turned wobbly.

“N—No, my Lord!”

This newly-turned traitor was tied up by a few others and sent to the fort. The acolytes present all displayed terror and dread on their faces.

“Lyhart’s finished!” an acolyte murmured.

As per the rules and regulations set by the light Magi alliance, all acolytes and Magi who defected to the enemy’s side received the worst punishments.

Lyhart had betrayed them so blatantly in front of Leylin and the many acolytes, and he even had a secret imprint from the opposing Magus. This was irrefutable evidence.

In this situation, death was the easiest way out.

If he had the misfortune to meet a strict judge, at the very least, his spirit would be extracted and tortured for a hundred years. His family and mentor would also have to face some calamities.

“Why are you so distracted? Get to work! Do you want to stay here all day?”

Leylin looked over at the stunned acolytes and exclaimed icily.

“Ah, yes, my lord!”

Only then did the acolytes respond and continue with their harvesting. Not even George and Shiera were spared.

If they did not finish harvesting this patch of Black Mandara Flowers, they would not be allowed to return to the Magus base camp. No matter how powerful Leylin was, he would eventually be pressured by the dark Magus forces.

It might not even take that long. If the enemy was less stressed and decided to focus 0.1% or even 0.01% of their attention on this place, they would be doomed.

Hence, the acolytes worked diligently, hoping they would complete their mission today and leave this damned place.

“Restore!”

At the other end, Leylin was in the middle of the sea of flowers. He drew the black scepter, muttering a single word.

*Weng!*

A ring of whiteness spread from the scepter, and like a thin thread, seeped into the ground.

At the same time, from the bottom of the flowers, the white spell formation appeared once again.

White threads that looked like spiderwebs surged, restoring the areas that had been destroyed by the dark magus.

[Jayle Defense formation—Second form! Defense against physical attacks: 20 degrees. Resistance against magical attacks… Energy in store: 34.9%]

A screen appeared in front of Leylin’s eyes, presenting him with information about the spell formation.

With the help of the A.I. Chip, the restoration works were very successful. A few areas that had been damaged were perfectly repaired by the A.I. Chip simulating and Leylin physically fixing them.

“But the defensive capabilities of this formation are much too weak…”

Leylin stroked his chin, wondering if he should modify this spell formation to increase its defense.

As the Magus who stood guard here, Leylin was able to gain a portion of the Black Mandara Flowers, the ratio was so miserable that he cared little for it.

However, the rate at which the acolytes completed their task was directly related to how soon he would be able to leave. If there were attacks everyday, how would the acolytes harvest the petals?

Hence, Leylin’s first priority was to ensure the safety of the acolytes so they could finish the task as quick as possible.

“I should just wait until it’s late at night and finish it myself!”

Leylin looked at the acolytes who were bending their backs and working like farmers, a gloomy look in his eyes.

It wasn’t that he didn’t trust the acolytes, but he was used to having some trump cards.

He could also come up with methods to increase the rate of harvesting. As long as he increased the rate at which the A.I. Chip operated, and prioritised this task, it would take but a few days.

It was highly possible that by that time, the acolytes would be able to work quicker.

……

In the blink of an eye, about half a month had passed.

In Eternal River Plains’ secret plane, the round disc in the sky began to descend, leaving a shadow on the ground.

The Magi organisation that had constructed this secret plane had used some sort of spell and structured it so that there was a sun, moon, and different seasons.

However, based on Leylin’s hypothesis and the A.I. Chip’s calculations, the sun and moon inside the plane had a hint of the energy of the original celestial bodies, which those ancient Magi were able to project into the secret plane using an unknown method

Leylin was in awe of the ancient Magi’s methods and boldness.

In Teljose City, the humans had made use of the volcano to allow increased production in its vicinity through the use of a spell, and just this had left Leylin agape. However, compared to the ancient Magi who could take the stars, embrace the moon, cause storms with one wave of their hands, and cast rain with another wave of their hands, Leylin had to bow down in inferiority.

“Not only is Lord Leylin a mighty Magus, he actually specialises in the study of plants!”

In the sea of flowers, two acolytes who were nearest to him were in conversation while their hands were busy.

“That’s a given; after all, he is an official Magus! It’s not something we acolytes can compare to.”

The male acolyte who had just spoken had short red hair. At this moment, there was a layer of blue light coating his hands. After rubbing his fingers, several strands of blue thread coiled itself around the Black Mandara Flowers.

*Ka-Cha!* *Ka-Cha!*

The sound of a flower being cut was heard. Following which, the petals of that Black Mandara Flower floated down slowly from its stem and was kept safely by the acolyte, who placed it inside a bag.

“Previously, every petal required a large consumption of magic power and spiritual force to acquire. Even Krall, who was the best amongst us, could only pluck 20 petal pieces in a day! However, ever since Lord Leylin imparted a new method to us, even I can harvest over 40 petals in a single day…”

The red haired acolyte had a look of admiration.

“With this kind of speed, as long as we endure for a couple more days, we will be able to leave this damned place!”

The other acolyte who spoke revealed an obvious hint of longing, “I don’t wish to stay for another day in this place! With so many dark Magi and acolytes coming to attack us each day, we would have died over a hundred times if not for Lord Leylin here!”

*Boom!*

At this moment, the alert from the defense spell formation had sounded. However, these two acolytes seemed to have not heard it at all, as they continued to diligently harvest the petals.

“Say…Who do you think is the unfortunate one today?”

The red haired acolyte asked with some schadenfreude.

“It should be another official Magus. Regular acolytes do not have such large energy wave fluctuations!” The other acolyte creased his brows before stooping down again to pluck more petals.

“Anyways, with Lord Leylin around, what’s there to fear?”

“You’re right!” The red haired acolyte nodded his head and began his day’s chores.

……

At this moment, within the castle’s walls.

In a gloomy, moist, and dark underground prison cell devoid of light, Leylin strode forward, carrying a black clothed figure on his arms.

*Crash!* The cell gate was opened, and Leylin tossed the person he carried into the cell without a care.

*Bang!* As flesh and the hard floor made contact, there was a loud thudding noise.

The person who was previously unconscious was now awake.

Chapter 210: Handover

“You…you dare imprison me!? I swear on my name, Jocelyn Lena, that I definitely won’t let you off!”

This Magus, who was called Jocelyn Lena, donned a black robe. Her hair was curly, and her eyeliner make-up was extremely thick. Dark circles were prominent under her eyes, making it look as if she had not slept in days.

She had numerous bizarre silver piercings on her skin, and she also had a few earrings.

The general impression that she gave was that she was a non-mainstream teenage girl who had taken a wrong step in life.

“Jocelyn, yes?”

Leylin stood by the door, snapping his fingers.

Immediately after, the metal door seemed to have developed a life of its own and automatically closed. Meanwhile, metal chains climbed and locked the cage, and then branded the symbol of a black snake onto the entrance of it.

“I don’t care who you are. As you are a dark Magus attacking us to pilfer the Four Seasons Garden’s resources, I hereby arrest you on the account of attempted robbery. Someone will take you away soon. Once you are at the light Magi’s headquarters, I imagine you’ll have to start thinking of ways to escape your fate of being burned at the stake.”

Leylin said expressionlessly, and then commanded a nearby acolyte, “I’ve temporarily suppressed their abilities, so watch them well till the defense squad takes over!”

“Yes, my lord!” The acolyte bowed deeply.

In these past few days, Leylin had given a little demonstration of his power, and that had been enough to instill fear into these acolytes.

All the dark Magi who had come to provoke them were easily taken care of by Leylin within a few rounds, whether they were acolytes or official Magi.

Just the number of Magi taken captive was enough to fill the fort’s jail to the seams. Leylin had no choice but to notify the defense squad. They worked out a schedule where they would take the prisoners away every few days.

“This power isn’t something that an ordinary Magus could even hope for! This Lord Leylin must be some amazing, important person!” the acolyte roared madly in his heart as he lowered his head.

Leylin cared little about this acolyte’s mental activities, and he cared even less about the female prisoner Magus, who was cursing hysterically. He shook his head and left the underground dungeon.

“Just wait! My uncle absolutely won’t let you off!”

From within the dungeon, Jocelyn was hatefully saying, “My uncle became a semi-converted Magus twenty years ago, and entered the secret plane with me. The moment he finds out what happened to me, he’ll definitely come save me! When that happens, I’ll—”

“That’s enough, Jocelyn! Can you be quiet?”

A helpless voice that held a hint of bitterness sounded from the opposite jail cell.

A curly haired middle-aged man appeared from the shadows and awkwardly greeted Jocelyn.

“Uncle-Uncle Luge, why are you here?”

Jocelyn covered her mouth, completely stunned.

“I was actually captured and brought here three days ago,” The curly-haired man called Luge forced a smile.

“The Magus guard in charge of this fortress, Leylin, seems to have reached the peak of a rank 1 Magus. I felt the terrifying undulations that could only belong to Magi who have reached the top.”

Jocelyn was stunned. The sole person she was counting on had long since been captured, and thinking back to how she had been cursing incessantly, she had looked as foolish as a clown.

……

“These are the Black Mandara Flower’s petals that we gathered today. They have had spells cast on them to ensure their freshness for at least fifteen days.”

Leylin pointed at a pile of materials that had been piled neatly to the side, and then at a few Magi who were in black robes and had their hands and legs cuffed, “These are the dark Magi caught recently. Take them away as well.”

“Yes, my lord!”

The one taking the petals and Dark Magi for Leylin was also an official Magus who was followed by a few team members of the same rank. In front of Leylin, however, he could not help but lower his body and spoke with honorifics.

In the Magus World, whether one was a light or dark Magus, the basic principle was that power was everything.

The team leader was only a semi-converted Magus, and Leylin had passed several dark Magi of that strength to him.

In battle, taking an official Magus captive was obviously much more difficult than simply defeating or killing them.

Hence, after being made aware of Leylin’s abilities, the team leader was unable to treat Leylin condescendingly and looked like he was meeting his boss every time he came.

“Hm! Three are official Magi, of which one is female, and thirteen are acolytes…”

This female Magus was naturally Jocelyn, whose complexion was deadly pale as if she had been dealt a serious blow and did not dare to provoke Leylin.

The team leader quickly recorded this information down and signed his name on a form.

Afterwards, he couldn’t help but greeting him using Magus etiquette.

“Lord Leylin! Your accomplishments in the field have far surpassed mine. Once we return to the main headquarters, your rewards and contribution points will be given to you all at once!”

As it was basically a war in the secret plane, the prisoners that Leylin had taken captive could be turned into merit points.

Not only could merit points be used to exchange for special items that could only be found within the Eternal River Plains’ secret plane from the large light Magi organisations, it could also be used to obtain unique items from other academies.

This included advanced knowledge, improved spell formations, precious potions, and the like.

“Alright!” Leylin nodded.

Based on his estimations, if the merit points he had gained could be converted into magic crystals, he would have least several million. This meant that soon, he could leave this place behind.

As a better method for harvesting had been provided, about half of the Black Mandara Flowers had been picked, and only a relatively small amount was left.

At the rate they were working at, the Black Mandara Flowers would be completely harvested in less than four days. And at that time, Leylin and the others would be able to leave this damned place.

Every time he saw the defense squad coming in fully armed, Leylin was filled with annoyance!

……

As the goods that were to be transported were of extreme importance, the means of transportation provided to the transportation team was the Toucan.

This type of bird had a large body, and when matured, could grow up to ten metres tall.

Its beak drooped downwards, forming a large space that was basically a room that could store many items and even humans!

The team leader split up his team evenly and directed them into the beaks of three Toucans, leaving the best spot for himself. On top of the box full of Black Mandara Flower petals, he began to rest.

At the thought that he was sleeping on top of several million magic crystals, his heart began to burn involuntarily.

If not for the almost abnormal strictness that the light Magi alliance had at the entrance checks, and the fact that it was impossible to smuggle things out, even he might have harboured some terrible thoughts.

It was warm in the Toucan’s beak, and even when it was flying high in the sky, not a current of air came through. It was very comfortable, and as the team leader shut his eyes, he began to fall asleep.

*Crash!*

All of a sudden, the surroundings rocked and several boxes were overturned and fell to the ground.

“What’s happening?”

He exclaimed in shock.

Immediately after, a secret imprint by his ear brightened. “Leader, it’s an enemy attack! It’s the dark Magi!”

The voice of his subordinate travelled from the imprint, and he sounded fearful.

“Those wretched things!” He cursed, and shouted through his secret imprint, “Prepare for landing; all members, get ready for war!”

*Boom!*

Before he had finished speaking, an intense explosion sounded, followed by squawks of pain from the Toucan he was riding in.

Flames swept through in a horizontal line, burning through the Toucan’s tough beak and revealing the blue sky.

*Whooosh!*

Large amounts of cold wind flowed in, and the boxes filled with Black Mandara Flower petals were strewn across the floor.

“Despicable! Land quickly!” The team leader hurriedly yelled.

If he lost these resources, all the blame would be placed on him. How could he not be anxious?

The Toucan was calling weakly.

Finally, as if the flying Toucan could no longer take on any more attacks, its entire body lost balance and fell from the sky like a rock.

*Rumble!*

The Toucan’s huge body smashed into some shrubbery and left a deep indent on the ground. Various little animals revealed themselves and quickly escaped in the opposite direction.

“Pah! Pui! Pui!”

Covered in dirt and grime, the team leader emerged from the Toucan’s beak and attempted to spit out the grass and leaves in his mouth.

“I swear I will learn a flight spell when I go back this time!”

The leader vowed vehemently. It honestly felt terrible to be hurtled through the air.

“Unfortunately, you won’t be getting the chance to do that!”

An ominous voice sounded, and several people in dark Magus attire with green light shining in their eyes surrounded him.

“Oh my! It seems I’m quite popular, eh?”

Looking at this scene, the team leader looked to be extremely dumbfounded, and just stared blankly at the opposing the dark Magi.

“Woofter magic arrows!”

A shrewd light flashed in the leader’s eyes, and his clothes exploded, countless fine needles flying towards the surrounding Magi.

“Go!”

He howled, and streams of lights and shadows flashed, rushing out in all directions to break out of the circle of people around him.

At this moment, he could clearly the state around him.

The Toucans, which served as a mode of transportation, had all been brought down, and were being surrounded by numerous dark Magi!

Chapter 216: Hunting Zone 3

Seeing that Caesar’s spiritual storm had almost torn space apart, the members of the hunting team that were present let out incredulous exclamations.

“I’ve long since heard about how 20 years ago Lord Caesar had reached the criteria to advance to rank 2. However, to pave the way and make his future advancement smoother, he chose to suppress his cultivation.”

A female Magus with gauze that veiled her face mumbled, her eyes revealing adoration for Caesar, “As I thought, our team leader really is the strongest!”

“As expected, he’s powerful!”

Leylin clenched his teeth and a large amount of spiritual force burst out from his sea of consciousness.

At the same time, a blue ray of light flashed in his eyes. “A.I. Chip, estimate the opponent’s power!”

[Beep! Mission established. Beginning information gathering, constructing the simulation model.] The A.I. Chip’s mechanical voice sounded.

Streams of data were rendered in front of Leylin’s eyes, eventually coming to a conclusion.

[Estimation of target’s spiritual force: 79.9. Opted elemental essence for conversion: Death element. Estimated elemental essence conversion: 85-90%.]

“This data means he’s way past the entry requirements to advance to rank 2!”

The conditions for advancing from a rank 1 Magus to a rank 2 Magus were that one’s spiritual force must be at least 80 and that their elemental essence conversion must be at least 80%.

However, many talented Magi did not want to advance right after meeting the bare minimum requirements. They wanted to be in the best condition when they advanced, which would pave the way for their future.

Thus, they voluntarily suppressed their spiritual force, keeping it at the boundary while they increased their elemental essence conversion to at least 90%. Only then would they choose to advance.

The type of Rank 2 Magi who chose to advance this way had a battle power that far exceeded that of their peers. All their future advancements would be easier as well.

Caesar was a talented Magus with this train of thought! Based on strength alone, he was even above the leader of the Potioneering team, Decarte.

However, this was quite normal. Decarte was the leader of the Potioneering team, and instead of battle power, he was more focused on being knowledgeable in Potioneering.

Caesar, on the other hand, was in charge of the Four Seasons Garden’s hunting team, and was thus definitely much stronger than his peers.

Leylin suddenly had a thought and immediately took a look at his stats.

[Leylin Farlier. Rank 1 Warlock. Bloodline: Giant Kemoyin Serpent. Strength: 7.1, Agility: 6.7, Vitality: 8.5, Spiritual force: 58.9, Magic power: 58 (Magic power is in synchronisation with spiritual force). Elemental essence conversion: 70%. Status: Healthy]

“My spiritual force and elemental essence conversion are much too weak compared to his, and he isn’t even using his full strength. If he did, my external spiritual force would have been destroyed long ago!”

Leylin gave a bitter laugh.

Of course, he hadn’t gone all out. His elemental essence conversion and spiritual force had been suppressed by the technique obtained from the old witch, which made it more obvious to the others that he was not a match for this person.

After Caesar had used the Spiritual Eye Technique, Leylin’s spiritual force gradually weakened, causing the attack to come dangerously close to his body.

“Puh!”

Leylin suddenly paled and staggered three steps backwards.

With every step, a deep footprint was seen. White gas seemed to rise around him.

A hint of red appeared in Leylin’s eyes, but it quickly dissipated. He rubbed the blood at the corner of his mouth, and looked at Caesar with an unwillingness to lose.

“Team leader is really amazing!”

In this situation, victory was very obvious. The female Magus from before cheered loudly.

“Shut it!” Caesar glared, and the female Magus kept quiet, feeling wronged.

*Pak pak!* Caesar clapped his hands expressionlessly.

After that, two rows of acolytes in formal attire came to the hall.

Facing the mess in front of them, there was no sign of confusion or astonishment as they quickly restrained their emotions.

Multi-coloured rays from magic spells lit up the area, and the level 3 acolytes even used rank zero magic spells to speed up the rate of cleaning up.

Minutes later, the hall looked as good as new. Even the long table had been replaced, and all types of steaming and tempting delicacies were once more displayed on the table.

“So? What’s your answer, Magus Leylin?”

Caesar watched Leylin, who looked gloomy.

“Since that is what team leader wants, I have no choice but to obey!” Leylin answered unwillingly.

“Very good!”

Caesar nodded. “Well then, everyone! Let us raise our glasses to Leylin’s future contributions!”

*Clink!* Numerous wine glasses touched together, producing bright, pleasant sounds.

……

“My lord! The area that we are in charge of, Hunting Zone 3, spans from the green highlands there to the region of dried up marshes. Here, the Eternal River Plains’ secret plane does not yield much, save for a type of Fantasy Spring Water, which is in high demand by Magi from both sides.”

An old Magus from the hunting team with traces of white hair brought Leylin around, patrolling the area.

The areas the hunting team were in charge of greatly differed from areas which had been officially conquered. They were at the border where many opposing powers were, and it was hardly strange to see enemy Magi around.

Thus, these few hunting areas were those where the most fights occurred within the secret plane.

Every day, there were many acolytes and even official Magi who died at the hands of the enemy, turning into mere merit points on the enemy’s part.

“Abyssal Bone Forest Academy’s acolytes? It’s really been a long time since I last saw them!”

Leylin was on high ground as he mumbled, gazing into the distance.

At that moment, his past life within Abyssal Bone Forest Academy along with each and every person there seemed to be fresh memories.

“Anyway, Professor Kroft is only a Potion Master, so it’s unlikely he will be sent to the battlefield. If he’s offended someone recently, that would be another story altogether.”

Leylin thought for a while— the only people he would meet on the battlefield were the official Magi from Abyssal Bone Forest Academy.

Out of the professors in the academy, he was only familiar with a few such as Dorotte and Kroft.

Even if he killed a few of the others, he wouldn’t have a guilty conscience since he didn’t know them anyway.

He even had hopes of running into some of the people from the Lilytell family! He clearly carried a grudge from being chased by them previously.

“Vice team leader! We have tarried here for more than 15 minutes! This is the boundary, and if we continue onwards, it’s possible that the enemy’s scouts will detect our energy waves and besiege us.”

The patrolling magician who was guiding Leylin bowed and reminded him.

In Hunting Zone 3, the vice leader Leylin was deserving of the title of being a local tyrant.

After all, he had sufficient strength, was the highest ranking person that was from Four Seasons Garden, and he was the boss of these hunting team members. This was very terrifying.

If Leylin found any Magus an eyesore, it was entirely within his right to send them to their deaths by commanding them to enter the enemy’s territory.

If they wanted to resist, Leylin could kill them on the basis of them defying orders.

Thus, now that their lives were in Leylin’s hands, things such as pride and honour would be long forgotten.

Leylin, who had been sent here, subdued these few Magi with a few moves.

“Got it, Old Man!” Leylin replied, indifferently.

Most of the members of the hunting team had nicknames, and this Magus who was next to Leylin went by the nickname of ‘Old Man’.

“Since the Lilytell family lost the competition to be the dean of Abyssal Bone Forest Academy, it implies that their strength definitely does not exceed that of a rank 2 Magus. Who knows, they might not even have a rank 2 Magus.”

Leylin quickly calculated the strength of the Lilytell Family.

“The grandfather of Bosain, whom I killed back then, was a powerful elder in the Lilytell Family at the peak of rank 1. He was probably a little weaker than Caesar and had about the same level of strength as Decarte.”

Leylin’s blue eyes flashed as he silently commanded, “A.I. Chip! Using the data gathered previously about Caesar, set up a simulation model and calculate my chances of winning in a fight against Caesar….”

[Beep! Mission established. Beginning data transfer, simulating a human form!]

The A.I. Chip faithfully pinged.

“Let’s go!” Leylin said to Old Man, who was standing at the side and heaved a sigh of relief as they quickly left the area.

As he moved, streams of data flickered in front of Leylin rapidly.

With Leylin’s mental power, it was very easy to multitask.

Moments later, the A.I. Chip came up with the results.

[Battle results: Number 2 and 3 will detonate themselves and die. Host and Caesar will die together. Probability: 89.7%.]

“What’s happening? Show me specific images!”

Leylin was shocked. The conditions that he set included what he would do if he went all out, setting up traps and adding in surprise attacks from Number 2 and 3, who were Branded Swordsmen. Even with these conditions, the outcome was not in his favour, which was entirely beyond his expectations.

*Weng!*

A faint blue screen, similar to a three dimensional display, appeared before Leylin’s eyes and showed an image.

In the scene, Leylin managed to launch a surprise attack when Caesar was distracted, dealing great damage to his opponent. Caesar then turned back in surprise and anger, and fought Leylin.

Two figures flickered across the screen. What shocked Leylin was how strong Caesar’s body was.

As they fought desperately for a few minutes, Caesar used his secret technique once again and healed most of his injuries.

At this moment, Leylin had also revealed his hidden cards: Number 2 and 3.

Number 2 and 3 roared and the brands on their bodies lit up, drowning Caesar in violent flames that shot out of their long swords.

The third eye on Caesar’s forehead blinked open, exposing a black, defensive ray of light that completely suppressed the two Branded Swordsmen’s attack.

From that eye, there also seemed to be a white light that had high offensive power against one’s spirit.

At the end, Leylin could was left with no choice but to order Number 2 and Number 3 to detonate themselves, thereby destroying Caesar’s third eye.

However, Caesar laughed crazily and split his body into two other figures. The three bodies stood at different areas, dragging Leylin with them as they exploded simultaneously.

Chapter 217: Black Smog

“Three spirits in one body! I never expected to see Magi still practicing this ancient technique, and actually succeed!”

Leylin’s expression showed his shock.

However, from the simulation from the A.I. Chip, Leylin now had a better idea of the level of his strength.

Currently, Leylin could be said to be at the peak of rank 1, where dealing with a semi-converted Magus was as easy as chopping vegetables.

However, if he were to compare himself to genius Magi—such as Caesar—who had already met the requirements to advance, he was still weaker.

Fortunately, Magi like Caesar weren’t common on the south coast.

His mortal enemy, the elder of the Lilytell family, was a little weaker than Caesar.

With Leylin’s current skills, if he were to fight him one on one without any tricks, he was not a match for Caesar.

This was to be expected though, since it had not been too long since Leylin had become an official Magus. Most Magi would still be new and inexperienced.

It was already an achievement for Leylin to possess this level of strength.

“As long as I endure for a while more and wait until my spiritual force and elemental essence conversion reach the ultimate degree that can be achieved by a rank 1 Magus. Then, with the added bonus from my Warlock bloodline, I will definitely be able to defeat and maybe even kill him…”

Leylin calculated inwardly, his eyes flashing with dark light.

This sight caused the old geezer beside him to tremble in trepidation.

*Boom! Boom!*

A severe seismic wave came from the ground.

A crack appeared, and a gush of tempting, fragrant and milky white spring water burst out from the ground.

The mysterious aroma pervaded the air, and the plants in the area rapidly grew, seeming to have received some nourishment.

“Squeak squeak…” An earthen yellow mole scuttled from the grass and it opened its intelligent eyes wide, observing its surroundings. It dashed to the side of the water, and began to drink in huge gulps.

*Boom! Boom!*

Heavy footsteps sounded and gradually increased in number, announcing a horde of animals.

There were regular animals such as wolves, cheetahs, and pythons, but they were nothing compared to the number of strange, bizarre-looking creatures that were there as well.

There were some whose upper half was human, while the other half consisted of the legs of a spider, and there were others that were as huge as mountains. More than all of these creatures, however, the thing that caused the most fear was the black smog at the heart of the wave.

This black smog spanned across a large area, and there were multiple tendrils of smoke at the edges that kept extending outwards like tentacles. Regardless of whether they were tigers, cheetahs, half-spiders, or double-headed snakes, all animals that got close would be silently consumed by the smog.

After it passed through, all that was left was a pile of white bones.

Even though there was a temptingly strong life force energy radiating from the milky white spring water, the animals all made the same decision to stay far away from the black smog. There was a deliberate amount of space left between the animals and the black smog.

They came to the side of the spring and competed desperately to have the chance to drink the spring water. Just the black smog alone had taken up a lot of space.

The sounds of furious roaring and the tearing apart of meat sounded out!

A bloody battle for the chance to drink the water started at the mouth of the spring.

Of course, these bizarre animals headed in the opposite direction of the black smog, and the mole from earlier had long since disappeared.

More than a few kilometers away, a group of Magi wearing the uniform of the Abyssal Bone Forest Academy were advancing.

In the middle was a Magus who had countless plants that seemed like tentacles hanging all over his body and embedded straight into the ground.

All of a sudden, a Magus halted his footsteps and began to grin.

“What’s up, Blake? Did you discover anything?”

The leader of the team questioned the scouting Magus called Blake.

“Yes! In that direction, about 7 kilometers away, I sensed dense life force energy waves, and I could feel the energy veins pulsing through the earth… It was at the mouth of a newly-formed fantasy spring. There are also multiple weak traces of life, which probably belong to the animals nearby that were attracted there.”

Blake spoke with conviction, pointing in the direction of the spring.

“Good! Let’s get there, lest those darned bastards drink up the entire spring!”

The Magus leader was extremely pleased. Discovering the fantasy spring was a substantial contribution!

“But…” Blake was obviously hesitant. “Within all those traces of life, there seems to be a large fellow…”

“Who cares? Do you mean it can resist with 5 official Magi joining hands to attack?”

One of the members in the group immediately exclaimed, “Then what are we waiting for?”

The entire group immediately set off in the direction Blake had pointed out, and Blake could only smile wryly, knowing that nobody would listen to what he had to say. Also, just as his teammate had said, there was nothing that could stop them… Unless they met a Magus from the Four Seasons Garden!

Once the Magi group reached the mouth of the fantasy spring, they saw many animals scrambling for the spring water.

“No! How dare these lowly, wretched bastards drink my fantasy springwater!”

As he watched the water level drop, the leader was on the verge of going crazy. “This is a high-level lifeforce spring water that sells for over a hundred magic crystals per gallon! It’s also a necessary item when brewing potions. Quick! What are you still doing there? Kill all of these bastards!”

Two ice blades emitting coldness appeared in the Magi’s hands, his expression complicated as if he bore a grudge.

Though the spring would be saved like this, and would become a possession of the Abyssal Bone Forest Academy, only a small portion of contribution points would be given to him!

“Team leader, look at that!”

Blake dragged the leader by his clothes, pointing at the black smog.

“The devilish black smog! Shit! It being so large must mean that it’s already an adult!” The leader could feel a headache coming on.

The devilish black smog was a high energy being in the Magus world.

They were born without a form and were just made of black smog. They did not move quickly, but it was because of this that spells were less effective against them, and their defensive abilities were more impressive.

The most pressing issue was the fact that this devilish black smog had already matured.

It was a large possibility that a matured devilish black smog has awoken their ethereal skill. Even official Magi might have trouble killing or chasing it away.

“Whatever! The good thing is that this type of devilish black smog has high defense, but relatively weak attacks, so the only thing to be careful of is to not let its tentacles touch you!”

The leader pointed at two members. “You two will follow me and release long range spells, and hopefully draw the devilish black smog away. The others will chase away the animals because every second they are still here means we lose thousands of magic crystals.”

The Magus leader seemed to be respected in the group, and his arrangements did make sense. Soon after, the Magi split up.

“Drilling Frost!”

“Fireball!”

“Globule of Secondary Energy!”

Spells at the energy levels of an official Magi were let out by the three Magi. Ice bolts, fireballs and multi-coloured balls of energy flew out towards the devilish black smog beside the spring.

The spells distorted the air as they streaked across the sky, leaving behind traces of energy waves.

“Wa… wa…”

The devilish black smog made sounds like that of a child crying as the black smog on its body dispersed. It then became more transparent.

The ice bolts, fireballs, and globules of secondary energy went through the black smog, but it did not cause any significant effect.

The entire body of the black smog became a little more transparent, yet it drank from the spring in huge gulps, as if nothing had happened.

“Physical attacks don’t work, which means this devilish black smog definitely has awakened its ethereal ability! Use vaporisation or area of effect attacks that are made up of pure energy!”

The leader was a veteran, and immediately analyzed the current growth stage of the smog.

“Ice fog!”

He first produced a large amount of white fog, in which were ice shards and beads, which quickly moved in the direction of the devilish black smog.

“Support me!” The leader howled.

Immediately after, the two other group members got to work. One released a green hurricane that hastened the speed of the ice fog, while the other constantly set up defenses in front of the group.

With the help of the green tornado, the icy fog moved extremely quickly and immediately reached and stopped at the devilish black smog.”

*Tss tss*

The sound of cold water freezing was heard as the ice fog collided with the black smog. The black smog all around the area started moving even slower.

“Whoa!” The roars of the devilish black smog continuously sounded, this time, filled with pain.

“Chi chi!” The black smog churned and revealed two huge yellow pupils, staring directly in the leader’s direction.

“I’ve already made it angry, so be careful!” Upon seeing the smog’s reaction, he began to yell.

*Chi chi!* With the strange sounds from the smog, two large portions of black smog were vomited out like a bomb, and rushed towards the three Magi!

“Shield of Gaia!” The only member in charge of setting up defenses went forward, pressing his finger to the ground in front of her.

*Rumble*

A layer of large granite rock rose up from the ground, taking the shape of a shield and defending the Magi behind it.

The black smog bomb collided with the large granite shield, producing an explosive bang.

*Pa pa!*

The surroundings seemed to be a mess—rock and mud were splattered in all four directions, and a crater was also created at the epicenter of the collision.

Chapter 219: Total Captivity

As he watched the enemy Magus in charge of defense, Leylin raised his right hand and tapped.

*Weng!*

Countless black figures emerged from the shadows, overlapping with each other as they continuously multiplied. With the accumulation of the shadows, a small light appeared in front of his finger that formed a small-scale vortex that seemed to be able to suck one’s spirit in.

In front of Leylin, a layer of greenish-gray iron covering instantly appeared on that Magus’ skin.

This was ‘Iron Skin’, an innate earth element solidification spell that rank 1 Magi liked to use.

*Ripple!*

Leylin’s finger seemed to be moving extremely slowly, though in actuality it was approaching very quickly. As he tapped the Magus’ Iron Skin, the sound of rippling water could be heard.

In front of Leylin’s finger, the Magus’ Iron Skin peeled off bit by bit like snakeskin. A look of incredulity appeared on the Magus’ face, and after having been quickly tapped on the forehead by Leylin, his eyes rolled back and he fainted.

“Laura?!” The team leader was furious.

Shortly afterwards, a scroll appeared in his hands and Blake, who was to one side of the leader, produced a small shield the size of a palm.

Immense energy waves were emitted from these two items, indicating that they were ready to be activated at any moment.

“You two can attack me together!”

Facing this sight, Leylin simply smiled and clawed with both hands.

*Tssss!*

Black streams of air were emitted from his fingers, and each of the ten black streams was like little snakes as they surrounded these two Magi.

Where the two Magi had previously stood, two black cocoons could now be seen. From these cocoons, the occasional snake-like hisses could be heard.

Seconds later, the black mist dissipated, leaving behind two Magi that had fainted on the floor.

There was a layer of vague imprints that were like black snakes wandering back and forth across their faces.

*Pak!*

After taking care of these three Magi, Leylin willed the shadow vines obstructing the sky to withdraw back into his shadow.

“I feel it now! With the constant stimulation from my bloodline, my control over the darkness is becoming increasingly stronger!”

The darkness in Leylin’s pupils became deeper, and he appeared to be intoxicated while deep in thought as he mumbled to himself.

After handling these three Magi prisoners, Leylin waited another few minutes.

*Zoom!*

Two unidentifiable human figures were flying across the ground, dashing towards Leylin rapidly. Even Leylin was only able to see after-images.

*Thud!*

The two black figures were carrying something on their shoulders and came to Leylin, throwing the things on their backs onto the floor.

“Master!” Number 2 and Number 3 knelt on one leg, greeting him.

“In accordance with your orders, we have caught all of them. None have escaped!”

The two Magi that had escaped just now were currently lying on the ground.

Several injuries that were so deep that bone could be seen on the bodies of the Magi. They were extremely pale, which was a result of extreme blood loss. It was not difficult to imagine that these wounds were the result of a fierce battle.

“Good! You did well!” Leylin expressed his approval towards his subordinates.

These two Magi were newly advanced, and thus the weakest amongst the Magi. Numbers 2 and 3 were able to defeat them because of the immense power of Branded Swordsmen, a subdivision of the ancient Magi.

Perhaps, this was the obvious result of the large consumption of potential and vitality from Number 2 and Number 3.

To obtain power, Leylin had no choice but to speed things up and carry out many taboo methods on their bodies. This allowed them to break through their limits and become Branded Swordsmen in a short period of time.

Because of this, their vitality was being consumed at a faster rate. Based on the A.I. Chip’s calculations, they only had two more months to live.

“Bring them along. Let’s go!” Leylin heaved a sigh of relief as he pointed at the five Abyssal Bone Forest Academy Magi lying on the ground.

He still had many questions that could only be answered by these people.

In addition, it was no simple task to obtain official Magi slaves and guinea pigs.

Leylin still had many ideas and conjectures regarding Branded Swordsmen, and he needed to test it on these Magi.

After all, in ancient times, Branded Swordsmen were a subdivision of the official Magi, not Knights!

Hence, with Grand Knights as guinea pigs, Leylin still felt he was lacking something even with the help of the A.I. Chip. In the end, all he produced was Numbers 2 and 3, who were incomplete versions of the Branded Swordsman.

This could be due to their lack of the tremendous spiritual force that Magi possessed, which resulted in Number 2 and 3’s difficulty in manipulating the elemental particles in the air. It was several times more difficult than predicted by the A.I. Chip.

Leylin considered some scenarios and then brought the five Magi to a secure hidden area. After interrogating them, he immediately began to verify his doubts regarding Branded Swordsmen.

Leylin only dared to be so unscrupulous because this was a time of war and he was doing this to those from the enemy camp.

If not, using official Magi as guinea pigs would most certainly result in society’s displeasure, and he would receive negative repercussions.

……

On a high ground filled with white flowers.

In the thick fog, a large castle that looked like an upside-down cone existed.

This castle only had one point that was connected to the ground, and yet it was able to support the main body of the castle on top. Looking at it gave one the misconception that the world was upside down.

It seemed like this castle was normally upright, but someone had turned it upside down.

In the walkway paved with white marble, an old woman with a head of silver hair was carrying an oil lamp, ambling slowly.

*Ka-cha!* A metal door with blue electric currents sparking on the surface was pushed forward.

*Tssss!* Large amounts of icy white gas began to condense as they came into contact with the outside. It filled the walkway behind her with a layer of white frost.

The old lady walked in the house, which was practically a world of ice and snow. It was below 0 degrees, and if one were a regular human, it would be impossible for them to stay here for more than a few seconds.

In the heart of the house, tendrils of white vapour constantly emanated from two ice coffins.

Through the translucent coffins, one could see a burly man in one, and a girl lying quietly in the other.

Both of them had their eyes tightly shut, a look of pain and signs of struggle flashing across their faces occasionally. Each had a rune with a snake wriggling about on their neck and right hand.

“Sorry for the trouble, Doctor Hyder!”

The old woman got out of the way, and a Magus with a head of silver hair came from behind her.

This Magus looked to be very old, with wrinkle after wrinkle heaping on his face. However, his eyes were bright and he had a benevolent smile on his face.

“Curses are a very troublesome part of spells. They involve many strange and cruel things and Magi in the south coast who know this type of magic are scarce. I can’t guarantee anything other than that I’ll try my best.”

Hyder, a Magus specializing in healing, did not immediately approach the patients, but first spoke to the old woman.

“You are an expert in this field. If you are unable to solve this problem, then I don’t even know who I should approach.”

She gave a bitter laugh.

“Alright! I’ll give it my all!” Hyder nodded. Usually, he definitely would not take on such jobs. Not only were they dangerous, it was easy to offend the Magus who had produced the curse.

However, he was on good terms with this family and owed them a few favours. Hence, he had no choice but to come.

Hyder went forward and looked the ice coffins up and down, and then nodded.

“When unable to treat a condition, freezing the victim is a very good method!”

He shifted his focus past the layer of ice, and upon seeing the curse runes within, he gasped.

Hyder’s expression immediately became serious, and a stifling atmosphere pervaded the air.

He produced several bizarre items from his clothes, which seemed to be useful in testing the nature and effects of the curse.

The old woman behind him stood behind him in bated breath, not daring to even speak a word.

A good while later, Hyder put down the stethoscope in his hands and rubbed off the cold sweat on his forehead.

“How is it?” She immediately inquired.

“It’s troublesome! No, it’s extremely troublesome!” Hyder looked abnormally solemn.

“From this rune I felt an ancient aura. It’s possible that this was a curse passed on from ancient times, and there are basically no other models of it to be found on the south coast. Furthermore, this technique is very complicated and without large amounts of experimentation, trying to treat it at this point will only result in the curse going berserk in the body. The end result is something none of us want to see…”

Now, after seeing how demanding and crafty this curse was, even Hyder regretted his decision. Was it worth it to repay a favour and, in turn, offend a terrifying dark Magus?

“An ancient curse… hss…” the old lady gasped.

As a family with a long history, she naturally understood the difficulty in dealing with this curse.

Forcefully breaking the curse would only result in death, unless the Magus who had set the curse decided to stop pursuing the matter.

“Are there no other methods?” With a hopeful glint in her eyes, she stared at Hyder.

“It would be best to make a trade with the Magus who set the curse. Other than that, I would need large amounts of guinea pigs and practical tests to find a way and break the curse.”

Hyder slanted his head and thought for a moment, before speaking.

“Also, there is a time limit for the curse. Based on my test, there is at most one more month before it will completely erupt!” Hyder dropped another bomb on her.

Upon hearing this, the old lady trembled and then she breathed in deeply, a resolute look on her face.

“It doesn’t matter what happens to Manla, but nothing can happen to Jenna! That is my final threshold!”

Chapter 220: Acolyte

“Huh?”

Hyder looked at the old woman, a little confused.

“What I’m trying to say is… Rather than guinea pigs, the results would be better if you could do tests on a Magus who has also been cursed. Am I wrong?” The old woman looked cold and indifferent as if she was a block of ice.

“Theoretically speaking, that’s true, and it would be even better if it’s an official Magus…” Hyder unconsciously muttered to himself, and suddenly came to a realisation. “You’re thinking of using Manla?”

Hyder could not hide his shock at her words. Though this lady’s family had a long history, official Magi were few and far between. There were not more than 5 of them; this act would sacrifice a fifth of their power!

“If that’s what fate dictates, then so be it!” The old woman looked to be in a trance as she gazed at Jenna, who was in a deep sleep within the ice coffin. “She is the seer and nothing can be allowed to happen to her!”

“The seer? No wonder!” Hyder repeated after her. He had also heard about the family’s strange ability to foresee the future.

“Kill him! The traitor that goes against fate!” At this moment, Jenna suddenly opened her eyes, revealing the whites of her eyes as she spoke expressionlessly.

“Those who offend the seer will have their spirits cast into a bottomless hellhole with black flames, and receive endless torture. Hehehe…” All of a sudden, Jenna’s expression changed, and she began to laugh crazily.

Next, the whites of her eyes disappeared, and a look of suffering appeared. She looked to be on the verge of tearing as she stared in the direction of the old woman. “Grandmother…”

This expression quickly dissipated, and the colour of her face changed. Several images appeared, forming different faces.

“Hsss…” As if stimulated, the black snake runes on her pale neck began to extend.

Lines of black veins instantly crawled all over Jenna’s face.

“This is bad!” Hyder immediately went forward, pouring a bottle of blue liquid into her mouth.

*Ka-cha! Ka-cha!* On the surface of Jenna’s body, countless shards of blue ice appeared, causing her body to freeze.

“Sleep!” Hyder spoke slowly; the expression in his eyes was hard to make out and was somewhat intimidating.

Blue threads from his fingers went deep into her body.

After a long period of time, Jenna finally went back to sleep, and the snake curse returned to its original shape, though it looked a little bigger than before.

“A fractured spirit! Or no, is this the fusion of spirits? How pitiful…”

After all that work, Hyder began to look at Jenna with pity in his eyes.

As a healing Magus who was friendly with this family, he knew about the divination ability they possessed.

This strange ability came from an incomplete high-grade meditation technique.

All who cultivated in this meditation technique would automatically gain the ability to receive premonitions of the future to some extent. As they progressed and cultivated further, they would even be able to observe fragments of the future.

Unfortunately, this incomplete high-grade meditation technique had stringent limitations, and only the female members of Jenna’s family were able to cultivate in it.

In addition, within each generation, only one member would succeed in it and gain the power to predict the future.

These people were called the ‘seers’!

If that was all, the situation would be manageable. However, with the passing down of this technique, a more scary phenomenon appeared.

The spirits of the seer through the years were somehow preserved, and they would possess the body of the current seer.

Hence, with the accumulation of more and more spirits, the seer’s mind would become mentally unstable, and she would become schizophrenic.

Hyder had previously accepted the task of producing potions that could stabilise the mental state or spirit of the seer.

The current Jenna looked like a single person, but within her body resided the spirits of the past seer.

With the increase of spirits within her body, Jenna’s mental health and rationality became frail, and there came a point where she did not even know what she was doing. The spirits of the seers from previous generations would even occasionally take over her body.

As a result, she would do some strange things that were unthinkable to the regular person.

Hyder was very much aware that after gaining this ability, Jenna’s family had become a little neurotic.

Not only did they say that pretty much everything they did was in the name of the protector, and were unwilling to accept any criticism, but they were also used to saying nonsense like “following what fate had in store for them.”

As this continued to happen, several families that had previously been on good terms with them distanced themselves.

After all, Magi were a bunch of rational and free people. Nobody wanted to be with someone who would constantly criticise their actions.

What had once been a large clan inevitably fell. Just looking for some external help was difficult, and they could only find a sole healing Magus—Hyder.

”How is she?” The old woman inquired worriedly, though she pointedly ignored Manla at the side.

Hyder sighed, feeling pity for Manla.

“Though I was able to temporarily suppress the outbreak of the curse, Miss Jenna’s unstable mental condition means that the outbreak can recur at any time!”

Hyder gave the old woman a long, meaningful look. “Also, with that outbreak just now, the date which the curse on her body will completely erupt has been brought closer.”

……

Leylin knew nothing about what was happening.

It was just the opposite. He was surprised that he hadn’t heard anything about Jenna’s family trying to find him through other organisations.

From the looks of it, Jenna’s speech about being on good terms with large white Magi organisations was just a ploy to scare him in a life or death situation.

Though Leylin had made some preparations, the feeling of having made preparations but there being no signs of attacks directed at him left him feeling a little dejected.

“But the time limit that I set is approaching! They will definitely look for me soon!”

The corners of Leylin’s mouth curved into a cold smile.

His curse came from the rank 4 Morning Star Magus, the great Magus Serholm. With the A.I. Chip’s simulation and encryption methods, it was basically impossible for anyone else in the entire south coast to undo it.

To save these two people, the family supporting Jenna would have to beg him for help!

Leylin was also quite interested in Jenna’s divination ability and desired to know more about it.

……

*Whoosh…*

The sounds of fierce wind whistled past Leylin’s ears.

*Awooooo!” The Venom Wyvern, Hawke, made sounds of excitement as it soared through the air.

The gale that met them ruffled Leylin’s clothes, producing the sounds of fabric flapping. Leylin closed his eyes in enjoyment, looking content.

“The Abyssal Bone Forest Academy and the Lilytell Family! It’s time to sever things off completely!”

Thinking back to the information he had gained from those few Magi, a merciless glint appeared in Leylin’s eyes.

He was quite knowledgeable in the field of spirits and had learned about methods in torturing spirits. Leylin even had the ability to use certain combinations of potions to search the souls of newly-advanced Magi.

Under the endless torture methods that Leylin had employed, the five Magi that Leylin had taken prisoner quickly relinquished all that they knew.

From their very lips, Leylin was able to obtain a very detailed distribution chart of the Abyssal Bone Forest’s forces in Hunting Zone 3.

What aroused Leylin’s interest was a stronghold that was headed by the Lilytell family!

In the beginning, in order to obtain the Kemoyin’s Pupil technique, he had killed off Bosain. This had offended an elder of the Lilytell family, so Leylin had no choice but escape from the academy. Scenes of his past flashed by Leylin.

This was a dispute that had come about in one’s pursuit of power. There was no right or wrong, but since he had garnered animosity from them, Leylin was prepared to eliminate this liability!

Though Giant had promised to mediate, one could only trust himself! The best enemy was a dead one!

That elder from the Lilytell family who specialized in metal had reached the apex of a rank 1 Magus. If Leylin were to make his move now, it would be a bit difficult.

However, he would be able to cut off his opponent’s wings and weaken his family!

It would be even better if that elder himself was around. Leylin was certain that he would be able to withdraw safely, and that he would be able to collect large amounts of data and command the A.I. Chip to simulate the best way to kill him!

The Venom Wyvern soared through the air at a frightening speed, causing animals and acolytes alike to only see a black blur.

“We’ve entered enemy territory. This is where most of the enemy Magus activity is.”

Leylin suddenly having an idea. He produced large amounts of grey clouds from within his sleeves, concealing both him and the Venom Wyvern.

With the spread of the grey clouds, the large figure of the Venom Wyvern actually become the same colour as the blue sky. Even the immense life and heat waves from it vanished.

……

On a valley floor, an obese-looking acolyte in grey robes was being chased by a group of wild wolves.

”Faster! Just a little bit faster, and I’ll reach one of the strongholds of the academy!”

The acolyte ran, cheering herself on while tightly grasping a unique red ore.

“Awoooo!” A wild wolf howled, surrounding itself with a ring of green particles. Its speed immediately increased fivefold, turning into a black line as it headed straight for the acolyte.

With green light shooting from its eyes, the wolf opened its mouth to reveal sharp teeth that reeked of blood, and snapped at the acolyte’s hand.

“Bite it!” This acolyte resolutely surrendered the left hand that the wolf was aiming for.

*Ka-cha!* The pathetic defense of the acolyte’s robes was pierced through.

Immediately after, the wolf fiercely bit onto the acolyte’s left arm, and a muffled sound similar to something biting on leather was heard.

“Hah!” The acolyte swung her left arm.

The wild wolf was swung away as she exerted her enormous strength.

At the next moment, however, multiple wild wolves caught up to her.

Chapter 222: Appearance

“Rain of Fire!”

From atop the Venom Wyvern’s back Leylin’s gentle voice was heard.

Shortly after, yet another huge black fireball emerged out of nowhere on top of the stronghold, and boom! The fireball exploded, dispersing into black fire droplets that looked like rain, spreading across the entire area.

*Sssii!*

An acolyte who had been surrounding Nyssa had brief contact with a fire droplet that brushed by his shoulder, and before he could even make a sound, he had been reduced to a pile of white ash.

“Ru- Run!” The acolyte from the Lilytell family’s voice wavered, his fear apparent.

*Shua Shua Shua!* The acolytes that had been surrounding Nyssa looked as if they had seen a ghost, evading the fire droplets in the air, terrified.

*Tss tss!* A black spark fell on the silver threads that bound Nyssa.

In that instant, this magic artifact was warped out of shape by the black flames and eventually melted into a silver white liquid that dripped to the ground.

Under the onslaught of black fire droplets, large numbers of acolytes were turned to ash without any chance to resist.

The surrounding buildings began to burn furiously, and under the attack of the Rain of Fire, everything instantly turned into a sea of fire.

“It’s- It’s Leylin!”

Nyssa whispered, but at that moment, she saw a black fire droplet flying towards her.

“Hm?” Leylin looked around mid-air and suddenly noticed a very familiar figure from the corner of his eyes.

“It’s Nyssa!” Leylin exclaimed, and under his manipulation, the black fire droplet deviated, brushing past the edges of Nyssa’s hair.

“Who dares to attack the territory of the Abyssal Bone Forest Academy?”

Several black human figures dashed out. One of them rapidly chanted a few incantations, and a dome emitting green rays appeared in the sky, blocking the attack of the black fire droplets.

*Drip! Drip! Drip!*

Countless black fire droplets splashed onto the dome and began to burn.

The Magus who cast the protection spell immediately cried out in alarm. “The might of this black fire is immense. My spiritual force is being rapidly consumed. Who will help me?”

“Me!” A Magus nearby immediately chanted a few words, and a layer of blue ice extended across the layer of protection.

Green, blue, and black rays of light mixed together soared into the sky and descended, forming a huge tornado.

After the tornado descended.

The two Magi looked pale, and it was evident that they had suffered massively.

However, at this point, nobody bothered with them.

“Black flames that are astoundingly strong! That Venom Wyvern as well! You must be ‘Blackfire’ Leylin!”

A Magus who seemed to be the leader recognised Leylin.

“What? It’s him!” “Leylin!” “That genius who betrayed us?”

All of a sudden, clamours of disbelief broke out from the survivors.

“You… must be Magi from the Lilytell family, right?” Leylin clasped his hands behind his back. “Don’t deny it! Even from this distance, I can smell that putrid stench of your bloodline on your bodies!”

“So what?” A silver-haired Magus stood. “You actually dared to kill the sole grandson of our elder. I’ve already sent him a signal, so just wait here and prepare to be punished!”

“You’ve told him? Good! That’s great!”

Leylin’s reaction obviously surprised the silver-haired Magus.

Leylin continued, “Since you’ve already alerted him, there’s no point in keeping any of you alive.”

Hearing Leylin’s words, the Magi present felt a chill in their hearts, a sense of foreboding became apparent.

“Shadow Domain!” Countless tentacles extended from the shadow under Leylin’s feet, spreading across the horizon and completely blocking all the sunlight in the area.

“Be careful!” The Magus leader nearby could only screech, before a black light flashed and a crimson palm went through his chest, digging out a bright red heart that still pumped furiously.

Under the assault of the Crimson Palm, the innate defense spells of these Magi were torn apart like paper.

“He- He killed the leader!”

One of the Magi present looked at Leylin as if they were looking at the devil incarnate, and yelled in despair before running in the opposite direction.

“Lum, come back!” The surrounding Magi shouted, but it was too late.

Within the shadows, Leylin seemed to be a grain of dust that had fused with the gentle wind and floated to Lum’s back. A crimson palm went for his head.

*Rumble!*

A layer of crimson flames began to burn furiously on Lum, and turned the official Magus into ashes.

Regular rank 1 Magi were as weak as children in front of Leylin. They were easily taken care of.

*Zoom!*

Leylin suddenly sensed something and gazed into the distance.

From far away, a silver ray of light was like a sharp sword, heading here in a straight line.

“The main character is here!” Leylin grinned, arms rising as he clenched his fists.

The darkness that had engulfed the entire region was withdrawn into Leylin’s palm, turning into a sphere of darkness which hovered in the air. Strong energy waves swept the area, a violent storm surging and bringing up an entire layer of the ground.

“Halt!” The silver-white ray shouted from afar.

Unfortunately, Leylin did not care for the voice and flung out the sphere of darkness.

The sphere of darkness that was full of destructive power approached the remaining Magi soundlessly.

Under their terrified gazes, the black sphere advanced slowly and steadily, their spells and innate defensive spells devoured by the sphere.

A few official Magi were run over by the sphere, leaving behind tracks on the ground.

“I’ll kill you!”

Along with the furious growl, the speed of the silver ray increased by a few times, and Leylin could almost see an old man with silver ornaments on his face.

“Time to switch locations!” Leylin gave a light smile and patted Hawke’s head.

“Awoo!”

Hawke let out a roar that seemed to be a demonstration of its might, and with a jolt of its wings, it quickly left the area.

*Chi!*

In a few seconds, the silver light from afar arrived, revealing the figure of an old man in silver white attire.

The old man gazed at the stronghold, which had been reduced to ruins. His clothes rustled despite the lack of wind, violent metal elemental particles hovered behind him.

“You can’t escape! Even if you were to escape to the ends of the earth, I will still find you and kill you!”

Metallic silver white rays flashed, and the old man was gone, leaving behind the echoes of his words.

……

Another ten or so minutes passed.

*Crash!* Within the ruins, there was an area with a mound. A bizarre creature that looked like it had been sewn together emerged.

“Was that Leylin just now? I can’t believe this! So he’s actually became such a powerful official Magus…”

Nyssa gazed in the direction Leylin had left, muttering to herself incessantly.

As Leylin had intentionally directed his attack away, as well as her somewhat strong resistance to magic, she had not gained any major injuries in this terrifying attack save for a few holes in her clothes.

“Official Magus…” An envious glint appeared in Nyssa’s eyes.

To be rid of the harm done to her body, she had to raise her strength to the level of an official Magus. Only then would she be able to alter her body and regain her original appearance.

“One day! I will reach that point one day!” Nyssa clenched her fists resolutely.

*Rustle!*

At this moment, a large sound was heard from a fallen wooden building nearby. At the bottom of the building, an acolyte could be seen.

Nyssa walked over curiously but was met with the face of the acolyte that belonged to the Lilytell family.

However, compared to Nyssa, this acolyte was very unlucky. Not only an arm and a leg was broken, there was a huge injury in his abdominal area. Even his intestines were spilling out, and all he could do was moan and groan in pain.

“You! Come here!” Upon seeing Nyssa, this acolyte brightened up.

“What is it?” Nyssa gazed at him indifferently.

“A filthy, lowly acolyte like you… still, has a bit of use! Send- Send me to my family, and I’ll give you a few items that are barely passable as a reward…”

The acolyte stumbled over his words, looking at Nyssa with disdain, as if letting her touch him was a huge honour.

However, Nyssa was unmoved like a block of wood and stood there without moving.

“You… “The acolyte was flushed red with anger as he pointed at Nyssa, wanting to say something.

*Pak!*

With his movement, a red ore fell from his lap, spinning on the ground.

Upon seeing the ore, Nyssa’s eyes looked dangerous.

“You! What do you think you’re doing?”

The acolyte that had been arrogant beyond belief suddenly felt a hint of danger, a fearful expression flashed past before he tried to sit upright. “Are you trying to attack me? You have to think this—”

*Bang!*

Before the acolyte could finish his words, a green corrosive ball landed on his head, eating through most of his head in the next second.

Gazing upon his corpse, Nyssa went forward and retrieved that red ore.

“I merely followed your earlier instructions and focused my attack on your face, young master Lilytell…”

Nyssa had a strange expression on her face. It seemed to be dread, but at the same time, she looked as if a weight had been lifted off her shoulders.

……

Leylin stood in the heart of a spacious land filled with broken stones while appearing to be waiting for someone.

The Venom Wyvern Hawke was useless in this level of battle and had been ordered to return.

All of a sudden, Leylin raised his head as if he had sensed something.

Chapter 224: Metal and Gravity

*Rumble!*

The world seemed to stop at this second.

A few seconds later, the surroundings returned to normal.

The situation just now was as if a movie was being been screened, but had suddenly malfunctioned.

Next, a strong energy storm spread out in all directions.

In the centre of the energy storm, black flames and silvery white rays of light constantly battled, engulfing each other.

*Creak…*

At the boundaries of the battle, where Marb had set up the metallic prison, the cage constantly creaked in protest of their intense fight.

Minutes later, the frightening energy storm dissipated.

Marb did not have a single injury on him, and even his hair was untouched. He stared straight in Leylin’s direction, grabbing at him with a single hand, “Lad! Come here!”

Leylin’s body moved sluggishly, and this was enough time for several silver chains to lock him into place, and make his body involuntarily fly towards Marb.

“Die!”

Marb charged forward furiously, the spikes and blades attacking like the rain, with each spike and blade carrying a large amount of energy. Just being hit by one would cause a regular rank 1 Magus serious injuries.

“Fallen Star Pendant!”

Leylin bellowed, and the black scales and dark red light fused together, forming a ring of unusual light.

*Ka-cha! Ka-cha!* His muscles swelled, and he broke the chains binding him using his brute strength.

*Ding ding! Ding ding!*

Silver flying needles and blades fell upon this layer of light and were then repelled, producing sparks and crisp sounds.

“Is this all you have? You disappoint me!”

Leylin looked to be quite disappointed, and moments later, his eyes turned amber!

“If that’s the most you can do, then I give my apologies. You’re the one dying here today!”

In a flash, a strange light emitted from Leylin’s eyes and headed straight into Marb’s eyes.

The innate spell—Eyes of Petrification!

Marb’s charging form suddenly became sluggish, and a layer of ashen stone skin spread, beginning from the corners of his eyes.

*Weng Weng!*

A burst of white light was produced by a talisman around Marb’s neck.

Under the milky white shine, the stone skin on his face came loose bit by bit.

“A talisman meant to counter against petrification? It’s quite effective. It must have been difficult to obtain!”

Leylin’s expression did not change as he came up to Marb in a few breaths.

The first time he had been chased after by Marb’s clone, Leylin had revealed his petrification abilities. That was how he had turned the tables on the clone, but in the process, he had also exposed his ability to petrify his opponents.

As his archenemy, how could Marb not make preparations against that?

However, even in ancient times, petrification was a lesser known spell. In the south coast, it was practically extinct. Talismans that could be used to negate it were scarce, and most could only be found in ancient ruins.

Leylin was a little surprised at Marb’s ability to find one so quickly.

However, even if Marb had a talisman, how could it be that effective against the petrification methods of an ancient creature such as the Giant Serpent Kemoyin?

Though Marb had dispelled the petrification, he had still been slowed.

*Shua!* Black light flashed, and in that instant, Leylin was already in front of Marb, his amber eyes meeting Marb’s.

“Die!”

The crimson light produced by the Fallen Star Pendant solidified into a giant axe. However, Leylin did not seem to be satisfied and pointed at the weapon.

*Shik!*

Immense black flames engulfed the axe.

“Hah!” Leylin shouted, and large numbers of shadows emerged from behind him, and converged onto his body.

From the shadows, Leylin’s tall figure suddenly shot up, and he transformed into a three metre tall giant with tanned skin.

“Aooooo!”

The giant roared, the muscles on his arm bulging, and showing the dark red, earthworm-like veins on his body.

Like a deity from legends, the giant held the large axe and swung, aiming for Marb’s neck!

*Chi!* Before the hatchet connected, the unimaginable sharpness of the heat waves and gales produced from the swing had already destroyed the defensive layer of liquid metal on his neck.

*Ka-cha!*

The fiery, black axe cut through Marb’s neck, and it looked as if his head was going to fall off. The black flames extended throughout his body in an instant.

Marb’s expression was blank as he collapsed.

“Hm?” Leylin was in a daze. This was much too easy, but even official Magi would not live if their heads were chopped off!

[Beep! Danger! Detecting target still giving out energy waves!] The A.I. Chip sounded at this moment.

Immediately after, a ray of snow white light appeared in front of Leylin.

“This is bad!” All Leylin could do was to try his best to dodge, and protect the most important parts of his body.

*Puchi!* A silvery white longsword that was giving off milky white light pierced into Leylin’s lower abdomen.

”Scram!”

Both of Leylin’s hands turned crimson, and blood coloured flames blazed as he clawed down!

”Crimson Palm!”

At the same time, he retreated without even glancing at Marb.

After he managed to create some distance between them, Leylin covered the injury on his abdomen while looking at Marb in shock.

At this moment, Marb had turned into a white metallic humanoid. His head, which was tilted, was loosely connected to his neck by a tiny amount of skin. His body was still burning with black flames, yet it was as though he didn’t feel a thing as he quietly stood there. The sword that was held by Marb was also dripping with Leylin’s blood.

At the point of Marb’s neck where he had chopped, Leylin could see that the surface of the open wound was now all metallic, where there was no likeness to a human’s flesh and blood at all.

”To think that not only did he have his outer appearance protected by the liquid metal, even his internals had completed turned into metal…”

Leylin’s heart sank.

”Hahah…” Marb, whose head was dangling, laughed wildly. “Bet you’d never thought of this huh? Ninety-odd years ago, I had already completely fused my body with a metallic creature, so now, I don’t have a single weak point on my body. Injuries in places that would be fatal to other regular Magi are just scratches to me…”

“How pathetic!”

Leylin looked at the somewhat crazed Marb with a pitiful look on his face.

Although there were benefits to fusing with an elemental creature, by doing so, one would lose their sense of touch.

When one’s flesh and skin turned into metal, he would not be able to enjoy the sense of touch anymore.

Wasn’t real reason for a Magus to pursue the truth and climb to the top, to control his fate and fulfill his desires, enjoying life to the fullest?

But now, for the sake of power, Marb had actually forsaken such a thing. So then, what more was the meaning of his pursuit?

”The pathetic one is you!”

Evidently, Leylin’s look of pity had deeply triggered Marb and his deranged expression grew even more intense.

Suddenly, a brownish yellow light flickered on Marb’s body. The silver liquid metal protruded outward, transforming into a tiny spell formation.

“Gravity spell formation!” After having been inflicted damage several times by Leylin, Marb finally revealed the trump card that he had been holding back!

*Weng!*

In an instant, a huge amount of brownish yellow light began to emanate from him.

“This is… Gravity?!” Suddenly, Leylin felt his body turned heavy as if it was being crushed by a large mountain. As it happened, Leylin recalled something.

Around him, the gravitational force multiplied in an instant. Not only was movement difficult, Leylin’s face darkened due to the fact that even his internal organs had suffered from the gravitational pull to the point that pain had spread from his insides.

“Not good; although my defense on the outside is strong, it’s a completely different story for my insides! If this goes on and he activates a one hundred times multiplier, my body will most likely be obliterated…”

Leylin’s face was extremely unsightly at this point in time.

Marb, who had a body made of metal, would not suffer any hindrances to his brain or organs.

“Hahaha… Once more! Times ten!”

Marb shouted, and the brownish yellow light flashed even brighter.

Leylin’s feet sank, and the injury to his abdomen, which had undergone hemostasis, started to bleed profusely again due to the gravitational pull.

“Hahaha… Come on!”

Marb dashed right in front of Leylin and brandished his sword, yet Leylin could only feebly raise his right hand to deflect the blow.

*Bang!*

The scales on his arm were crushed and shattered, and Leylin was sent flying backwards like a cannonball.

“Not enough! Still not enough! Times twenty!” Marb pierced the ground with both of his hands.

In an instant, Leylin felt as if the gravitational force had increased once more. If he had felt the weight of a mountain crushing him before, now, it was the weight of three mountains!

*Boom!*

A huge crater was created on the ground the moment Leylin’s body landed.

“Go to hell!” Marb’s right hand turned into a giant silver hammer.

“Urgh! You actually restored the ancient gravity spell formation!”

Leylin laid on his back as he smiled with a hint of admiration, “Not bad indeed!”

This expression gave Marb a sudden yet very uneasy premonition.

“You’re already going to die. What are you trying to act so tough for?” Marb hammered down viciously.

“Suction spell formation! Activate!”

Under the shadow of the large hammer, Leylin rapidly chanted a few syllables.

*Weng!*

A reversed ‘j’-shaped rune suddenly appeared on Leylin’s body.

In a flash, Leylin seemed to be pulled back by a huge force and flew away from under the giant hammer, and into a distant place.

“Trying to escape? Times thirty…”

Watching Leylin’s retreating figure, the brownish yellow light on Marb’s body increased in brightness once more.

Chapter 227: Transition

“Number 2! Number 3!”

Leylin shouted.

“Master!” Two Branded Swordsmen wearing heavy armour immediately came and knelt down in front of Leylin.

“I’m activating all concealment and defence spell formations. You are to stand guard outside and not let any living being come inside.”

Leylin instructed. The two spirit-branded slaves nodded, keeping a strict vigil outside.

These two Branded Swordsmen were controlled by Leylin through spirit branding. Even if asked to die, they would do so with no qualms and were the best people to guard Leylin.

[Counting down: 8, 7, 6…] The A.I. Chip’s voice became softer.

All that Leylin needed to do now was to snap his fingers, and a ring of a spell formation suddenly emerged from his surroundings, protecting the area.

After doing all this, Leylin closed his eyes and submerged himself in the green liquid.

……

Time flowed by.

Ten days later, in this little cave, in the middle of the spell formation, dense Dark elemental energy particles were mixed with flaming-red Fire elemental energy particles and they filled the entire pool.

These elemental energy particles were so dense that they were immediately apparent in the external world; different colours were visible on the rock wall around him due to the reflection of light on these elemental particles.

At the heart of the elemental energy particles, black and red vapour converged, seemingly about to crystallize.

In the pool, the original green liquid had completely disappeared, revealing a dried up bottom.

A large black cocoon lay still at the centre of the bottom of the pool, constantly expanding and then shrinking back, just as if it was breathing.

While the black cocoon was ‘breathing’, the Dark and Fire elemental energy particles were continuously being pulled inside it with each ‘inhalation’.

The black light became increasingly thin, till at the end, the hint of a perfect human figure could be seen.

”Tsss!”

A long hissing sound was produced from within the cocoon.

Shortly after, a huge gale engulfed the cave.

The Dark and Fire elemental energy particles in the air seemed to have come across a black hole, and were dragged into the heart of the black cocoon.

The black light around the cocoon became weaker, and then completely dissipated.

“Hm?” Leylin blinked his eyes open.

The moment he had completely awakened, he could feel as if there was a layer of something sticky on his body, and it was very uncomfortable.

He lifted his right arm, and a layer of skin that was the colour of his skin peeled off like withered tree bark.

”What’s this? Is this like imitating the molting of the snake species?”

Leylin was a little speechless and quickly tore off the dead skin.

*Ka-cha! Ka-cha!*

He efficiently removed the layer of dead skin covering his body. On the layer of the dead skin, there were even scaly resemblances similar to that of a snake’s skin.

Leylin placed the skin aside and reassessed his body.

Currently, there were no signs of injuries on his body. All his wounds had recovered, and his mental state was brimming with vitality. In general, his condition was great and better than before.

Leylin stared at his hands.

His palms were now even whiter and exquisite, and the pores seemed to have disappeared — it was like the skin of a newborn baby!

However, Leylin could clearly sense that a hidden and monstrous power was flowing through his arms..

*Ba-dump! Ba-dump!*

His heart was pounding strongly, circulating blood and other nutritious substances all around his body. While his heart beat, Leylin could almost feel his body becoming stronger bit by bit.

Though this was very slight, with the passing of time, the strength held in his body would be terrifying!

“My body’s vitality has already become so powerful, but what about my spiritual force?”

Leylin closed his eyes and began to feel the elemental energy particles in his sea of consciousness.

In the sea of consciousness, the red rays were even more prominent, and the silvery-white threads of spiritual force were spiralling, seemingly very steady.

“The total amount of spiritual force actually increased so much?”

Leylin transferred a bit of the silver spiritual force to the external world.

While maneuvering the spiritual force, he could feel himself extremely comfortable with this process. His body had adapted to the rapid increase in his spiritual force, and Leylin also knew that after this miraculous transformation, his spiritual force was slightly able to solidify. Within rank 1 Magi, the quality of his spiritual force was definitely one of the best.

After he had made a thread of silver spiritual force probe out of his body, an astonishing scene appeared.

Blackness! Numerous black lights appeared in the sky like fireflies, rushing towards Leylin’s spiritual force and clinging onto it.

Leylin had never felt so comfortable in his life.

Even without the use of the A.I. Chip, Leylin knew that the level of his elemental essence conversion had already reached a very high amount.

“I was wrong! I got it all wrong!”

Leylin was dazed for a second, and then laughed wryly.

“The Giant Kemoyin Serpent was originally the child of the shadows, and the elemental essence conversion is just child’s play for it. Rather than exploring the strength of my bloodline, I persistently tried to use crystallised Dark elemental energy particles to break through the bottleneck. How stupid…”

Fortunately, it was not too late. Using crystallised elemental energy particles only delayed Leylin’s second bloodline transition.

Once he got more familiar with his body, Leylin commanded silently, “A.I. Chip! List the recent changes in my condition!”

*Shua shua!* Rows of blue words emerged in front of Leylin.

[Beep! Detected rapid liveliness in Host’s bloodline, the Kyerlis coefficient is: 44 — 46 — 56 — 78 — 89 — 101! The liveliness has reached the threshold and the Giant Kemoyin Serpent bloodline’s second transition begins!] [Beep! Host has gone into deep sleep. Commencement of reformation of Kemoyin’s Bloodline within body.] [Detected unknown composition in Host’s body! Permission to dispel substances… Countdown: 5, 4, 3, 2, 1!] [Beep! No authorization from Host, unable to dispel! Entering observation mode! Recording data…] [Beginning of alteration of heart. Rate of completion: 1%, 2%, 15%, 30%, 51%…] [Strengthening of Host’s bloodline. Innate spell, Kemoyin’s Scales strengthened!

[Kemoyin’s Scales: Forms a layer of defensive scales on host’s body, has an instant effect. Physical defense: 35 degrees. Resistance to magic: 40 degrees. Consumption: 1 spiritual force, 1 magic power every 6 hours.] [Measured large rise in Host’s stats in multiple areas. Collecting data…] [Beep! Collection of data completed, converting into numerical values…]

Leylin found his stats being refreshed.

[Leylin Farlier. Rank 1 Warlock. Bloodline: Giant Kemoyin Serpent. Strength: 20.1, Agility: 13.4, Vitality: 25.7, Spiritual Force: 75.9, Magic Power: 75 (Magic Power is in synchronisation with Spiritual Force). Elemental essence conversion: 89%. Status: Heart remodelling, progress: 61%]

The heart was an important organ that produced the blood of the Giant Kemoyin Serpent. Through the remodelling of the heart, ancient Warlocks obtained vitality and the ability to produce blood as powerful as that of the Kemoyin Serpent.

With the scanning of the A.I. Chip, Leylin could clearly see a purplish red colour constantly extending from his heart.

Wave after wave of power and blood was transported to all parts of his body.

Along with the throbbing of his heart, the last few digits of the numbers that represented his spiritual force, vitality, elemental essence conversion constantly increased.

“Even before my heart is completely remodelled, the rise in my stats is still increasing. How terrifying…”

Leylin mumbled to himself.

His current stats were comparable to a peak rank 1 Magus, and in terms of vitality, he exceeded them by a fairly large amount.

He could feel a strength that he had never experienced!

Pak! Leylin supported his weight with his hands, and a deep palm print was indented onto the rock at the bottom of the pool.

His entire body bounced, and he jumped out of the pool.

*Peng peng!*

Under his feet, fine cracks in the rock extended like spider webs.

“After the increase in my vitality, the density of my body has also increased. I’ll need to train again so that I can control the strength I now possess.”

Seeing the damage he had unwittingly caused, he smiled wryly.

He found a random piece of black clothing in his bag and wore it, and then snapped his fingers.

*Weng weng!*

The defense spell formation around ceased operation and two black figures arrived like a hurricane. They knelt before Leylin and said, “Master!”

“In the time I’ve been asleep, has there been any strange happenings?” Leylin asked indifferently.

Number 2 and Number 3 shared a glance, and Number 2 took the initiative and held out a pendant that looked like a book.

“In the time that Master has been asleep, everything has been quiet. The five specimens are still unconscious, though Master’s secret imprint has been flashing constantly. Without Master’s approval, we did not dare answer…”

“Oh?”

Leylin took the pendant and flipped to a page with an imprint with a strange smile on it. Under the smiling face, there were rows of communication requests, but since Leylin had been in the process of transitioning his bloodline, he naturally did not bother answering them.

He tapped on the smiling face, and string of Dark elemental energy particles shimmered.

“Tsss…” Similar to the static in radios due to bad signals a noise sounded, and the voice of the old man in Leylin’s team could be heard.

“My lord, is that you? Please forgive me. Due to the issue of signals in the secret plane, I can only contact you through the headquarters’ signal tower.”

“Cut the nonsense. What do you need?” Leylin asked.

“My lord… In the time you have not been around, our Hunting Zone 3 was was attacked by a peak rank 1 Magus by the name of Marb. He was like a mad dog, and as long as someone appeared in front of him, whether an acolyte or an official Magus, they would be killed. He even announced your name and said that if you did not appear, this situation would continue… Bat and Crow have already died in his hands…”

Chapter 231: Nefarious Filthbird

At headquarters, in the hunting team’s administrative zone.

*Thump!* A huge Venom Wyvern descended from the sky and created two large depressions as its feet touched the ground.

A black shadow flickered, and a robed Magus jumped off the back of the Wyvern.

“My Lord! My Lord!” An old Magus saw the Venom Wyvern, his eyes brightening as he approached them.

“Old man! We’ll need to have some words about you escaping at the last minute!”

Leylin couldn’t be bothered to deal with him and entered the hall.

“Vice Team leader! Lord Caesar is looking for you!” Two hunting team Magi came before Leylin and bowed slightly, their manners impeccable.

Though Leylin had no real power in front of Caesar, ordinary members like them were small fry. Those who had offended him the other time were still in isolation! Hence, these members were extremely respectful to Leylin, or at least on the surface.

”Great timing, I was just about to look for him!”

Leylin nodded slightly.

*Ka-cha!* The door opened, revealing Caesar’s figure behind the office desk. The two Magi who had escorted him here quickly left.

“Magus Leylin! You’re just in time. Regarding the previous mission…” Before Caesar even spoke, a huge metallic piece was firmly thrown onto the table.

“It’s done!”

On this huge silver white metal, there were indents that formed an old, wrinkled face.

“Metallic lifeform?” Caesar was slightly suspicious, but at the thought of something, his eyes suddenly opened wide.

“I need to inspect this!”

After speaking, Caesar took the metallic sculpture and jogged out of the office, leaving Leylin alone inside.

Though Caesar had issued this mission before, not in his wildest dreams could he have expected Leylin to actually complete it. After all, Marb was a Magus on the same level as him!

However, Leylin had given him something that looked like Marb’s head. How could this not astonish him?

In that moment, Caesar even had the suspicion that Leylin had brought him brought a random head to escape punishment.

*Creak!* Ten minutes later, the door opened once more.

Caesar appeared in front of Leylin, but his expression was dark, with even hints of shock in his face.

“I didn’t think you would actually be able to do it…” Caesar could not conceal the shock and curiosity in his eyes.

“If it’s possible, could you share the process of your mission with me? You know, as the hunting team leader, it’s necessary that I know about the entire process and then give rewards accordingly.”

Caesar spoke indifferently.

“It was very simple…” Leylin unfolded his arms. “After taking on the mission, I was going to look for you but coincidentally saw him heavily wounded, which is how I completed this assignment.”

“Magus Leylin…” Caesar’s face darkened further. “Please speak the truth!”

“That’s what happened! I even brought along a neutral wandering Magus. If there’s anything else you need, you can just ask her.”

Leylin was indifferent.

In reality, as long as one was not completely blind, anyone could see this was an excuse!

But so what? Marb was dead. If Leylin said he was heavily injured, that must be the truth!

As for that female Magus, she was just a semi-converted Magus. How could she tell the state of a peak rank 1 Magus’ injuries?

“You…” Caesar’s face began to flush.

In that instant, he suddenly seemed to have thought of something and his entire body relaxed.

“No matter what, Magus Leylin, you have disposed of a peak rank 1 Magus from the other faction, thus showing your loyalty to Four Seasons Garden. Your bravery will be known by all light Magi, and you might even be recorded down in history…”

Caesar congratulated him with a fake smile.

“Thank you for your compliment, but I want to know more about the substantial rewards I will be getting!” Leylin nodded nonchalantly and then spoke.

For him, having a reputation wasn’t all that important. With the prerequisite that the situation would not be unfavourable to him, he was, of course, willing to do some good deeds and obtain a good reputation. However, if there were no advantages and him needing to put in so much effort, making a name for himself in history was just something that only idiots would bother doing!

“Hah…“

Caesar breathed in deeply to calm the fire within his heart and said icily, “There will naturally be rewards. As for any promotions, that will have to wait. However, the contribution points have already been issued to you. 1500 points! Don’t worry, the organisation is very strict when it comes to things like this, so I don’t have the authority to dock points from you.”

Immediately after, Caesar produced a green crystal card from within his robes and passed it to Leylin.

An obscure look flashed past Leylin’s eyes as he held out his hand to take the card.

*Ka-cha!*

That instant he took the card, a slight explosion happened.

Leylin and Caesar’s bodies shook for a second, and they immediately sprang apart.

“What a terrifying rate of improvement! Magus Leylin!” His expression held a trace of fear as Caesar looked at Leylin.

Before, he still had the confidence that he could suppress Leylin, but now, after the probing, he found that this Magus who he had looked upon with contempt had already caught up to him and become a mighty peak rank 1 Magus! He might even be stronger than him!

Caesar could not be so casual with Leylin any longer. Leylin’s ranking in his heart had already risen to the same level of opponents who were of equal strength as him.

Leylin only gave a slight smile in response to Caesar’s exclamation.

He had even concealed a part of the strength of his Warlock blood. If not, Caesar might be completely stunned.

He took his own contribution point card and swiped the green crystal card above it!

*Beep!* A light flickered and the 0 on Leylin’s own card changed to 1500.

“Alright! Magus Leylin, you may return and take a rest while waiting for news from the Elders.” Caesar spoke slowly.

Leylin’s transformation made him feel a little uncomfortable. He was currently in need of some time to come up with a counterplan.

“Thank you!”

Leylin stood up and took a small bow, each action revealing an unspeakable sort of elegance.

……

“Really? His strength exceeds yours?”

In a room made primarily out of plants, Reynold placed the white porcelain cup on the table, a hand supporting his forehead and a finger curling his hair. Another hand was unconsciously striking the table, producing the dull ‘thud’ sounds.

The current Reynold looked like an old man who was not in the best state of mind, but all those who were familiar with him could tell this was him pondering over something deeply.

Caesar stood aside, waiting for the final decision from this elder of the Four Seasons Garden.

“If that’s the case, we’ll give him the position of the head of patrolling at the headquarters!” Reynold thought over this for a long time till the steam from his porcelain cup had vanished, before speaking.

“Alright!” In response, Caesar merely nodded.

“Also, I found out that we might have paid too little attention to that guy… If there’s time, I think I want to meet him.”

Reynold stretched, looking pleased as he glanced at Caesar.

“Don’t you know how rude it is to bother an old man who was planning on taking an afternoon nap?”

“My apologies! I’ll take my leave now!”

Caesar quickly bowed and left, a mysterious grin about his lips.

“Leylin Farlier?”

Behind him, Reynold mouthed this name.

He had naturally taken Leylin’s talent into account. If he was truly sincere about joining Four Seasons Garden and that the value of the item he had gotten from the ruins was not too high, Reynold would not go so far as to do anything dirty and covet his inheritance.

However, from how Leylin had been able to improve his strength so quickly, what he had obtained was definitely not as simple as he had thought it was.

It was extremely beneficial to the user and was worth the risk for Reynold to take action.

In addition, based on the information he had gathered, ever since Leylin entered Four Seasons Garden, he still had dealings with dark Magi. He was even involved in a few of the large incidents in Nightless City!

This was just intolerable! Any organisation would not put up with the existence of disloyal members!

Though this was just a hypothesis, this was enough reason for Reynold to make his move!

He was an existence that had stepped into the level of rank 2 Magi! The difference between Magi from each rank was like heaven and earth. Even if Leylin received some amazing inheritance, as long as he had not promoted to a rank 2 Magus, he was powerless in front of a true rank 2 Magus.

Just the fact that he could solidify his spiritual force was enough to suppress most rank 1 Magi!

……

At this point in time, Leylin was oblivious to all this.

He was currently in a laboratory, holding a test tube that contained a grey liquid within. His blue eyes flashed as he constantly scanned the contents.

“The solution that contains a Nefarious Filthbird’s feathers! Rumours have it that the ancient Nefarious Filthbird and Trial’s Eye were nemeses. Its feathers also carried with it the chaos its original body was known for. It is an item that swindlers love.”

The conclusion that the A.I. Chip had was presented in front of Leylin’s eyes.

“Based on the information and simulations, this solution is able to take care of the oath I made with Four Seasons Garden. But what happens after? The problem I have isn’t just with the oath…”

Leylin mumbled to himself, and looked at his stats once more.

[Leylin Farlier. Rank 1 Warlock, Bloodline: Giant Kemoyin Serpent. Strength: 20.1, Agility: 13.4, Vitality: 25.9, Spiritual Force: 76.1, Magic Power: 76 (Magic Power is in synchronisation with Spiritual Force). Elemental essence conversion: 90%. Status: Altering heart, progress at 69%.]

“The heart is the location where the Giant Kemoyin Serpent’s blood was produced. Through the alteration of the heart, ancient Warlocks obtained similar vitality and abilities to produce blood!”

Chapter 234: Using the Solvent

Under the circumstances, each division could do little but pinch their noses in distaste while they did as Leylin wanted. However, his reputation had gone straight to the gutters and had gained him the reputation of ‘least welcomed’ at all divisions.

To be honest, when he had first received news of this, Leylin was a little surprised but found it very amusing.

In the Magus world, strength was to be respected. Reputation wasn’t entirely useless, but it only applied to those within the same ranks of strength.

As long as he continued to improve his strength, after he advanced to become a rank 2 Magus, these people would stick onto him like dogs, wagging their tails and lamenting that they had not let Leylin taking more advantage of them.

“Magus Leylin! Greedy Dragon! Lord Reynold would like to see you tomorrow at 7pm. Please be prepared.”

Caesar expressionlessly announced in front of Leylin and left.

“This is a little earlier than expected. Have I finally angered the heavens?” Leylin laughed without fear.

He did not take his position as the patrolling inspector seriously, and on top of that, he had been doing all sorts of things. It was no surprise that all of the Four Seasons Garden viewed him as an enemy and opposed him.

If he did not make any preparations, he was going to die!

This was definite. After all, Leylin himself was not completely innocent, and investigations would spell his downfall.

In addition, the inheritance from the Great Magus Serholm would definitely attract the attention of rank 2 Magi!

In the Magus World, there were all sorts of spells that could be used to detect lies and test one’s spirit.

The reason the Magi here did not use them was because they were light Magi and did everything in sequence. However, this was wartime! Everything was about power. Furthermore, there were also a lot of mysteries about Leylin.

Currently, if any of these spells were used against him, he wouldn’t even have the chance to explain himself!

Actually, Leylin had long since suspected that the Four Seasons Garden had discovered his activities with the dark Magi. Though he left no proper evidence, there might have still been some traces left behind.

If not, why would he, a high-level potion master who was young, talented, and sure to be held in high regard wherever he went, be assigned to this place to fight?

“But this is enough.”

Leylin’s lips quirked in a slight smile.

He had already been mentally prepared to be found out. After all, Magi had too many unknown methods, and he had no way to guard against everything.

Being able to have up to 2 years and allow his bloodline to transition, as well as being able to accumulate a large amount of resources and knowledge, had Leylin feeling quite satisfied.

“It looks like it’s time to fall out with them!”

Leylin looked apathetic. Theoretically speaking, he was the one who had betrayed the Four Seasons Garden, but this was for his own sake! For benefits! To chase his dreams! He was not going to turn back from this route.

“Alright! I’ll use this!” Leylin turned over to the palm of his hand, revealing a well-preserved test tube in his right palm.

Within the test tube was a grey solvent. It was a type of grey that people would find disgusting, and just a glance at it would cause one to feel dizzy.

“The solvent of the Nefarious Filthbird’s feathers! Tests have been conducted on it. In order to break away from Four Seasons Garden and perhaps even become enemies, it’s necessary to dispel the constraints of the contract witnessed by the Trial’s Eye!”

Leylin stared hard at the test tube in his hand, looking unusually excited.

He snapped his fingers, and in an instant, the room was shrouded in a layer of faint yellow light. Leylin then carefully removed the covering from the mouth of the test tube.

*Tsss!* A grey gas floated out of the test tube, and upon contact with the air, the solvent of the Nefarious Filthbird’s feathers produced innumerable tiny bubbles and began to evaporate violently.

“Ugh!” Leylin pinched his nose tightly. “What a terrifying stench!”

He had taken in just a small breath, yet he was already on the verge of fainting from the smell. It was just too stinky! Even with his vitality of over 20, it was almost unbearable for him.

The Nefarious Filthbird was originally a congelation of all of the filthy things in the world, and its feathers held traces of its filthiness.

In actuality, the solvent made from the feathers did not get its power from the feathers themselves, but from the projection of the Nefarious Filthbird’s strength onto this part of its body!

The ancient Nefarious Filthbird was an existence that was the archenemy of the Trial’s Eye! Not only had their battles affected the Magus World, it also several other large-scale areas.

There were traces of them present everywhere in legends and myths.

“Filth! Chaos! How did these characteristics come about, and how did they work?”

A curiosity that could not be concealed appeared in Leylin’s eyes. Whether it was the chaotic characteristic of the Nefarious Filthbird or the fairness of the Trial’s Eye, they were very much different from the spells in the Magus World. They were more like a type or regulation, which gave Leylin the strongest urge to find out even more.

Magi usually liked to research on all types of strange phenomenon and strengths, as well as to try to find ways to make that power theirs.

In terms of trying to chase after the truth, Magi were similar to the researchers and scientists in Leylin’s previous world.

“It’s a pity that this sort of thing can only be approached by those who are at least Morning Star Magi!”

Whether it was the Trial’s Eye or the Filthy Bird, both could traverse through the entire world and weave through terrifying beings. Their existence surpassed that of normal beings, and they had entered a level that Leylin could not hope to even reach for, much less understand.

The current Leylin wasn’t even an ant to them; he was probably a little smaller than a speck of dust.

Even if he wanted to offer sacrifices and summon them, he would only see an apparition that lacked power. It wasn’t possible to explore and find out more about them.

Even though Leylin was a little disappointed, what he felt was, even more, the kindling of fire and a stronger desire within.

“One day! One day, I’ll reach the peak of the Magus World and make people take note of the other great existences, and chase after the truth and eternity they hold…”

*Tsss!*

After the volatile grey solvent in the test tube finished its reaction, Leylin’s body was engulfed by grey mist.

This mist was unbearably smelly, causing Leylin to feel suffocated.

The grey mist seemed to have a life of its own as it climbed onto Leylin’s skin as if trying to find ways to enter his body.

*Rumble!*

Leylin suddenly felt faint, and his expression changed.

*Pak! Pak! Pak!* As if provoked, several apparitions of the Trial’s Eye appeared on his body.

These apparitions were mostly only the size of his thumb, and the biggest was as big as his fist. There were a few mysterious threads connected to it that winded around Leylin.

“The power of regulation?” Leylin extended his right hand, trying to touch those threads.

Unsurprisingly, his hands went straight through the threads as if they were thin air.

“These must be the threads from the contract and regulations! The small Trial’s Eye represents the agreement I had with the old witch, while the largest one is the contract I made that was witnessed by the rank 2 Magus, Reynold!”

The largest Trial’s Eye had the thickest threads and was inseparably close to Leylin’s body.

Some part of him gave him the idea that if he went against the contract, these lines would break, and it would end in a result he did not want to even think about.

*Tssss tssss!*

After witnessing the apparitions of the Trial’s Eye, the fluctuations from the grey mist became more intense. Through an unknown channel, a mysterious piece of information was transmitted to Leylin.

“One feather solvent can only dissolve one contract?” Leylin nodded, and spoke in the ancient Byron language, “I choose this one!” He pointed at the largest Trial’s Eye.

Not only was the ancient Byron language the basis of spellcasting, it even held a mysterious power that allowed all beings with spirits to be able to understand its intended meaning from its words. Hence, it was a language used throughout the Magus world and in other places.

*Chi chi!*

After receiving Leylin’s answer, the grey mist quickly became denser, and the chirps of a bird were sounded in the middle.

The coarse chirps of this bird were was extremely unpleasant to hear, like the bawling of a woman.

Along with the chirps, the grey mist spread out two wings and turned into a faint, large grey bird in the mist.

“Is this the actual body of the ancient Nefarious Filthbird?” Leylin carefully took down the Filthy Bird’s appearance. However, with the hindrance of the mist, besides the bird’s main appearance, nothing else could be clearly made out.

“Judgement!” “Judgement!” “Judgement!” “Judgement!”

At this moment, as if provoked by the Nefarious Filthbird, the Trial’s Eye image on the surface of Leylin’s body began to vibrate.

Small bolts of lightning were produced around the Trial’s Eye, the void crackling around them as sounds of sacrificial hymns sounded out.

The Trial’s Eye in the middle immediately expanded several times, powerful undulations overflowing as it tried to break through the void to borrow a bit of power from its original body.

“Chii!”

The giant bird in the grey mist extended its wings, where large amounts of grey-black mist emanated.

Filth! Chaos!

Leylin felt dizzy again and was almost unable to tell where he was.

”Chi Chi!” The grey-black mist and blue electric currents tried to devour each other, and eventually perished together.

However, it was obvious that there was much more mist than blue lightning, and in a few seconds, it was in an advantageous position.

“Chi Chi!”

Under the shroud of mist, the Trial’s Eye shook wildly and even stopped all attempts at contacting its original body.

At this moment, the large bird in the grey mist soared into the air, and like a predator hunting for food swooped down from midair!

*Pop!*

With a peck from its grey beak, the apparition of the largest Trial’s Eye was pecked out.

*Ka-cha!* *Ka-cha!* *Ka-cha!* The threads that connected Leylin and the Trial’s Eye were snapped in twain.

As the threads snapped, Leylin felt his body slouch in relief, with even his spirit feeling a sense of freedom, as if a weight had been taken off of his mind.

Chapter 236: Enchantment

“Don’t worry, we won’t abandon you!”

Giant tossed a detailed map that had a route marked out in red to Leylin.

“After completing your mission, follow this route, and you’ll definitely be able to leave safely before any other Magi find out. The Lord behind us will divert Reynold’s attention, and we’ll provide support as well.”

Giant spoke calmly, even going out of his way to mention the rank 2 dark Magus supporting Thousand Meddling Hands. It was obvious that he was trying to threaten Leylin.

Leylin was silent for a while. “I will try…”

If it was much too dangerous, he wasn’t going to risk his life for this organisation!

“Alright! You’ll find that this is a very simple and effortless mission!” Giant smiled, “After finishing this, you can rejoin us as a dark Magi! How about it? Which academy or organisation do you want to join? Just tell me.”

Leylin shook his head. He had no such plans yet, and he still did not entirely trust Giant’s words.

If one was not shrewd when dealing with dark Magi, it was certain that they would be taken advantage of so thoroughly that every last bone of theirs will be gobbled!

“Alright! To ensure that things go well, you will need to sign this!” Giant threw a black scroll to Leylin.

“Hm?” Leylin looked through the contents of the scroll and was amazed. “A Trial’s Eye contract? After I have taken the solvent of the Nefarious Filthbird’s feathers, you still dare to use this?”

“This is a special contract that the Lord behind us specifically made for you!” Giant pointed out, emphasizing the last three words. “Also, that solution was the very last one in our organisation. If you can find another, we can only blame it on our bad luck.”

It looked like he was quite confident about this.

“Hehe… in that case, you’re the first person who dares to do something like this!” Leylin scrutinized Giant and smirked.

At the same time, the phantom giant serpent suddenly opened its mouth wide and bit towards Giant!

*Rumble!*

As it neared Giant, the phantom giant serpent suddenly collapsed and turned into a mass of shadow, slamming against Giant’s green fog and producing the sound of waves crashing on the shore.

“Haha… I was just cracking a joke! I’m but a regular member in the Thousand Meddling Hands, so how would I dare to pit myself against elders like you?”

A bright, gentle smile suddenly appeared on Leylin’s expression!

“You’ll become an elder soon enough! After this operation, I can nominate you!” Giant spoke after a moment’s thought.

“In that case, thank you!”

Leylin lightly tapped on the scroll, and the imprint of a black snake instantly appeared on it.

*Rumble!*

The apparition of the Trial’s Eye gave Leylin the feeling that this was even more powerful than the one that Reynold had summoned the previous time.

Under its emotionless gaze, the scroll in Leylin’s hands began to spontaneously combust.

Green flames enveloped the scroll.

The moment after the scroll completely burned up, a ray of light that represented the contract and its restrictions flew into Leylin’s mind.

Afterwards, the apparition of the Trial’s Eye automatically dispersed into the air.

He had skimmed through the contract. The only conditions were that he could not help the Four Seasons Garden; there weren’t any harsh conditions. After all, they still needed his help and could not go overboard.

“It didn’t detect traces of the acts of the Nefarious Filthbird?” Leylin wondered.

He then left the area without a word.

Only Giant was left standing quietly in the basement as if he was waiting for something.

*Boom! Boom! Boom!*

Minutes later, Giant’s body, which was covered in green fog, began to shudder violently, and the wall behind him suddenly exploded!

After the dust settled, a large portion of Giant’s fog had dispersed, revealing a giant figure that was up to 2 metres tall.

“Crazy! That person’s a lunatic!”

Giant murmured to himself and proceeded to laugh maniacally. “Haha… Good! Interesting! Things are getting more interesting!”

He then transformed into a green fog and drifted out of the area.

Behind him, the basement gave way and dust filled the air…

The next day, Leylin punctually arrived at Reynold’s office at seven in the evening.

“Lord Reynold!” He knocked on the door gently.

“Come in!” From behind the door, Reynold’s gentle voice was heard.

Leylin took in a deep breath and pushed the door open. Reynold was seated on a chair of vines, wearing a pair of spectacles as he drank a green beverage. Beside him was a little round table and a similar chair.

“Leylin, you’re here! Take a seat!” Reynold pointed to the chair beside him.

“Many thanks!” Leylin bowed once more and sat near Reynold.

“Here! Try the juice of the Jaded Daro Flower! We’re just having a private conversation now, so don’t be too reserved!” Reynold seemed just like a hospitable old man.

As if a little embarrassed, Leylin gave a slight smile and drank from the cup on the table.

The refreshing scent of nature pervaded his taste buds and extended throughout his four limbs. Leylin felt as if warm water was rinsing his body and making him feel rejuvenated.

“How is it? It tastes pretty good, right?” Reynold asked with anticipation.

“The collections of an elder like yourself are pretty good!” Leylin praised sincerely.

“Haha…” Like a child who had received a compliment, Reynold laughed aloud brightly.

“Here, let us have a friendly chat. Leylin, you seem to be from the Chernobyl Islands right? I went there once when I was young. Resources are scarce in such a barren land, and it’s lacking in Magi…”

Reynold was a very entertaining speaker, and he began to chat with Leylin about his past experiences.

As they spoke leisurely, time flew by, and in the blink of an eye, an hour had passed.

All of a sudden, Leylin suddenly smelt something very sweet.

“What is this?”

“It’s a type of incense from the Wetland Gardens. It’s said to be useful in replenishing one’s spiritual force, and is a favourite of the Magi there.”

Reynold explained lightly, his voice seemingly less and less discernible. A thread of silver spiritual force slowly extended.

Leylin’s expression became slacker and he could feel his eyelids becoming heavier. He eventually fell asleep.

Seeing Leylin in a deep sleep, a smile appeared on Reynold’s face.

He took off a ring on Leylin’s hand and inspected it closely.

“Ring of Sobriety? Looks like it has a few other effects that can defend against probings! There are seven different potions smeared on it as well. Looks like you’ve prepared well, but it’s a pity…”

Reynold glanced at Leylin with a victorious smirk.

“The juice of the Jaded Daro Flower, as well as the pollen from the Intoxicated Dragon Petals, are something even a rank 2 Magus might not be able to withstand. What use is a mere ring and potion?”

These two items were a special combination that Reynold had picked out specifically for Leylin. Some of them even had to be transported from the secret plane, and he had used up a portion of his allowance as the chairman to obtain the items.

This had delayed his plans and allowed Leylin to have the chance to wreak havoc in the Four Seasons Garden.

Of course, since he had paid such a huge price, the effects were superb.

A peak rank 1 Magus was an existence that even a rank 2 Magus like Reynold needed to be careful of! Also, these Magi also had special methods, and might have had a high resistance against hallucinations and enchantments. What was more troublesome was that Leylin was still a member of Four Seasons Garden, so without actual evidence, Reynold could not do anything that might have severe aftereffects.

As an experienced, veteran rank 2 Magus, this was not a problem for Reynold. Now, using a special concoction, he had made Leylin pass out.

In addition, these two ingredients were not harmful to the body, and at most, they would cause Leylin to faint. His resistance to hallucinatory magic would be temporarily lowered, but after this, his body would ultimately benefit in the long run. Hence, Reynold was not going against the contract with the Trial’s Eye.

“Even so, the effects of this type of hallucinogen will not last for a long time. With his body, he’ll awaken in about half an hour, so I have to be quick.

The vined chair under Reynold began to move until Reynold was right in front of Leylin.

“Open your eyes and look at me!”

Reynold spoke lightly, his voice having a strange effect that made one feel dazed.

As he spoke, silvery white rays of light shot out of his eyes. This was the appearance of the solidification of his spiritual force!

Upon hearing Reynold’s words, Leylin’s eyelids flickered and then opened.

“Your name?”

Reynold asked, the silvery white rays so intense that they seemed to be on the verge of piercing through Leylin’s eyeballs.

“Leylin Farlier!”

“Where were you born? Do you have any relatives?”

……

The questions Reynold asked were quite simple at the beginning, and as time went on, he went deeper and increased the difficulty.

Soon enough, after tens of questions, he got into the heart of the matter.

“Why were you wanted by the Lilytell family?”

Reynold asked gently, with some tremors in his voice.

“It is because in order to obtain an inheritance from a ruin, I killed Bosain Lilytell!” Leylin answered in a dazed manner, unable to control the words that spilled out of his mouth.

“What inheritance?” The silver light in his eyes became more concentrated.

“An inheritance that contains incomplete information about the Branded Swordsmen! There’s also a high-grade magic artifact.” Leylin answered.

“Is that so?” Reynold shifted his glasses.

“Branded Swordsmen? A branch of the ancient Magi?” He sized up Leylin’s body.

“A tall and strong body with some brands on the surface. It seems quite similar to the legends…”

As his vitality was amazingly high, the muscles on Leylin’s body were now very obvious, and he had a terrifying amount of strength within. If he tried to impersonate a Grand Knight, nobody would doubt him.

“In that case, what is your relationship with the Thousand Meddling Hands?” Reynold came to the key question.

Chapter 237: Deceit

*Rumble!*

Just as Reynold was using the illusionary spell to interrogate Leylin, a mighty energy wave fluctuation came from afar.

This fluctuation was so immense that even the buildings had mildly shook.

“What? A sneak attack?” Reynold stood up abruptly.

A layer of white light which seemed to be a communication device shone on his body in an instant.

“What’s happening?” Reynold asked indifferently.

“It’s the dark Magi! We suffered a sneak attack from the dark Magi! The first and second defense lines have already perished. We’re currently at the third line of defense!”

From the communication device, the image of a fair-skinned burly bloke who had donned a military uniform was projected.

This was the leader of the defense team who was specially assigned to defend all of Four Seasons Garden. The expression on his face was wrought with fright and worry. It seemed that the dark Magi had placed him under great pressure!

A simple and tiny issue.

“I will mobilise the fighting and hunting teams to your area as soon as possible, you…” Reynold replied to the communicative device.

Suddenly, his face darkened.

Through the projection of the communication device, he could see a gigantic black hand land from the skies and mash the burly bloke between its fingers.

“Ah…” The burly, fair-skinned bloke cried out miserably as he produced large amounts of milky white flames.

*Ka-cha! Ka-cha!*

A large number of miserable looking faces appeared on the gigantic black hand, their mouths opening wide as they swallowed the milky white flames.

*Ka-cha! Ka-cha!*

The bone-chilling sounds of gnawing sounds were heard. After swallowing the white flames, they actually began to gnaw at the burly, fair-skinned man’s body.

“Jejeje…”

In midair, solidified silver spiritual force appeared and formed a human face.

“Reynold, my old friend! Why aren’t you coming to greet me?”

The face sneered.

Immediately after, the huge black hand swept the area and made a mess of the Four Seasons Garden’s defensive line. Under the tyrannical abuse of a rank 2 Magus, the ordinary rank 1 Magi were as insignificant as ants.

*Pak!* The armrest of Reynold’s vined chair was kneaded until it broke.

*Shua!* In a flash, he turned into a green figure and rushed out.

*Ka-cha! Ka-cha!*

After he left, his vined chair squirmed and constantly twisted, gradually turning into something that resembled a human. It stood by Leylin who was still unconscious as if keeping guard.

*Boom!* *Boom!* *Boom!*

Huge undulations from the magic that were even more immense than before travelled over. This was an intense fight between two rank 2 Magi.

As they fought, they moved further and further away as if deliberately trying to avoid this area.

In Reynold’s office.

All of a sudden, Leylin who had been unconscious, suddenly opened his eyes.

At that instant, his eyes turned amber.

Innate spell formation—Eye of Petrification!

The vined human that had been keeping watch over him immediately turned into a grey stone statue.

After his second bloodline transition, this spell and Kemoyin’s Scales had evolved.

Leylin surveyed the area and stretched lazily, fixing the Ring of Sobriety that was on the round table back onto his finger.

“Though the process was a little unexpected, nothing bad happened.”

Leylin’s eyes were very clear. Where were the traces of him being caught in a hallucination?

Previously, Reynold had used a few ingredients and set up a trap, which had indeed cause him to fall into a hallucination.

But that was just for a moment. The power of the bloodline of the ancient being, the Giant Kemoyin Serpent, was flowing in his veins and devouring all external substances!

His vitality of over 25 degrees had made it easier for him to quickly come back to his senses.

At that time, Leylin had beat Reynold at his own game and pretended he was still in a daze, thus lowering Reynold’s guard.

With the help of the A.I. Chip, his breathing, his body’s situation, and waves of his spiritual energy had been feigned spectacularly, which even deceived Reynold.

All that nonsense about the Branded Swordsmen was obviously just that—lies. With the adjustments made by the A.I. Chip, making up runes was a simple matter.

Only now did Leylin have the time to really look at the rank 2 Magus Reynold’s office.

Based on his interests, the office was made of plants. The bookcase and window, as well as the tables, chairs, and even a few strange books were all made of plants.

The entire setup was very clever and wasn’t very big, giving off a cosy and tiny feeling.

“Where is the place at which I need to place the spell design for it to activate?” Leylin mumbled to himself, producing a scarlet crystal from his pocket.

The crystal now was emitting a bright red and was boiling hot.

“Is this… some sensing technique?

Leylin touched his chin, using the crystal to discern the direction in which he should be moving.

He eventually found out that when he pointed the crystal at Reynold’s desk, it would emit the brightest light and be the hottest, to the point that he felt his hand was being burnt.

Following the crystal, he came before Reynold’s desk.

This was a large green table with rings on it that indicated the age of a tree.

*Weng Weng!*

At this moment, the crystal in Leylin’s hand exploded in a ring of light and mysteriously hovered in the air.

“This is… a spell formation that is triggered automatically!” Leylin’s eyes widened, and he pointed his right hand at the crystal, causing tendrils of black gas to crawl onto it like snakes.

*Crash!*

Under the shine of the scarlet crystal, the dark green desk suddenly shook, and most of the papers, quill, ink and various items on top of it rolled off of the surface.

The surface kept squirming, and the various types of plants making up the table began to grow and extend.

*Pak!* The green desk was split into two, and under these two parts, numerous plants grew and acted like little feet which scurried away.

In the place where the desk had been, there was now a huge pit.

In the heart of the pit was a huge sealing spell formation that was shining with all sorts of runes that were floating around.

On the surface of the spell formation, there were a few gaps. After making some comparisons, Leylin figured that the spot right at the middle could fit the red crystal.

“Classified information like this actually got out, and there was even a spell design specially made for this…” Leylin mumbled to himself.

All of a sudden, something strange happened!

The scarlet crystal that had been hovering in midair suddenly burst out into blood red flames, zooming like a fire arrow towards the part of the formation that was caved in.

In the crystal, there was a requirement that required it to make contact with the spell formation before it was activated.

Combined with Giant’s obvious attempts at hiding the truth, Leylin could easily tell that it wouldn’t be good if the crystal activated.

However, there was no sense of flustering on his expression. Rather, there was a profound look on his face.

“I’ve been waiting for this!” He reached forward with his right hand!

“Snake Binding!”

The little black snakes that had been crawling on the crystal immediately began to squirm and turned into a huge snake ball, securing the red crystal within.

Black gas pervaded the area, on the verge of concealing the red light the crystal was emitting.

*Weng Weng!*

The red crystal constantly expanded, and Leylin seemed to hear a sound of unwillingness from within.

“As expected, there’s even a backup plan! It’s a pity…”

Leylin rapidly chanted incantations and sprinkled some light blue powder into the air.

“Freezing River!” As he finished the last syllable of the incantation, a light blue light surrounded the snake ball.

*Tssss!* White threads of mist were produced, and on the surface of the snake ball, the white mist condensed and turned into a layer of thin ice.

The amount of ice became greater and greater, until, at the end, a thick layer of ice had been formed around the snake ball. The entire snake ball seemed like it had turned into a huge ball of ice.

The red rays of light that the crystal had been producing was now completely contained within.

As if it had lost its detection abilities, the large spell formation in the pit ceased its rumbling, and all sorts of runes ceased to move on the surface of the formation.

*Shua! Shua! Shua!*

Three large ice pillars were like pylons, or perhaps chains, as they connected with the blue ball of ice.

“Hn! The power of this sealing spell formation is not half bad!” Leylin nodded in satisfaction.

This sealing spell formation was something he had gained from blackmailing Pierre at the Four Seasons Garden. It was definitely something worth being kept safely in the warehouse as it was quite effective. It looked like Pierre had not given him inferior items to go against him.

Leylin then shifted his attention to the spell formation that was caved in in the middle.

“A.I. Chip! Compare the runes on the spell design!”

A blue ray of light brightened in his eyes and shone straight at the spell formation.

A huge amount of data flashed past Leylin’s eyes.

Countless runes and designs were currently being compared.

The red crystal from before was merely a key. The runes used on it were strange, and Leylin previously had no way to tell its function from the runes.

But now, both the key and the keyhole were here. Hence, he was able to make comparisons between the runes on both ends and tell the rough functions of the spell formation and crystal.

Seconds later, the A.I. Chip’s conclusion appeared before Leylin.

“The part that’s caved in is a sealing formation, and the crystal’s function is to detonate?”

A cold look emerged on his face as Leylin read through the first two lines. “Very good, Giant! Just you wait!”

The A.I. Chip’s robotic voice continued to intone.

Chapter 238: Scapegoat

[From the energy emitted by the spell formation, analysis shows that the probability of a body of consciousness residing in the spell formation is 78.9%.]

The A.I. Chip’s conclusion was presented before Leylin.

“A body of consciousness?!” Leylin’s eyes sparkled.

“Can you compare it with the database and find out what sort of body of consciousness it is?”

[Searching… Beep! There is no such information in the database. Comparing with Host body’s existing memories…]

The A.I. Chip operated quickly.

Seconds later, a new conclusion was shown to Leylin: [The body of consciousness emits an aura that comes from the Eternal River Plains’ secret plane. Determined to be a special being from the secret plane itself! Compatibility with large platinum gate of entrance to the secret plane: 67%.]

“Platinum gate?” Leylin’s eyes widened, suddenly thinking back to the platinum gate that seemed like an ancient existence, right across from the headquarters. Incomplete spiritual force waves were emitted by the gate!

“From the looks of it, I’m afraid that the platinum door has already evolved to have its own intelligence. However, it was removed by Magi from Four Seasons Garden and sealed here. Hence, its spiritual force waves gave me such a strange feeling…”

Leylin slowly came up with the entire process that led to this result.

Though he had no idea why Four Seasons Garden sealed the consciousness of the entrance to the secret plane, there were only a few reasons that Leylin wasn’t going to bother wondering about.

What he was more focused on was what would happen to the entrance to the secret plane if its consciousness was destroyed.

After all, the red crystal that Giant gave him was no unsealing spell design! Instead, it would control the spell formation as well as the consciousness within, and destroy them together!

“A.I. Chip! Simulate the consequences of the destruction of the secret plane’s body of consciousness.”

Leylin spoke quietly, his expression dark and dreadful.

[Beep! Mission established, beginning to compare with high-level patterns. Importing data…] The A.I. Chip intoned loyally.

After which, the result was placed before Leylin.

[Based on simulated experiments and remnants, if the body of consciousness is damaged, the possibility of the platinum gate being destroyed is 79.8%. Entrance will automatically close and be sealed shut. Another 15.2% chance of the opposite happening. The entrance will then become a public entrance and be open to any living beings… the last 5% possibility has unknown consequences!]

Leylin, who was silently reading the conclusion, suddenly understood everything.

The most important part in the battle for the Eternal River Plains’ secret plane was the acquisition of the entrance. Seven entrances had been discovered, with four being controlled by the light Magi.

This control referred not only to the Magi army set up on the outer areas but also to a certain key that could control the opening and closing of the entrance!

From the looks of it, these keys referred to each gate’s core body of consciousness!

“If I detonate this area, there’s a large probability of Four Seasons Garden’s entrance disappearing. The dark and light Magi will then hold the same number of entrances and there won’t be any disadvantages when trying to take over the secret plane.”

Leylin could easily tell the intentions of the dark Magi.

These Magi were planning to destroy the entrance here!

Gaining control of the entrance meant obtaining a large amount of land, plentiful resources, as well as a huge number of troops. Most importantly, the speed at which spoils of war were transported would be increased!

Light Magi currently held possession of four entrances. Whether in terms of the areas with radiation or potential battle power, they exceeded the dark Magi by a large margin. Hence, the dark Magi had to think of ways to make up for this handicap!

Even if this place was not destroyed, it was still necessary to rob this place from the light Magi. They would rather have this place become a public domain than let it be controlled by the light Magi!

“Shrewd! A very, very clever plan!”

Leylin, who had made sense of this whole situation, couldn’t help but praise the person who had come up with this operation.

However, as the very last chess piece in this game, he was in a very difficult position.

If he destroyed the body of consciousness now, the gate to the secret plane would immediately be damaged and perhaps permanently lose its abilities. This may or may not be a good thing.

Leylin, who had completed this task, would be held in high regard by the dark Magi, but the light Magi would definitely not let him off so easily.

This was a decision that he needed to think through carefully. Just for that little bit of merit, was it actually worth it to offend the entire light Magi alliance?

“Is there still… a need to consider any further?”

Leylin’s eyes brightened.

“From this crystal and the extremely opportune timing, it looks like there’s someone in the shadows controlling everything. This person also has to have a high position in Four Seasons Garden, or else it’d be impossible for him to do this much… I’m almost sure of who it is! Once this operation is over, he’ll be the one reaping the most benefits. I might even be labelled as a traitor and be chased to death, while he will get the most merits for everything….”

Leylin’s lips quirked in a cold smile.

Since ancient times, a spy’s position was the most difficult. Even if they succeeded, if the person who instigated the operation was not willing to tie up loose ends, the spy would be the one who would stand to lose the most!

Besides, compared to a lowly spy like him, there was another spy with a higher position, had been in Four Seasons Garden longer, and was an even more loyal choice.

If there were conflicts of interest between them, who would Thousand Meddling Hands choose? This was a rhetorical question.

Besides, the contract he had signed with Giant only specified that he could not help Four Seasons Garden, but the reason he was doing this was for his own benefit. With his own desire to get some benefits from Four Seasons Garden, it was evident that he would not suffer any backlash from going against the contract’s terms.

Afraid that Leylin would not agree, Giant did not dare to make the conditions too strict. If the conditions stated that he had to destroy specific things, then Leylin would definitely investigate further and could decide not to sign the contract at all.

“Shatter!”

Leylin clenched his fist while facing the blue ball of ice!

*Ka-cha! Ka-cha!” Countless shards of ice fell from the ice ball, and immediately after, innumerable cracks appeared on the surface of the ice ball.

*Crack! Crack! Crack! Crack!*

Finally, the entire light blue ball of ice cracked and along with it, the red crystal dispersed into powder.

This spell design that would cause the spell formation to implode was destroyed by Leylin, just like that!

Leylin had thought this through.

It was alright to betray Four Seasons Garden. At most, he would have become the enemy to one more organisation, but destroying the gate of the secret plane would mean offending the entire light Magi alliance!

The current Eternal River Plains’ secret plane was a huge chunk of flesh that dark and light Magi alike were waiting for an opportunity to swallow into their stomachs!

The gate to the secret plane did not belong to just Four Seasons Garden, but the entire light Magi alliance! Four Seasons Garden was but one of the characters who would look over the entrance. The moment Leylin destroyed the entrance, all light Magi forces would lose their advantage in this battle!

Since ancient times, destroying a person’s livelihood was akin to murdering one’s own parents. For Magi, the secret plane was a huge gold mine where one could obtain a limitless amount of top grade materials! If he pitted himself against the light Magi like this, he would be chased to the ends of the earth and there would be no end to it!

On top of that, all of the light Magi powers would be working together to exterminate their enemy! The dangers of this operation were way above that of the times previously when he had gathered spirits and plundered brazenly!

In the south coast, light Magi were at the top. If the entire light Magi faction was against him, it was impossible for Leylin to stay alive. All he could do was find a deserted place and live a hermit’s life.

If he had connections in the dark Magi alliance things would still be fine.

This operation would be a huge gain on the dark Magi’s side, and based on his huge contribution, he would have a comfortable life with the dark Magi.

It was a pity that Leylin had entered Thousand Meddling Hands halfway through and was not as trustworthy. Otherwise, he would not have been deceived into doing this.

Besides that, he had no backing in the dark Magi alliance and rather, had some foes within!

After all, Abyssal Bone Forest Academy was a member of the dark Magi alliance. He had brazenly killed off the elder of the Lilytell family, Metallic Lunatic Marb, which resulted in a blood debt!

After considering the matter carefully, Leylin concluded that exploding the gate to the secret plane did not benefit him at all, and he would have actually become the scapegoat!

Leylin was definitely not going to do something that would harm his own interests.

Hence, with one last look at Reynold’s office, he ruthlessly left!

……

*Rumble!*

Within the headquarters of Four Seasons Garden at the Eternal River Plain’s secret plane, immense energy waves from spells exploding could be felt everywhere. Mixed within those sounds were miserable cries and maniacal laughter.

The dark Magi’s attack, this time, was very fierce and they had quickly made their way to the centre of the headquarters.

Hence, Leylin found very few official Magi along the way. Nobody bothered to interrogate him either, so his whole journey out was very smooth sailing.

Many Magi in black cloaks were freely venting their dark desires, and some Magi could be seen bursting into flames.

The violent flames engulfed the area and turned the prosperous and busy trading centre into a sea of fire.

The official Magi of Four Seasons Garden were doing their utmost to hold back the dark Magi while awaiting support.

The Magi who had chosen no sides were around mostly to look on without lifting a finger, while only a few who were on good terms with Four Seasons Garden chose to participate in the battle.

Magi were a bunch of cold people, and seeing that the dark and light Magi were participating in a large-scale battle, most of the Magi present chose to look after their own hide and observe.

This was obviously the case for acolytes.

While official Magi were fighting, they did not even have the chance to intervene. Usually, just a stray wave of magic from an official Magus could cause a large number of deaths.

“Things seem to be rather chaotic!” Leylin laughed without care.

Though he was wearing the attire that belonged to Four Seasons Garden, the expression on his face was very composed and as cool as ice, as if everything happening here had nothing to do with him.

“Magus Leylin, what are you doing?”

At this moment, a figure rapidly appeared before Leylin. It was Dolorin.

This vice team leader of the defense squad cut quite a sorry figure, his white robes torn into shreds.

Chapter 247: Flaming Serpent

Faced with the little boy’s head exploding like a watermelon, the green mist distorted, revealing a heavily muscled figure that was more than 2 meters in height. For a moment, his head was visible, but he covered his head, his eyes bloodshot and glowing red.

“You actually…… You actually killed him……”

Giant roared, as if the little boy was very important to him. Seeing Leylin unceremoniously kill the little boy instead of letting him go, Giant was on the brink of going ballistic.

Tendrils of green mist rushed towards Leylin, looking like a swarm of moths and bees, and appeared to envelop Leylin like a huge cloud.

*Chi Chi!* Green meridians crawled over the muscles of Giant’s body like small snakes. Then his body grew instantly, increasing in height by more than three meters. The hairs on his head stood straight up, facing the sky like small thorns.

“Why are you in such a hurry? Are you afraid?”

Leylin sneered, and immediately, black smoke billowed from his body, rising and dispersing into the air.

A trace of the black gas condensed to form numerous black snakes.

The bodies of those black snakes had fine black scales, and each had a pair of bean-sized eyes that exuded an unnatural, devilish red light. The snakes constantly hissed, and went to meet that green swarm of bees and moths.

*Peng!*

For a moment, the two big groups — the wisp of green gas and the den of black snakes — immediately mingled, and there were all kinds of sounds of biting, hissing, and other sounds all constantly emanating from within the green mist.

“Ah! I will kill you, I swear! I shall break all the bones in your body; I will make you regret being born into this world!”

Giant howled as he crouched and jumped.

*Boom!* A huge pit immediately appeared on the ground, soil and rocks flying outwards like bullets, and creating sparks in the air.

With this momentum, Giant’s body was like a fiery arrow heading straight for Leylin.

“Kemoyin’s Scales!” A layer of fine black scales covered Leylin’s hands, from which spreaded rings of black light. The black colour from the scales turned even more vivid, and vaguely formed a design that was similar to a rune!

Following which, the muscles on Leylin’s arm bulged, and his strength of 20.1 was then displayed!

*Boom!*

Green and black figures fiercely slammed into each other, explosions continuously sounding out.

The two human figures flickered as they fought. Anything that the shockwaves from their battle brushed past, whether it was rocks or wood, would immediately explode into pieces.

*Bang!* Leylin’s left hand blocked Giant’s fist. As quick as lightning, his right hand turned into a claw, blood-red flames burning as it headed straight for Giant’s chest, where his heart was.

Currently, Giant’s two hands were rendered immobile by Leylin, and it was basically impossible to evade an attack that was so close.

Giant’s expression became resolute and he adjusted his position, avoiding that fatal claw at his chest! However, his right chest had been caught by Leylin’s Crimson Palm, and a huge chunk of flesh and blood flew out.

“Bone Piercing Technique!” Giant yelled, and his arms spread wide. Not dodging nor avoiding any attacks, he charged straight for Leylin.

*Tss! Tss! Tss! Tss! Tss!*

White bone spikes rapidly pierced through Giant’s skin, growing out from inside his body.

*Ka-cha!* Leylin’s right hand was the first to be struck by the bone spike.

There were some spiral designs on the bone spikes that, upon contact, drilled into whatever it hit.

The revolving spikes first broke through the crimson flames, and then struck the surface of Leylin’s right arm, which was covered in Kemoyin’s Scales.

The extremely piercing sound of metal scraping against metal sounded; it could also be said to sound like a woman’s screams. Leylin’s brows furrowed, and he quickly moved back.

“Haha! If you’re only thinking of leaving now, it’s much too late!”

Giant laughed heartily, ignoring the blood that was gushing all over his body, and spread his arms. His posture was like someone giving a bear hug, he brought his arms together and was ready to prick Leylin till he became like a porcupine.

“This distance… Shadow Stealth!”

A large amount of light appeared on the surface of Leylin’s black, scaly armour. He then disappeared into thin air.

“You thought that I wouldn’t have prepared against this?”

After losing track of Leylin, Giant looked around and suddenly shouted, and then breathed in deeply.

Two streams of white gas that even the naked eye could see entered Giant’s nostrils like dragons, bulging his chest to a noticeable degree.

After this, Giant made a lengthy howl, “Awooooo!”

The piercing sound travelled in all directions, and one could even see ripples in the air, with Giant at the epicentre.

An entire layer of the ground was peeled off by the soundwaves, and the green fog of moth and bees in the air, as well as Leylin’s little black snakes, exploded from the soundwaves, turning into vapour.

The fog was pushed further and further away by the soundwaves and eventually disappeared.

As Giant’s voice increased to a higher pitch, the insects and moles in the area simply exploded in the air, forming a bloody mist.

*Weng!*

With some undulations in the air and a flash of black light, Leylin’s body flickered from his camouflage.

“I found you, you damned worm!” Giant snarled, the spikes on his body growing more densely and constantly rotating. He was like a human killing machine, charging ahead blindly and turning all the trees and rocks that obstructed him into powder.

“Latent Fireball!” Leylin’s gestured, and countless black fireballs converged into a giant jet black, flaming fireball.

With the added bonus from Leylin’s elemental essence conversion, the latent fireball currently had a power of 57 degrees. It could even be said to be the maximum amount of power that a rank 1 Magus could produce!

The moment the black fireball appeared, the temperature of the surroundings rose, and the earth began to melt, with some of it evaporating into black smoke.

“Go!”

Leylin pointed at Giant, and the black fireball kept stretching until it formed a python that blazed with black flames.

The python’s eyes were brimming with intelligence as it nimbly floated around, sometimes spitting out flames and blocking Giant’s path.

Giant’s eyes were fixed on the flaming serpent, the fear in his expression more apparent. Being able to manipulate such a powerful spell that required immense precision showed Leylin’s immense talent in this area. His rate of improvement had far exceeded Giant’s expectations.

“Hisssss!”

The flaming black serpent hissed while coiling around Giant’s body.

*Ka-cha!* The black flames that brought blazing heat with them crashed into the white armour made of bone spikes!

*Rumble!* The raging flames constantly ascended, turning into a giant black inferno.

At the heart of the inferno, Giant’s figure that was filled with bone spikes stood silently within, looking quite pale.

The air constantly distorted, shrinking inwardly and seemingly turning into a black hole. It kept sucking in all matter around, getting smaller and smaller.

*Rumble!*

Then, a huge black mushroom cloud gradually rose from the ground.

Immense energy waves constantly dispersed in all directions, to the point that even Magi from both factions who were battling at the Four Seasons Garden’s headquarters could feel this power, which could destroy the heavens and the earth!

“Has the two great rank 2 Magi’s fight brought them here?”

A young light Magus stopped what he was doing, “What do we do? Should we go take a look? Those are rank 2 Magi! I’ve never seen one fight before!”

*Pak!*

Immediately after, the back of his head was firmly struck. The youthful light Magus turned back and pitifully looked at a Magus with a white beard, “Teacher! Did I say anything wrong?”

The old light Magus’ face was full of wrinkles, but his eyes sparkled with wisdom. He did not hesitate in the least and struck the young Magus’ head again.

“Why are you still in a daze? Get out of here! Just the aftershocks from the rank 2 Magi’s battle is enough to annihilate you without leaving a speck of dust behind!”

The old Magus was obviously very wise and had many life experiences. He knew that this high-level battle between Magi was a disaster for regular people and even low ranked Magi such as themselves!

“Hm? What?”

The young light Magus had yet to react.

“Look!” The old Magus yanked him by the hair and made him look in the direction of the battle.

At this moment, the young Magus suddenly discovered that the dark and light Magi who had been battling had all given up. as if they had reached a mutual understanding, and were moving in the opposite direction of the mushroom cloud.

“Do you see that now? Only a rookie like you would even think of watching a battle between rank 2 Magi.”

The old Magus pulled the young Magus along as he spoke, green hurricanes under his feet as he used invisible gusts to wind to send both of them far away.

……

In the middle of the black mushroom cloud.

The previous explosion had left a large crater that was more than ten metres wide. At the heart of the pit was a seemingly bottomless hole that was sending out black luster, as if it was a direct pathway to the core of the earth.

*Boom!*

A white human figure surrounded by green mist fell to the ground, along with shards of bone that had shattered.

*Pak!* Giant struck the ground, carving out long troughs as his body ploughed through the floor.

He looked to be extremely pitiful, with more than half the bone spikes on his body gone and his right arm missing. There were serious injuries all over his body.

*Xiu!*

A black figure appeared in front of him, and what appeared next was a pair of phantom, blood-red flaming claws!

“Crimson Palm!” Leylin, on the other hand, was completely fine. He was also very satisfied with the strength of the latent fireball, which he had released with his full strength.

There was no expression on his face as he calmly dealt out the final blow to Giant!

Giant struggled and crawled a little, but the phantom crimson claws mercilessly caught hold of his two legs.

*Ka-cha!*

Giant’s legs snapped, and there were even crimson flames climbing towards his body from the legs.

Chapter 248: The Appearance of Rank 2 Magus

“Giant, when you first decided to exploit me to detonate the seal, did you ever imagine that things would turn out like this?”

Leylin slowly walked forward, a strange look in his eyes.

He calmly raised his blood-red right hand, preparing to send out another magical attack!

*Xiu!* At this very moment, a figure separated from Giant’s body, the energy waves from its body indicating that it was also a peak rank 1 Magus! It pounced towards Leylin at a very high speed.

“Eye of Hallucination!” After this command, an apparition of a vertical eye appeared behind this figure.

The apparition let out dusky light with various colours flashing past. Anyone who even chanced a glance at it would be dazzled and feel dizzy.

Two black magic artifacts in the form of daggers appeared in the figure’s hands, moving like a viper as they struck towards Leylin’s vital areas.

This attack was very sudden, and the assailant was a peak rank 1 Magus who specialised in sneak attacks. Even if it was a Magus like Marb, he would suffer greatly!

Strangely enough, there were no signs of shock on Leylin’s face. Instead what appeared was a grin as if he had expected it.

“You’ve finally appeared?”

Next, a cross-shaped, dark red pendant over his neck produced large amounts of dull red rays of light, and his body was covered with a layer of dense scales.

Leylin’s eyes had also turned into amber vertical pupils. Two rays of petrifying light were shot out of his eyes, piercing into the apparition of the vertical eye.

“Ahh!” Ashen gray rays of petrification ripped open the apparition, and a circle of petrification spread throughout the body of the black figure, causing him to yell miserably.

“Crimson Palm!” Leylin’s hands were covered with three layers of protection. The innermost layer was black — the Kemoyin’s Scales. The middle one was a dull red — an apparition from the Falling Star Pendant — and the outermost one was the protection from Crimson Palm’s flames.

The three layers produced different colours as they alternately sparkled on Leylin’s hands.

Leylin welcomed the two black daggers that were headed for him.

*Boom! Boom!*

Though the black daggers emitted the energy waves of middle-grade magic artifacts, they bounced away from Leylin.

Leylin’s Crimson Palm then unhesitatingly struck the chest of the black figure.

*Rumble!*

It was obvious that the black figure’s chest had caved in, and it was coupled with the ear-piercing sound of bones breaking.

*Boom!* The figure was flung to the ground, revealing a Magus that Leylin was very familiar with.

“Team leader Caesar, what are you doing here? And can you also explain why you chose to appear in such a strange way?”

Leylin came before Caesar and enquired.

From his tone, it was obvious that Leylin was not surprised at Caesar’s appearance here.

“Cough cough…” The dark figure who had launched a sneak attack was, as expected, Caesar.

However, he looked to be in a bad state, constantly coughing out blood, and his face ashen. Around his third vertical eye on his forehead, there was a ring of gray stone. This was the effect of the Eye of Petrification, and it was still spreading.

“You…… When did you find out?” Caesar did not reply to Leylin’s question, and instead, countered with another question.

“From the very beginning! In all honesty, I really admire you for daring to train in “Three Spirits In A Body”, which is an extremely dangerous ancient secret technique. You actually succeeded and forcefully separated your spirit into three portions!”

Admiration was apparent in Leylin’s expression.

He had previously used the A.I. Chip to simulate Caesar’s trump card, and then heavily researched about ancient secret techniques like these.

Even in ancient times, these kinds of techniques were considered to be very dangerous. Only lunatics would choose to train in them, as they forcefully separated a Magus’ soul into three parts, each having their own will, and having the ability to be spread apart or merged together in crucial moments.

In other words, a person would be separated into three individuals. As long as a single body remained alive, the other 2 bodies could be resurrected given enough resources.

This was basically a secret technique that defied the heavens.

The situation was now very obvious.

Caesar, Giant, and the little boy were the different bodies of a single Magus who practised “Three Spirits In A Body,” and Caesar was a spy who was buried the deepest in Four Seasons Garden, and the instigator of this entire thing!

Leylin had found it strange that the Thousand Meddling Hands knew so much about the Four Seasons Garden, were able to come up with a spell design to destroy the seal linked to the core body of consciousness, and possessed a map of the locations of the defense squads.

From the looks of it, with Caesar, the leader of the hunting team, as a spy, everything made sense.

Caesar forced a laugh, “It’s far from a success. Originally, if the boy had been able to become a peak rank 1 Magus as well, I would have been able to merge all three bodies and try to advance to become a rank 2 Magus! It’s a pity, though…”

While speaking, a ring of stone-like skin had spread from the sides of Caesar’s third eye, almost reaching his nose.

“Why did you lure us here?”

Caesar asked while lying on the ground, without activating any defence formation. He was now aware that he would not be able to withstand even a blow from Leylin and was not going to humiliate himself by trying to protect himself.

“You’re smart! I want to make a trade with you. I hope that…”

“No! Don’t listen to him! Kill him! I want to kill him!” Giant, who was seriously injured, began to yell.

Leylin sighed as he held his head, “Looks like I have to take care of all the troublesome matters first!”

He could clearly tell that out of all the three bodies that Caesar had, only Caesar himself was relatively sane. Giant and the little boy obviously had a few screws loose, which might have been a side effect of the technique.

The little boy’s craziness was possibly even a level above Giant. After his death, his maniacal tendencies were transferred to Giant.

Out of everyone present, Caesar was probably the only one willing to listen to his proposition. Giant was just an obstruction!

At this thought, Leylin’s eyes were filled with a murderous aura; he was prepared to act right away!

Even if Giant and the little boy died, Caesar would still be able to revive them given a lot of resources, and as long as he was still around. It would just take a little more time.

Caesar and Giant were currently heavily injured, and it was impossible for them to fight back.

“Young man, can you stop now?”

Just as Leylin was about to move forward and deal the final blow to Giant, an aged voice sounded by his ear.

A silver ring of spiritual force descended upon the battlefield.

This spiritual force was incredibly malicious and strong, to the point that the air was distorting. Silver spiritual force formed a large hand, which picked up Giant.

The silver hand formed out of spiritual force was extremely sturdy. The flames from Leylin’s Crimson Palm were still burning fiercely, but there seemed to be no effect on the hand.

Grains of solidified spiritual force constantly fluttered around, slowly extinguishing the crimson flames on Giant’s legs.

“Spiritual force solidification!”

As he watched the silver, solidified spiritual force, Leylin suddenly thought back to the Gargamel that he had seen previously.

That being formed out of evilness also had the strength of a rank 2 Magus, and at that point in time, Leylin was basically helpless against it.

“A rank 2 Magus from the Thousand Meddling Hands?”

Leylin halted his footsteps.

The silver hand sent the heavily wounded Giant before a Magus donned in black robes.

This Magus was tall and slender but was surrounded by a terrifying spiritual force that even Leylin was fearful of. His eyes were a sparkling green, and anyone who saw him would feel immense fear from the evilness they gave off.

“Father! Father! After killing my ‘little boy’ spirit, he actually tried to kill me, the only member of your bloodline! He must pay the price in blood!”

Giant curled up beside the dark Magus, beginning to wail like a little child.

Caesar, on the other side, called out ‘Father’, his face ashen.

“So this dark Magus is actually Caesar’s father!” Leylin realised. However, something that the rank 2 dark Magus threw over made him feel anxious.

It was the head of a Magus. Its skin was pale, and its face was full of wrinkles. Leylin was extremely familiar with this face, as he had actually seen it not long ago.

“Reynold! You actually killed him!” Leylin’s eyes widened.

This rank 2 Magus was even more powerful than Leylin had expected, to actually be able to behead Reynold, who was also a rank 2 Magus!

*Pak!* at this moment, the petrification on Caesar’s face had extended to his neck, and his expression was still as if he had become a statue.

*Rumble!*

A streak of green flames began to burn, and the dark Magus traversed through space and arrived in front of Caesar.

“Ancient Petrification Technique?” His voice was hoarse, like two metal pieces scraping against each other.

“Don’t worry, my child!” The dark Magus extended a pair of thin arms, which had green spores on them, and caressed Caesar’s stone head.

*Bzzz!* Milky white light descended onto Caesar’s head.

Within the light, greyish white stone skin fell off bit by bit, revealing Caesar’s original skin tone.

“Thank you, father! Also, he…” Caesar began to whisper in the dark Magus’ ear, and the Magus constantly nodded.

Upon seeing this scene, Giant, who was not far away, glared furiously like a child who had his sweets stolen. There was even some jealousy as he stared hard at Caesar.

“Aren’t you all the same person? Are you jealous of yourself?”

Leylin was speechless.

At this point, Caesar was done speaking. The rank 2 Magus turned his gaze to Leylin.

A powerful burst of spiritual force was fixed upon Leylin, to the point that he felt as if he was standing stark naked in a field of snow.

Chapter 249: Concede

“Your name is Leylin, and Blood Rogue is your alias, yes? Very good! You actually dared to thwart my plan!”　　

The dark Magus laughed coldly, and suddenly made his move! 　　

　　

Silver solidified spiritual force controlled the energy particles in the air, turning into a large, colourful tide that was several times larger what Leylin was able to produce. It rushed towards Leylin like a tempest, covering the heavens and the earth.

“So strong! Whether it’s to catalyse or cast a spell using solidified spiritual force, the effects are far greater than that of us rank 1 Magi with our invisible spiritual force!”

Leylin’s expression was grim as his pupils turned amber.　

Behind him, large amounts of dark energy particles converged, turning into the terrifying form of a large, black python.　　

The python was ten metres long, its eyes were the same amber colour as Leylin’s, and the scales on its body emitted rings of black rays while it kept hissing.

*Rumble!* The python slammed into the tide of elemental particles like a huge ocean wave crashing against a reef, producing a monstrous sound like that of said ocean waves.

In the midst of the colourful rays of light, the apparition of the black python and the elemental wave were extinguished. Immense pillars of wind rose towards the heavens and then rushed down low, before forming immense gales that swept across the surrounding area.

Leylin quickly retreated four or five steps, his face pale, and two streams of blood dripping from his nostrils.　　

“Hoho, you’re not half bad! Out of all the rank 1 Magi that I’ve seen, you’re probably the strongest. You’re currently bordering a rank 2 Magus!”　　

The dark Magus was unmoving, the only sound being the wind rustling his clothes.

“But it’s a pity! A rank 1 Magus is still only rank 1, and there still remains a huge gap between us! The feeling of personally killing a genius is really making me feel intoxicated…”

The dark Magus mumbled to himself, the dark green light in his eyes suddenly intensifying to the point that it started to solidify into two beams of light.

“Anguished Howl of — Cough cough…”　　

Just as the dark Magus was about to attack, the light from his body began to flicker, and he started to violently cough.　　

Rings of green light flashed as things that looked like plants began to emerge from his body. The green spores on his hands began to sprout, and green plant tendrils grew and spreaded across his body.　　

“So, killing a rank 2 Magus like Reynold was not without a price.”　　

While observing this scene, Leylin came to a conclusion. The dark Magus must have suffered some serious injuries in killing a rank 2 Magus like Reynold. 　　

This was advantageous to him for the next part of his plan.　　

At this moment, the platinum gate to the secret plane suddenly rumbled. The energy waves produced were very distinct, to the point that Leylin could feel them from his current location.　　

Afterwards, an unknown existence that must have been at least a rank 2 Magus passed through the gate of the secret plane and approached them.　　

“You darn dark bastards! Receive the judgement of lightning!”　　

This voice was full of anger, seemingly full of raging flames.　　

*Hualala!*　　

Countless blue bolts of lightning that were like crazed serpents scattered all over the sky and fell like raindrops.　　

*Ka-cha!* An electric current that was as wide as a bucket struck a dark Magus who did not have the opportunity to dodge.　　

This dark Magus immediately turned into ashes in the midst of the lightning, his body crumbling away.

*Boom! Boom! Boom!* The platinum entrance to the secret plane spat out light. Every time it flashed, groups of light Magi descended into the area.

These light Magi were dressed in uniform, and the metallic smell of blood was apparent on their bodies.　　

Compared to the dark Magi, who were already experts in battles, the division of work between the light Magi was even more efficient. The Magi who were specialised in battles were extremely experienced in bloody battles. Some even had a strength that rivalled the dark Magi!

With the help of these light Magi, the tide was turned. Rather than the Four Seasons Garden, the dark Magi of Thousand Meddling Hands lost their advantage.

“They’re here! The reinforcements from the light Magi Alliance!” Leylin mumbled.

He quickly glanced at the dark Magi, who were being suppressed by the bolts of lightning.　　　

“Look, my lord! The reinforcements of the light Magi have arrived. Are you still confident in destroying the gate to the secret plane?”

Leylin gave a slight smile as he asked.　　

“No, but I think this little bit of time I have left is enough for me to kill you before I retreat!” The dark Magus was silent for a moment, and then sneered.　　

“Is that so?” The rune of the suction spell formation on Leylin’s back lit up, and a brownish-yellow spell formation emerged in front of his chest.　

In that moment, a brownish-yellow light covered the earth, and the gravity around the area intensified by a factor of almost thirty.　

“The ancient suction spell formation and the gravitational spell formation? You’re actually using both of them here?”　　

There was a subtle hint of fear in the dark Magus’ voice.　

With the added bonus of these two spells, even if he were in his best condition, he did not have the confidence that he would be able to take down Leylin. Presently, his strength was depleted and his opponent would definitely be able to escape.

“I’m actually still on the dark Magi’s side. After all, a leopard can’t change its spots!”　　

Leylin spoke hurriedly and quickly, “Rather than completely destroying the gate to the secret plane, I believe that gaining possession of it will be of even more value.”　　

His voice had a bewitching quality to it.　　

“What does that mean?” The dark Magus asked coldly but stopped his attack.　　

“Currently, Reynold’s already dead, the team leaders of all the main divisions are dead, and Caesar and I may very well be the Magi with the most authority here! The reinforcements from the light Magi will have to leave eventually. Once that happens, and before a new member is assigned here from headquarters, we’ll be the people with the highest authority, and will consequently be in charge.”　　

Leylin was expressionless. “Once that happens, we’ll continue to cooperate with you in secret, and give you access to the spell formations and defence formations here. Wouldn’t that make everything easier?”　　

It must be noted that this was a very attractive proposal, and was very much viable. After Leylin said this, he could even feel the dark Magus tremble a little.　　

The dark Magus considered for a while, and then solemnly presented this question.　

“We can assassinate him or make him a scapegoat. Anyways, all we need is some time. By the time headquarters finds out what had happened, we’d be long gone…” Leylin answered swiftly.　　

“What do you think?”　　

The dark Magus glanced at Caesar, who was already standing.　　

Caesar was silent. “I think it’s possible. Considering that our original plan has already failed, the situation can’t possibly get any worse than this!”　　

There was actually something else that both Leylin and the dark Magus had not pointed out. 　　

When that happened, even if the rank 2 dark Magus would be able to escape, his sons, Caesar and Giant, would definitely die here!　　

Leylin was, of course, not so daring as to blackmail them so blatantly, but his hidden threat had been understood.　　

“I don’t trust you! Unless you let me give you a branding of your consciousness…” The dark Magus slowly spoke.　

“Impossible!”　　

Leylin resolutely refused. Though receiving a branding of consciousness was slightly better than receiving a branding of the spirit, who knew what a rank 2 Magus could do? He didn’t want to be in a situation where he was unknowingly being controlled.

Leylin had a rascally attitude.　　

In front of real power, only a person with a strength that others would be jealous of could have the guts to say this.　　

Though Leylin was not yet on equal grounds with a rank 2 Magi, he was confident that he could survive and escape, resulting in his more brazen attitude.　

“A contract with the Trial’s Eye. That’s the furthest I can go.”　　

The dark Magus pondered silently, and then responded in a low voice.　　

“…Fine!” Leylin hesitated for a moment and then agreed.　　

“As compensation for helping you, I’ll need a large amount of resources and magic crystals, as well as some high-grade knowledge. After this, you also have to guarantee that I’ll be able to enter Lighthouse of the Night. All of these things have to be written into the contract…”

The Magi acted quickly, and minutes later, the dark Magus left with Giant.　　

Leylin glanced at Caesar, who was standing strangely, with a smile appearing on his face, “Team Leader Caesar! Do you need me to help you back?”　　

After signing another agreement that could be said to be very harsh with the Trial’s Eye, Leylin and Caesar were now allies once more.　　

In the eyes of the light Magi, the sight of two Magi who were always at odds with each other suddenly becoming friendly was quite strange. However, for the dark Magi, this was just an everyday occurrence. In the dark Magi faction, all sorts of battles happened everyday. Betraying one’s alliance for the prospects of more benefits was very common.

“Then I’ll leave it to you!” Caesar glanced at Leylin and actually let him assist him back.

Doing something like exposing one’s vulnerabilities was unthinkable to the dark Magi, but Leylin could understand what he was thinking.

Previously, Leylin and the rank 2 Magus from the Thousand Meddling Hands had agreed and signed another contract.　　

Through the Caesar’s scrutiny of the contract, the conditions were very harsh. In order to prevent Leylin from making use of any loopholes, Caesar had practically gone through the contract word by word.　　

He had basically made it impossible for Leylin to do whatever he wanted, not even giving him the chance to go back on his words.　　

As he had to deal with a rank 2 Magus and the dark Magi alliance, Leylin could only be placed at a slight disadvantage.

In other words, the moment Leylin expressed bad intentions towards Caesar, the power of the contract would devour him before he could even use his magic.　　

Hence, Caesar was quite trusting of Leylin now.　　

“We need to work quickly for our objectives regarding Wade!”　　

Caesar’s lips moved slightly, his low voice travelling into Leylin’s ear.　　

As the one in charge of the hunting team, which actually had true authority, Caesar had a very high position in the Four Seasons Garden. He was second only to Reynold, and only a handful of people could match his authority.　　

What was even more coincidental was that a few peak rank 1 Magi had died on the battlefield for a variety of reasons. Some had even been personally killed by Leylin!　　

As long as Wade was disposed of, Caesar would immediately be in control of everything!

Chapter 250: Lightning Corp

Leylin reflected briefly.

Currently, in the entire Eternal River Plains’ secret plane, the Four Seasons Garden had received a fatal blow.

Other than Reynold, a great elder, the combat and defense team leaders had all died in battle. The person in charge of the merit points exchange centre had been killed by Leylin, and it was unknown whether Wade, the envoy from the headquarters, was dead or alive.

Leylin was stunned at the discovery that in the headquarters of Four Seasons Garden in the secret plane, there might only be two peak rank 1 Magi here — Caesar and himself.

Under these circumstances, it would be an easy task to exploit his authority in the headquarters.

Though the headquarters in the external world was sure to react quickly, dispatching large numbers of Magi and even rank 2 Magi here to investigate, that would take time!

Caesar and Leylin could use this time to further diminish the power of the Four Seasons Garden and create opportunities for the dark Magi.

By the time the light Magi found out, the battle array of the defence would have been controlled thoroughly by dark Magi, and the situation would be set.

Even if there were to be another large war, with the dark Magi in charge of four entrances and three under the light Magi’s control, the dark Magi would have an advantage.

Leylin had thrown out such tempting bait, which was how he had gotten the dark Magus to bite!

“It’s Lord Caesar! And Patrolling Inspector Leylin!”

As they approached the headquarters of the Four Seasons Garden, the figures of Leylin and Caesar were quickly noticed by the large remaining numbers of the light Magi. The surviving members quickly came forward to greet them.

Leylin ran his eyes over everyone. These Magi’s robes were in tatters, and there were traces of dust and blood on their faces. To all these Magi who had seen Caesar and Leylin, it was as if they had seen the pillars of their organisations.

“It seems like the loss of the higher levels in Four Seasons Garden is worse than I thought!”

Leylin admitted to himself that in the time he had been a patrolling inspector, he’d done nothing good, instead extorting much from every department. However, after these Magi saw Leylin, they gathered and greeted him, their enthusiasm surprising him to no end.

Unfortunately, there were no longer any peak rank 1 Magus in the Four Seasons Garden. That meant that Caesar and Leylin were the only two peak rank 1 Magi on the light Magi’s side, which was why they were welcomed with such enthusiasm and ardent hope.

“If they found out that Caesar and I were the instigators of this recent attack, who knows what expression they would be wearing…”

Leylin was slightly dumbfounded, but he still put on a solemn expression.

“May I know who currently has the highest authority in the Four Seasons Garden?”

At this moment, a Magus with lightning designs on his silver-white robes separated the Magi and approached them.

“I’m Caesar, the team leader of the hunting team. This person here is Magus Leylin, the newly appointed patrolling inspector.”

Caesar’s face was pale as he spoke.

“We are the Lightning Corps of the light Magi alliance. The leader of our corps would like to meet you.”

The Magus’ expression was blank, as if he was incapable of expressing emotion. Not caring about Caesar’s serious injuries, he forged ahead and led the way.

The surrounding Magi of the Four Seasons Garden cowered and did not dare to move forward.

Compared to a something as large as the light Magi alliance, the Four Seasons Garden was just one of many allies. Also, every single member of the Lightning Corps was at least a semi-converted Magus, which would make them equivalent to the elites of the Four Seasons Corps. Their numbers were greater, and the leader was coincidentally a rank 2 Magus, which was something they could not contend against.

Leylin shrugged his shoulders, met Caesar’s gaze, and walked on.

They were naturally familiar with the headquarters here. After walking through an area with destroyed walls, Leylin and Caesar met the leader of the Lightning Corps in a temporary guest hall.

“Are you Caesar? 19 years ago, we met at Reynold’s wine reception!”

Unexpectedly, this Magus knew Caesar.

Caesar quickly bowed in greeting, “So it’s Lord Desmund!”

Leylin ducked his head and bowed slightly, chancing a glance at this rank 2 Magus.

Desmund had a blue robe draped over his sturdy body, which proudly displayed his chest and bulging muscles. Under his blonde fringe, there was a blue lightning mark on the forehead.

What garnered the majority of Leylin’s attention was Desmund’s eyes. Every time they blinked, slight electric currents flickered; it was rather astonishing.

“Where did you go?” The rank 2 Magus asked right away.

“My lord! I was previously leading the hunting team in a battle with the dark Magi, which resulted in many casualties. In the end, even I sustained injuries, and it was thanks to Magus Leylin rushing over that I managed to survive…”

Caesar began to narrate a story that he had previously made up.

The gist of it was that he had been defeated in battle, but had been saved by Leylin in the nick of time.

This was a version that he had previously discussed with Leylin, and they had recorded all of the casualties as well.

Of course, Caesar was the sole culprit for the annihilation of his own team members, and the two of them had also shifted a few dark Magus corpses from elsewhere to create the illusion of a battle.

With a rank 2 Magus helping to conceal this matter, it was a large possibility that they would not be found out.

What made Leylin feel relieved the most was that Desmund merely had asked in passing; he nodded, and did not continue with more questions.

Though they were all part of the light Magi alliance, Desmund was an outsider, after all. These were things that required the Four Seasons Garden to dispatch their investigation team and investigate everything properly.

“Hm! You two peak rank 1 Magi, and also Wade, would be the Four Seasons Garden’s final force.”

Desmund looked solemn.

*Teng teng!*

Caesar fell back a few steps, his face full of disbelief, “The last force? Does that mean… Lord Reynold…”

Seeing Caesar’s Oscar-worthy acting skills, Leylin was speechless. Although Leylin had appeared to be shocked, his expression was formed with the manipulation of his facial muscles by the A.I. Chip.

If not, with his current acting skills, he would have definitely been seen through by Desmund, a sly old fox. No matter how boorish he looked, he was still a rank 2 Magus, and he would not lose to anyone in terms of intelligence or observational skills.

In comparison, Caesar’s performance was remarkable.

“No! I don’t believe it! Lord Reynold is a rank 2 Magus, and…” Caesar’s eyes glazed over as he kept muttering.

“Though I also find it hard to believe, this is the truth. Reynold has fallen… I felt the extinguishment of his life force. Unfortunately, I arrived too late, else I would have definitely been able to save him. I’m sorry…” Desmund touched his chest, his expression showing regret.

“As Reynold’s good friend, I will inherit his dying wish and carry out revenge on the dark Magi!” This corps leader guaranteed.

“Thank you, esteemed lord!” Caesar’s face showed his resolution. “After I’m healed, I will immediately apply for missions to take revenge!”

“Hn!”

Desmund nodded, and then clapped his hands.

*Rumble!* The floorboards at two ends of the temporary room split open, and a large, translucent, metallic pillar rose from the middle of the room.

The sounds of turning gears sounded from the heart of the pillar. Streams of glowing runes constantly travelled upwards, creating a magical sight.

“This is the core control of the Four Seasons Garden’s defensive formation! There had been a powerful interference, and the procedural spell design also had some issues. Don’t worry about that though, as I’ve already fixed it. Based on the rules stated in the alliance’s proposed laws, I now announce, in my capacity as the leader of the Lightning Corps, the formation of the Four Seasons Garden’s Crisis Team, which will be in charge of the defensive and spell formations. The members will consist of Caesar, Leylin, and Wade. If you have differences in opinions, you should decide based on the majority’s decision.”

Desmund spoke as if he were reciting, and circles of light that represented a contract and celebration twinkled around the three of them.

“Now then, complete the ceremony for the formation genie to recognise its master!”

Desmund pointed at the metallic pillar in the center of the room. “Press your palm on it. The formation genie will automatically record the aura of your spirit and give you authority.”

Caesar nodded, and then placed his palm on the surface of the metal pillar, closing his eyes and seemingly communicating with a body of consciousness.

Moments later, while beaming with admiration, he withdrew his hand.

“Your turn!” Leylin nodded and also placed his hand on the pillar.

The surface of the metallic pillar was very glossy, and there was a strange feeling when he touched it. It was very soft, as if it were not metal, but rather cotton.

It was also different from the iciness of metal. The surface of this pillar gave Leylin a rather warm feeling.

“Recording spiritual aura! Conferring an authority of seven stars!”

A robotic female voice sounded in Leylin’s mind. It was different from the A.I. Chip’s genderless voice, and was instead a crisp feminine voice.

“Is this a formation genie?”

Leylin was a little rueful. Whether science or magic, when it came down to it, there were basically different means to achieve the same end.

However, this formation genie obviously did not have any intelligence, and could only robotically answer Leylin’s queries.

Communication with this conscious was quick, and in a quick ten seconds, Leylin was able to largely grasp what his authority extended to, and the function of the formation genie.

This formation genie was the core of all the defensive spell formations that the Four Seasons Garden had set up. Through the formation genie, one could easily check any single region.

However, this spell formation had previously been heavily interfered with by the dark Magi, which resulted in the unexpectedness of the attack this time.

As for the limits of his authority, this referred to how much manpower he could command. The chain of command consisted of a total of nine stars, with one having the least authority, and nine commanding the most. Leylin currently had a ranking of seven stars, and was therefore capable of dispatching most of the defensive forces in the Four Seasons Garden to besiege anybody, as well as having access to all available information, save a few top secret documents.

In the past, Reynold had had nine stars, and was capable of ordering the formation genie to self-destruct!

Leylin, Wade and Caesar were merely granted seven stars temporarily to deal with this emergency.

Chapter 253: Divulged

“Goro! It’s you!”

Wade glanced at one of the few surviving members of the Four Seasons Corps, his tone displaying his regret.

That day, he had sustained serious injuries, and practically all of the small team from the Four Seasons Corps had died. All that was left was Goro. As he had fainted because of the explosion, he had narrowly escaped death.

At the sight of Goro, Wade couldn’t help but think back to that scene.

Explosion! Figures! Green mist!

Everything had happened so suddenly that even his secretary who was also his girlfriend, had died in the attack.

“Now, even Goro is probably ridiculing me as well.”

Wade shook his head as he thought, and spoke in a hoarse voice. “What’s the matter?”

“My lord, I’ve brought you your breakfast!”

Goro placed a silver tray on the table, on which were fruit salad, white bread, and steaming hot milk.

“Thank you!” Wade was silent for a while before he spoke.

“My lord, please be careful!” Goro bent his head slightly and quickly left.

Wade did not have much of an appetite, but for the sake of his teacher and as well as his own wellbeing, he still forced himself to go to the dining table.

He picked up a slice of white bread, preparing to slather some jam on it, but a slip of paper sandwiched in the loaf caught his attention.

Wade retrieved the slip and spread it out.

After being in contact with the warmth of Wade’s fingers, rows of little letters appeared on the originally white paper.

“Danger! Dark Magi have infiltrated the headquarters and are planning to attack you. Leave immediately!”

The words were very strikingly written in red.

Wade stared hard and immediately got up to set up a few detection and isolation spells.

Next, with some astonishment, he focused on the slip in his hands.

“Like I thought, the dark Magi’s attack was way too ferocious, and they knew too much about our defense system. The formation genie was also interfered with, and could not be used at all. There has to be a spy!”

Hatred appeared on his face, “If not for there being a spy, we definitely wouldn’t be in this position, and even… Teacher Reynold wouldn’t…”

His fists were clenched tightly, to the point that a few drops of crimson blood flowed out through the bandages on his hands.

“I’ll definitely find you and avenge my teacher. I swear on it!”

A glint of resolution appeared in Wade’s eyes, and he then rubbed the slip of paper in his hands.

“The paper used is the most ordinary parchment paper. The words were designed to show after coming into contact with my body temperature, so the sender has to be someone I’m familiar with. If he was able to warn me, that means that he’s very clear on whatever’s happened here, but… who could it be?”

Face after face appeared in Wade’s mind, but he quickly pushed this thought down.

“It’s not the time to think about this. Danger? Does this mean someone is planning on attacking me? Within the headquarters?”

Wade didn’t quite believe it.

*Pu! Pu! Pu!*

At this moment, explosions sounded in the air, and numerous black needles as fine as cow hair penetrated the air. They were sharp glints in the air, launching towards Wade like raindrops.

“Really?!”

A green shield of vines appeared, and the numerous thin needles struck the surface and produced sparks.

He then dropped to the ground and rolled!

*Boom!* A black dagger punctured the area that he had previously been, and the bench split apart like tofu. Even the air had been cut, producing two pure, white gusts of wind.

*Tss tss!* From the area where the chair had been sliced, the sound of an object corroding was heard, with much white smoke accompanying it. The bench that Wade had been sitting on was corroded in a few seconds, not even leaving behind any residue.

The person holding the dagger was a dwarf-like figure.

The dwarf was surrounded by a layer of black gauze, and his movements were extremely agile. After seeing Wade avoid the attack, he pounced towards him like the wind. The black dagger was like the tooth of a poisonous snake, searching for Wade’s weak points.

“Formation genie, activate the defense spell formation here, and inform the Lightning Corps!” Wade looked pitiful as he dodged a few attacks, and quickly swiped at a ring on his hand.

*Boom!* Green mist exploded at the scene, and with this chance, he began to yell.

“Order received! Activating defense at Zone B-7… Beep! Received a different command, cancelling out both. Your authority has temporarily been superseded!”

A robotic female voice sounded by Wade’s ear, causing his heart to sink.

The formation genie had control over a large area, which practically included the entire headquarters of the Four Seasons Garden at the Eternal River Plains’ secret plane. The moment he activated the power of the formation genie, he would definitely be able to break away from danger and arrest this killer.

But now, the enemy was even able to control the formation genie! Didn’t this mean that the headquarters was now being controlled by the dark Magi?

A huge sense of fear suddenly made itself known. Despite the strong defense here, he could not feel any security and rather, felt like he was being caged in.

At this moment, the green mist in the room dispersed, and the dwarf-like killer’s eyes had a cold glint within them. He seemed to transform into a black hurricane, which swept towards Wade.

*Teng! Teng! Teng!*

Outside the room, footsteps kept sounding. The guard Magi who were outside had heard noises inside and quickly rushed here.

The dwarf suddenly flung something, and the dagger in his hand turned into black lightning, streaking across the air and flying straight for Wade’s heart!

“If I weren’t seriously injured and cursed, this type of attack…” An unresigned expression appeared on Wade’s face, and he quickly tried to avoid the attack.

*Pu!* The black dagger stabbed his shoulder, leaving behind just the handle exposed.

Large amounts of fresh blood spurted out, and Wade’s face paled as he collapsed.

The dwarf quickly ran forward, preparing to deal the final blow!

“Protect the lord!” At this moment, the door to the room was forcibly kicked open and was turned into wood shavings. A few Magi wearing uniforms with lightning designs on them broke in.

Seeing Wade collapsed on the floor, they roared, and a few people produced blue and white electric currents.

The bolt of electricity arced across the air and arrived in front of Wade.

*Pak! Pak!*

The blue and white electric arcs struck the dwarf, causing green smoke and the smell of charred flesh to spread throughout the room.

The dwarf’s body trembled, before he glared hard at Wade as if staring at his prey, and suddenly threw two black balls to the ground!

*Poof!* A large amount of black gas billowed out and concealed the dwarf’s figure. After the gas had dissipated, the dwarf assassin had already disappeared.

“My lord, are you alright? Inform and warn Lord Caesar and Leylin about this!”

The Magi of the Lightning Corps supported Wade and then instructed.

Half an hour later, Wade had already moved to another room, his injuries having been treated. However, while he glanced at his surroundings, terror was beginning to engulf him.

The assassination attempt just now made him feel like something was wrong.

Within the headquarters, an assassin had actually managed to enter without obstruction and suppressed the activation of the formation genie! What did this mean?

“Who could be the thief who seized the authority to command the formation genie? Or is it Caesar? Leylin? Did they both join hands?”

Wade was expressionless as the gears turned in his mind.

“No! The headquarters are extremely dangerous, and there are too many hidden enemies that I don’t know of. If things really are like the what slip of paper said, where the dark Magi have infiltrated here, I’m in even more danger…”

Wade glanced around his surroundings. A few Magi were patrolling the area, walking back and forth. After the attack, Caesar had brought over guards, but all he could feel were bad intentions in their gazes, causing him to sweat profusely.

“This isn’t going to work. I need to leave here as quickly as possible; it’ll be best to meet with the academy’s investigation team!”

Wade’s eyes showed his staunch resolve.

“What? Wade’s missing?”

Leylin glanced at Caesar, shocked.

“How did this happen? You couldn’t even carry out such a simple task! He must be suspecting us now!” In front of Leylin was the three-eyed Magus, Caesar, who did not look to be in a good mood.

“Even if he’s an idiot, he’ll definitely know there’s something up with both of us after his authority in using the formation genie was suspended. If he were to report this to the investigation team…”

“That’s impossible!” Leylin shook his head.

“The entrance to the secret plane is in our hands. I’ve checked all the recent records of people entering and exiting; there are no problems. Communication between the secret plane and the external world is very unstable, and the few communication towers we have don’t work unless we use a spell formation exclusively for communication. Unfortunately, with our access to the formation genie, we can seal this entire area and turn him into a caged bird!”

“So the only thing he can do is to escape to other light Magi regions!” Caesar added.

“Exactly! A very daring decision!” Leylin nodded.

The area of the Eternal River Plains’ secret plane was enormous, and the distance between each entrance was vast. One even needed to pass through a few extremely dangerous zones.

The difficulty would be too much for Wade while he was in his best condition, much less while he was cursed.

“This is your problem. You solve it!” Caesar answered in annoyance.

“Alright! This situation is actually what we wanted, though, isn’t it?”

Leylin got up while he continued speaking. “Desmund has been transferred away, and nobody knows whether Wade is dead or alive… In these next few days, he won’t have the chance to communicate with any Magus from the external world. Hence, the entire headquarters of the Eternal River Plain’s secret plane now belongs to us…”

Chapter 256: Threats

“I guess I should let you know!”

Seeing this old lady acting like this, Leylin suddenly found her quite pitiful and lost the urge to play with her any further.

He waved at the few guards. “You may return first.”

“Yes, my lord!” The guards gave Leylin a deep bow, appearing as if a heavy weight had been lifted off their shoulders, and quickly dashed out of the room.

“Wait! What did they call you? My lord? Aren’t you just a regular Magus from the Potioneering Team? Aren’t you also ostracised?”

The old woman spoke agitatedly. She could feel that things were beyond her control as if a stone had lodged deep in her heart.

“It seems like you’ve investigated me quite thoroughly! Unfortunately, I’ve climbed up the ranks a little faster than that…”

Leylin spread his hands, a mischievous grin on his face.

Was he merely fast in climbing to this position? He had practically flown here! First, by killing large numbers of dark Magi, he had obtained the position of the vice team leader of the hunting team. With his battle achievement of killing Marb, he had been named the patrolling inspector of the headquarters. In theory, he was just as powerful as Caesar, the leader of the hunting team.

After the attack of the dark Magi and Reynold’s death, he had seized a third of the power within this branch of Four Seasons Garden. But wait, there’s more! After chasing Wade out, the authority he possessed had increased to two-thirds!

His position was infinitely nearing the chairman with this much power! This old woman only had a rank 1 contribution token, which was useless against a team leader, much less Leylin.

Next, the smirk on his face vanished, and his expression turned solemn.

“Formation genie, record this down! This… Ahem! This person who holds the power in the Botelli family overstepped her authority and ordered for my arrest, with a rank 1 contribution token. I hereby announce that she be stripped of the authority and the contribution token in her hands!”

*Weng!* Magical light brightened in the middle of the room, and the walls were filled with a ring of wandering illuminated runes.

“Recorded! Verifying! Verification complete. Removing authority from rank 1 contribution token!”

A robotic female voice was heard, and the rays of light from magic suddenly flashed outwards.

The old lady seemed to be scared silly by such a strong energy wave. If all the spell formations around them exploded in one go, her body would simply vanish.

The colourful magic rays did not attack her, but transformed into a hand the size of an adult, grabbing the rank 1 contribution token in her possession!

Then, the fingers exerted force!

*Ka-cha! Ka-cha!*

The sound of an object breaking sounded. A web of cracks spread across the surface of the entire token, and under the hopeless gaze of the old woman, it turned into little bits of dust.

*Tss tss!* The magical light receded after destroying the token. Even the spell formation on the wall vanished.

The old woman was now like a duck grasped at the neck, unable to utter a word.

She naturally knew the amount of authority needed to be able to order the formation genie to destroy a rank 1 contribution token! That was something only the chairman was able to do! Could it be that this young man had already advanced to become a rank 2 Magus, and had become the chairman of the Four Seasons Garden?

This world was just too crazy. The old woman supported her head, feeling as if she was dreaming!

“How is it? Do you have any other trump cards? You can try using them!” Leylin crossed his arms, staring icily at this old woman.

Her heart fell. Her family was now not in a very good position. This token, which was something their ancestors had left behind, was the last resort, but had been rendered useless without properly being made use of! She herself would even be in trouble upon returning!

“What do you want?”

Her voice was hoarse as if she had aged by ten years. She bent her back, and then released the pride from her tone, completely defeated.

“What do you want?” Leylin sounded innocent.

“Your granddaughter came up to me, saying I’m the main cause of a war and wanted to purify me. I was forced to strike back and gave them a lifeline when I could have simply just killed them. I’m already being very kind, and now you even want to threaten me!”

Leylin was indeed the victim in this affair, except for the fact that he had retaliated with just a little too much strength.

“Jenna is the seer of our generation. Her predictions can’t be wrong!” The old woman persisted.

“You…” Leylin was exasperated but calmed his heart. There was no point in arguing over a trivial matter such as this.

“Alright, now it’s time for me to name my conditions! My requirements are simple. I’m interested in that divination ability of Jenna’s. Impart me this technique, and I’ll release the curse on her!”

“Oh, Mother of Peace! Not only does a sinner like you want to control us, you even dare to covet our family’s meditation technique!”

She clutched her chest as if she was on the verge of going crazy.

“Is it a meditation technique? Or even a high-grade meditation technique?” Leylin was suddenly very interested.

“Don’t even think about it, you monster! Devil! Don’t even think about trying to obtain our Botelli Family’s meditation technique!” The old woman resolutely rejected him, a cold glint that could not be concealed flashing past her eyes.

“Hehe… You may not know this, but the curse on Jenna’s body can only be released by me. Otherwise, you could try finding a Morning Star Magus, or else you’ll just be waiting for a dead body.”

“I’ll give you one day! Think it through!”

Leylin clapped his hands and two guards immediately entered.

“Send this lady away to get some rest. Do not be negligent!” Leylin’s tone was slightly different, and the two Magi who knew what he was implying quickly came before the old woman, ready to take care of her.

Leylin nodded and left.

Though the old woman had concealed it well, the coldness in her eyes was still apparent to Leylin. All that she was thinking had long since been discovered by Leylin.

“Trying to swindle me with a fake meditation technique? No! Magi are intelligent people! If you give me a fake one, I’ll definitely know. If I can’t tell, I can just find a few acolytes and perform tests on them… Unless… If she really gives me a high-grade meditation technique, but it has a very obvious flaw! Only with these conditions will Magi who lack high-grade meditation techniques be tempted to use it…”

“What a pity!” Leylin cracked a smile.

If he was a Magus without a high-grade meditation technique, he would definitely be unable to resist the temptation, and would end up training in it. After all, it represented an increased chance of advancing, as well as insuring a better future.

Unfortunately, he already had a high-grade meditation technique of his own—Kemoyin’s Pupil! No matter how amazing the Botelli family’s meditation technique was, he would only use it as a reference, and wouldn’t do something so stupid as to switch meditation techniques.

With a smile on his lips, Leylin went inside a secret room.

The four walls of this secret room were made of thick stone, with numerous runes that could isolate energy placed all over.

In the middle was a rather strangely shaped, little stone counter. Three pillars supported a triangular section, large amounts of green vines crawled along it.

“Formation genie, activate the communication spell formation!” Leylin spoke.

“Authority verified! Activating communication spell formation!” As the formation genie spoke, a dusky splendour shot out from the little stone counter, and all the runes in the room began to glimmer.

Leylin nodded upon seeing this. Communication between the secret plane and the external world was all but impossible, and could only work through a particular communication spell formation.

This was a specially constructed communication spell formation that could penetrate the isolation effect of the secret plane and was considerably expensive. The Four Seasons Garden only had this one formation in the entire Eternal River Plains’ secret plane.

Before, Wade’s authority to communicate with the outside world was sealed through the combined efforts of Leylin and Caesar. Hence, in a situation where he could not contact anyone, Wade had no choice but to flee.

Leylin took out his own secret imprint book and flipped through to the most recent page. At the end was a blue imprint that looked like a beacon.

Leylin lightly tapped it.

*Boom!* The blue beacon suddenly became bigger, and the runes in the room unceasingly lit up.

A red line shot out of the stone counter, connecting to the surface of the blue beacon secret imprint.

“Is this Sir Hyder? How have you been feeling recently?” Leylin asked, full of smiles.

“It’s… you! Quick! Give me the cure!”

From within the blue secret imprint, a haggard voice came on and off, as if the owner had been severely injured or was being tortured by some illness.

The owner of this voice was Hyder, the Magus who was on good terms with the Botelli Family, who had been invited by the old woman to treat Jenna!

Previously, he had failed in his treatment methods. Not only had he been infected by a poison that Leylin had made himself, but the poison had also come with a communication imprint.

Hence, Leylin was able to know a lot about the Botelli Family.

The grin on Leylin’s face widened. “Sir Hyder, I want to tell you something quite unfortunate! The wielder of power in the Botelli family has already approached me. She implored me to remove Jenna’s curse, but never said anything about you…”

Upon hearing his words, the imprint became quiet, and then came the sound of something breaking. “That whore, that lunatic! To think I worked so hard for her… Cough cough…”

After just two sentences, Hyder began to cough violently.

Leylin’s smile was even brighter. “Sir Hyder! How’s the effect of my ‘Shadow Corrosion’? I spent a lot of effort on it! You’re also a very outstanding healing Magus. I would like to know your evaluation of it!”

After a long time, Leylin once again heard Hyder’s voice from the secret imprint. “You’ve won. The composition of the poison is much too complicated, and they’re intricately linked together. I really have no way to remove it… Give me the cure, and not just medication to suppress it, and I’ll tell you everything I know!”

“Fine! I want to know everything, especially your knowledge regarding the contents of the meditation technique.”

Chapter 260: Another Round

After speaking, Leylin turned to gaze at the bustling market.

Life and death happened all the time, much like the way flowers bloomed and withered away. Everything was being transformed in front of his eyes.

“Nothing in the world can escape the decay of time! This is why I’m so set on seeking eternity, which is something I live by!”

Leylin sighed deeply in his heart.

The rebuilding of this market was not entirely without reason. At the very least, Leylin had gained quite of a bit of experience from managing it. In the future, if he ever needed to take charge of an area where Magi gathered, he knew he could do it much better than before.

Seeing Leylin expression, Caesar snickered inside without showing anything on his face, “Then let us begin as quickly as possible! Someone will move the core body of consciousness today!”

“Alright! Are we finally going to make a move?”

Anticipation flashed in Leylin’s eyes, as they walked side by side as they left.

……

Caliste wore the robes unique to Magi from Four Seasons Garden, and ambled over to the region he was in charge of.

Along the way, acolytes stood by the road and bowed to him. He walked past them expressionlessly, and occasionally nodded aloofly.

“This is it! Respect! Reverence! This is what it feels like to be an official Magus…”

As someone who had just been promoted to be an official Magus, Caliste had yet to adjust to this situation.

Such treatment that was reserved for those who were more powerful than the regular human had him feel a little intoxicated.

However, all these thoughts vanished after seeing the large hole beside the fort.

At the outer layer of the headquarters of Four Seasons Garden, there was a huge hole.

This was the masterpiece done by the dark Magi in their previous attack. Leylin and Caesar had ordered for people to mend this, but it had yet to return to its original state.

As he looked at the light Magi and acolytes who were carrying out construction work, Caliste felt as if all the wounds had been re-opened as they sniggered at him.

This huge wound was a disgrace to all the Magi of Four Seasons Garden!

“Those darned dark Magi! One day, I, Caliste, shall…” Caliste’s complaints and curses suddenly stopped as he recalled the insane power the dark Magi had displayed.

For a Magus like him who had grown up in a safe environment, every movement from the dark Magi, which were filled with bloodthirstiness and violence, made him feel a little stifled.

In this condition, even those who were of the same rank might lose quite badly.

“If they attack once again, will I be able to do anything?” Caliste was filled with self-doubt. After all, it was his luck that had allowed him to survive while other, more powerful, light Magi had died in battle!

“Hah… I don’t care anymore! There’s still the Lightning Corps, large-scale defense, and amplification spell formations here, as well Lord Caesar and Lord Leylin! With this level of power, there’s definitely no problem for us to hang on for one or two more days. Besides, the people from the headquarters are going to arrive tomorrow!”

Caliste exhaled slowly.

*Boom!*

At this moment, green flames suddenly streaked across the sky like a meteor, a tail of light following behind it.

*Xiu!* Accompanying the flames was the piercing sound of friction with the air.

*Pak!* Green flames rumbled as they exploded in the middle of the sky, forming the image of a green skull!

“This is… the symbol of the dark Magi…” Caliste’s voice became hoarse, his expression displaying his disbelief.

“Enemy attack!”

The patrolling Magi bellowed, and layers of black magical beasts charged forth like a tide.

“The biochemical army of the dark Magi! This is an army made out of cannon fodder, formed due to the radiation and poisoning of beasts in the secret plane! The real enemy is still behind. Activate the defense formation and notify the two Lords!”

Atop the watchtower, a Magus who seemed to be the leader of a team icily roared immediately.

“Activate the Heavenly Fire spell formation! Magi on the ground are to prepare wind spells and fire rain scrolls!”

This little leader was obviously the commander of a zone, and he immediately began to seek permission from the formation genie with his spiritual force.

“Formation genie! Activate the energy amplification spell formation again! The targets are all Magi of Four Seasons Garden!”

The energy amplification spell formation was a large-scale spell formation that would cover the entire area of the headquarters at the secret plane. It could cause Magi who were semi-converted and below to have their power to increase by 10%.

“Received request, verifying authority!”

He could hear the emotionless voice of the formation genie in his mind.

“Verification failed! Spell formation will not be activated!” However, the formation genie’s next words seemed to throw him down into the abyss.

“What? It didn’t go through?”

The commander’s face changed and he fiercely smashed the stone railing beside him. *Pak!* A huge chunk of green stone fell.

“It happened again! There’s a traitor!”

He turned his head, glancing in the direction of Reynold’s office. “Is it Caesar? Leylin? Or both of them?”

Magi were not fools in general. The failure to activate the formation genie could be said to be a fluke the previous time, but it had happened again. The scope of people he suspected had been made smaller, and no amount of concealing would work.

Caesar and Leylin did not bother doing that either, as they were already prepared to leave Four Seasons Garden.

“Leader, what do we do?” The female Magus behind him asked anxiously.

“Let’s go!” This Magus looked at the beast horde that was going to arrive soon, and then the platinum gate of the secret plane a distance away. He gritted his teeth and made his choice.

“The situation now is extremely dangerous, and there are also traitors here! The casualties here will definitely be more than the previous time. If you want to survive, leave with me! Immediately! Now!” The leader quickly explained.

He was deemed to be very trustworthy in this team, and a few members chose to leave with him. The rest stayed behind.

At this point, those who chose to stay behind were completely loyal to Four Seasons Garden.

The expression on this commander’s face changed, becoming icy as he led his team members and broke away from the beast wave.

Before leaving, he turned back to look at Four Seasons Garden’s defensive line.

Though the ranged spell formation of the formation genie could not be activated, there were still a lot of defense Magi who chose to stay behind. Hailstones, storms, flashes of lightning and thunder, and fire raining from the sky could be seen on the defensive line.

“I’m sorry!” This leader apologised in his heart and immediately turned to leave.

Magi were a bunch of logical and practical people. The team leader was very clear that the enemies were very aggressive in their attacks, and they even had a highly-ranked spy to provide support. The Magi of Four Seasons Garden here would not end up well.

As the defense Magi battled with the army of magical beasts, immense energy waves swept through Four Seasons Garden.

In a second, Four Seasons Garden was in chaos once again.

Wandering Magi with no affiliation thought back to the previous time this happened and quickly chose to leave. Acolytes were as powerless as ants in this situation, and they could only wail in hopelessness.

On top of that, a few Magi also took the opportunity to conduct some illegal activities, and in a short period of time, the sound from quarrels, wails, and on top of that, the roars from magical beasts coupled with the aura of magic traveled throughout the region.

“How terrifying! Oh Four Seasons, did my nightmare reappear?”

“Too terrifying! It’s too terrifying!”

Caliste mumbled away. As a defense Magus of Four Seasons Garden, it was his duty to protect his homeland. However, his legs were becoming jelly and started to shift backwards.

*Boom!* At this moment, half a body, from which the other half had been ripped off by a beast, fell from the sky. As the corpse dropped, it sprayed a rain of blood that covered his entire face.

“Ah…” Caliste’s facial muscles twitched, and he no longer hesitated to run in the opposite direction.

While running, his lips moved slightly and a ring of green energy particles appeared, causing his weight to decrease by half.

A layer of dense earth armour also emerged on his body.

“I’m sorry…” While Caliste dashed off wildly, he apologised in his heart…

*Boom!*

Just when he passed by a building, the building suddenly began to shake violently, and then exploded in flames.

The wave of flames and heat spread out in all four directions, with sparks and rocks flying everywhere. A few acolytes who were nearby turned into ashes instantly in this explosion.

*Bang! Bang! Bang!*

Caliste had his innate defensive spell formation, so he was physically alright. However, a few larger rocks had struck his chest, causing him to pale and fall backwards.

“What happened? How could the dark Magi enter so quickly?”

Confusion was apparent on his face, which would be the last expression that he would ever make.

*Tss!* A large crimson sword that was still burning with yellow flames pierced through this Magus’ innate defensive spell formation, sticking into the area where his heart was.

“So there was one more official Magus here! I almost let him escape!”

Behind the cold voice, a Magus in black robes appeared before Caliste’s corpse and pulled out the crimson sword!

He gazed at the ruins around him, unexpectedly producing a crazed look of enjoyment, “Kill! Cry! Only after feeling the deepest sense of hopelessness will my Weeping Skeleton Sword be able to exhibit its most formidable power!”

He glanced at the acolytes around him that were completely stunned, and the sword in his hand began to flame once more, charging into the crowd of Magi.

Corpses that piled as high as mountains, blood that flowed like the sea!

Caesar had brought in many elite dark Magi troops secretly using his authority, situating them at various core areas and had them unleash attacks together!

Immediately, Four Seasons Garden was turned into a sea of flames once more! Dozens of areas went up in green smoke. Dark Magi brazenly slashed and killed as they liked, venting their innermost desires…

In this situation where attacks were coming from both within and outside, Four Seasons Garden was definitely not going to last long.

Chapter 262: To Inform

It wasn’t as if there was no way to undo the contract with the Trial’s Eye. The last time, Thousand Meddling Hands had given Leylin the solution of the Nefarious Filthbird feathers which had destroyed one side of the contract.

What made Leylin more uneasy was that this liquid had come from the hands of Cabourn, this rank 2 Magus!

Though it was impossible to find another solution of the Nefarious Filthbird feathers, for Magi like them, they did have ways to achieve a similar effect.

After all, the people behind Thousand Meddling Hands was the Dark Magi Alliance, which had at least a rank 3 dark Magus in charge!

If Leylin actually believed in that contract, then he must be a fool!

Caesar in front of him was a very good example! He was a Magus of Four Seasons Garden that was highly regarded. The force of the contract on him must be even stricter, and yet he had been able to betray Four Seasons Garden without the slightest hesitation. He must have used some method to break away from the effect of the contract.

Hence, though they had stated in the contract that they would not attack each other, Leylin did not take this to heart.

Just as expected, the rank 2 Magus had outrageously attacked him after obtaining what he’d wanted, not caring about the effects of the contract. This meant that he had destroyed his side of the contract.

Fortunately, Leylin had been wary of this rank 2 Magus from the start and been able to improve his strength after modifying his heart. Only then was he able to take on the attack.

“How… How were you able to retaliate? How are you able to break away from the influence of the contract?”

Cabourn first disregarded his shock at Leylin’s strength, and first asked this question.

The contract with the Trial’s Eye was not something to be made light of, otherwise it would not be used so extensively.

Besides its mortal enemy the Nefarious Filthbird, there were few other ways to deal with this sort of contract.

Even he himself needed guidance and help from the rank 3 Magus in charge of the Dark Magi Alliance and paid a large price to eliminate the limitations of the contract on his end.

The meaning of ‘eliminating the limitations of the contract on his end’ was to remove the effect of the Trial’s Eye on him, while Leylin would still be bound by the contract.

In other words, he could attack Leylin, but Leylin would not be able to strike back. The moment he did, the Trial’s Eye would punish him!

It was because of this that he had been so fearless and brazen in wanting to eliminate this untrustworthy factor first!

However, the powerful effects of Trial’s Eye did not work on Leylin. How could this not surprise him?

“Could it be that Leylin also trained in some magic that is similar to “Three Souls in a Body”?” Cabourn was beginning to realise that he could not fathom this young Magus.

His son, Caesar, had used the special effects of Three Souls in a Body that allowed Caesar to violate the contract with Four Seasons Garden. He had died once, and after the effects of Trial’s Eye had completely disappeared, he had come back to life and thus evaded the power of the contract.

Cabourn did not think Leylin had any rank 3 Magus aiding him, and the only other way for this situation to happen was that he trained in some ancient techniques!

“Fools!”

Cabourn glanced around coldly, and then coldly hummed. Due to the immense explosion, they had exposed themselves entirely to the light Magi. There were already a few wandering light Magi that wanted to investigate and find out what was happening.

Their surroundings had turned into barren land, and only the place sealing the core body of consciousness had a layer of black energy guarding it.

A few Magi wearing the uniform of the Lightning Corps had quickly made their way here. The leader was someone Leylin was extremely familiar with. It was the vice-leader that Desmund had left behind, who was a formidable peak rank 1 Magus.

“The Lightning Corps? What an eyesore!”

Cabourn let out a roar as if he had some animosity towards them, and he moved his arms forward, “Withering Breath!”

A ring of silver-gray stream was generated between his hands, and like a tornado violently revolved towards the Lightning Corps.

This stream seemed to have an immense corrosive effect and produced long, deep tracks on the ground. In an instant, it arrived before these Magi.

*Tss tss!*

The stream charged towards a Lightning Corps Magus. With a strange expression on his face, he suddenly began to wither.

In the blink of an eye, this powerful Magus had turned into a dried up corpse and collapsed to the ground.

“Keke!” Cabourn laughed in a way that sent shivers down one’s spine, and the silver-grey tornado killed the Magi one by one. It then pounced towards the face of the vice-leader, who was struck with hopelessness.

“The rank 2 Magus, Deathbringer Cabourn! Lighting’s Fury!”

The vice-leader of the Lightning Corps obviously recognised Cabourn and roared, raised his metal arm and struck towards the tornado!

With his movement, two large balls of lightning appeared in front of his fists.

The huge lightning fists brought with it thunder, flames, and inexhaustible fury, and hissed as it pounced towards the silver-gray tornado in the air.

Unexpectedly, the two lightning fists charged into the tornado and somehow completely disappeared without even having produced a sound.

“Pu!” The vice-leader paled and coughed out black-red blood that emitted some grey gas.

“Keke! Ever since I suffered a loss the previous time, did you think I wouldn’t research your lightning magic?”

Cabourn could not stop with his strange laughter, and the huge tornado continued to howl as it sucked this man in.

*Woo woo…*

The tornado constantly revolved where it was, and in a few seconds, dissipated, revealing the scene within.

*Pak!* A spotlessly white skeleton fell the moment the tornado disappeared, which cracked in many places before turning into powder.

What had been the vice team-leader had had his flesh and blood stripped from him. Even the life force in his bones had not been let off.

Cabourn was able to take care of the Lightning Corps in a single blow. Such fearsome power intimidated the light Magi nearby, and the Magi of Four Seasons Garden unhesitatingly turned to leave quickly.

Though they were loyal to Four Seasons Garden, they were no fools! A person able to kill a peak rank 1 Magus had to have reached the level of a rank 2 Magus! If they went up against this sort of Magus, then they were simply committing suicide!

Cabourn nodded in satisfaction and turned to look at Leylin.

“I’ve taken care of the hindrance. Now it’s time for us to start again…”

Leylin had been standing quietly while Cabourn had attacked and slaughtered the members of the Lightning Corps. Nobody had an idea of what he was thinking about.

“It’s time!” All of a sudden, Leylin exclaimed quietly.

“What time is it?” Cabourn suddenly felt cold, having a bad premonition.

*Weng Weng…*

The sound of something vibrating emerged, and the metal gate to the secret plane across the center of Four Seasons Garden began to buzz.

The Magi were no strangers to this situation. This had happened just once before, and this was when a rank 2 Magus had brought in a whole army of Magi through the gate of the secret plane!

*Tssss!*

Blue electric currents swept along the metallic gate. What had been a cloudless blue sky suddenly dimmed, and dark clouds appeared.

A pair of large hands formed out of lightning charged in through the gate and swept through the dark Magi around.

In an instant, the dark Magi who had been brazenly plundering and looting turned into ash with shock still apparent on their faces.

What followed the large hands was a blonde, burly man with a lightning symbol on his forehead that gave off eye-catching rays.

“Desmund!” Cabourn gritted his teeth as he forced out this name.

Next, he gave Leylin a withering look, “Did you do this?”

Within the Eternal River Plains’ secret plane, the only person who was so clear about their plan and was able to communicate with the external world was Leylin!

What Cabourn just could not understand was how this would benefit Leylin.

What he had done was enough for the Light Magi Alliance to kill him hundreds of times. Even if he disclosed this information, he would still not be let off lightly.

In addition, Leylin had offended both the dark and light Magi, so there was no way he would be in a good situation.

However, Cabourn did not have any time to think about this. Desmund looked at the scene around them, shocked, and blue rays of light floated from the bodies of what had been the Lightning Corps, launching into the mark at Desmund’s forehead.

This burly man was immediately overcome by fury.

“Cabourn, you despicable maggot! A cowardly fool that only knows to run! I’ll definitely twist off your head and trample it for ten thousand years at my parliament hall!”

Desmund roared and covered himself in blue lightning.

*Ka-cha!*

A tremendous lightning bolt split open the heavens and, in a straight line, landed on Desmund’s hand, turning it into a weapon that looked like a pike.

*Xiu!* Desmund’s figure streaked across the sky and appeared before Cabourn.

“Repulsive!”

Cabourn’s eyelids blinked rapidly, and two lines of silver-gray tornados shot out from his hands.

Large tornados thundered and combined into a larger tornado that wrapped him within.

Like a lightning god, Desmund charged into the midst of the tornado, and one could vaguely see two figures wandering within.

The violent tornado floundered around at will, and any Magus which came into contact with it instantly turned into a withered corpse or was burnt to ashes by stray lightning bolts.

“They’re finally gone!”

Leylin glanced at the two rank 2 Magi that were fighting and revealed a smile of relief.

Though he had already modified his heart and was indefinitely closer to the world of a rank 2 Magus and could be said to be the strongest rank 1 Magus in history, he was still a rank 1 Magus! There was still a huge divide behind him and a rank 2 Magus.

Though he had been able to take on an attack from Cabourn, but if they were to continue battling, he was only confident in his abilities to escape.

This was something that was simply unacceptable!

Chapter 267: Scorching Touch

The largest issue Leylin had with this was that the poison worked too quickly, and even he himself did not have any methods to save the poisoned ones.

The poison from the Giant Kemoyin Serpent was not simply a neurotoxin. Some ancient sinister thoughts and intentions had been mixed within, which made it difficult to dispel.

The reason that Leylin was not afraid was because after modifying his heart, he was now considered to be partially a Giant Kemoyin Serpent. Naturally, he would not be affected by his own poison, but it would be too difficult for him to save someone else.

Based on his estimations, even a rank 3 Magus would find it nearly impossible to deal with this poison. Perhaps only a rank 4 Morning Star Magus would have a solution to this.

“Looks like I can’t use this ability as I like! It can only act as a trump card.”

Leylin forced a smile.

The area of attack was much too vast, and it did not differentiate friend from foe. If he used this, it would definitely result in the loss of many innocent lives and give rise to public anger.

Though Leylin would not feel any guilt or shame, he did not want to become hated by many due to a simple accident.

For instance, after seeing all their subordinates dead, the two rank 2 Magi, Cabourn and Desmund, were on the exploding with rage!

“You… You actually…”

Desmund howled, the lightning imprint on his forehead shining crazily, “You actually destroyed my Lightning Corps! I will kill you”

He had brought all the elites of his Lightning Corps here. On top of that, he had left two large armies here. In other words, Leylin’s Toxic Bile had utterly decimated his surbodinates, which caused Desmund’s eyes to turn red. A violent aura undulated around his body.

Compared to Desmund, Cabourn was dealing with this situation much better. After all, he was a dark Magus, and was used to massacres. No matter how many of his underlings were killed, it wouldn’t affect him.

His mind was focused only on the strange spell that Leylin had displayed that intimidated him.

“What a terrifying ability! Is this his innate spell? A toxic area of effect attack that even a rank 1 Magi cannot withstand?”

As a veteran dark Magus, Cabourn immediately began to estimate Leylin’s battle power. He could envision how terrifying such an ability would be in a war!

This was a battle power that had a destructive power that could rival a natural disaster.

“Crap!” Cabourn and Desmund paled at the same time, and their bodies, which were in midair, began to tremble.

A purplish-black gas rose in front of their faces. This was the poison of the Giant Kemoyin Serpent! Even a rank 2 Magus could not completely dispel it!

“Seal of Ten Thousand Poisons!” The lumps on Cabourn’s shoulders exploded, and a red ring of flesh twisted into a circle rune, sealing the purplish-black gas within.

Only after the poison was sealed did he have the time to look at the state of his old rival.

Desmund was in worse shape than he was. Great amounts of lightning were in front of Desmund’s face, and the lightning rune between his brows was moving around, forcing the black poison to coalesce into his right arm. With a resolute look, his left arm struck down as quick as lightning, and he chopped off his entire right arm!

Though Magi could use all sorts of methods to regenerate their limbs, their battle power would be largely diminished if they had just lost an arm.

“Old fart, how are you?” Cabourn and Desmund were old rivals, and in front of Leylin, whose strength was scarily powerful, these two had joined hands to oppose this enemy.

“It’s…it’s nothing!” Desmund huffed. A ring of lightning flashed by his wounds and immediately stopped the bleeding. “It’s just that I can only use 70% of my peak strength. How about you?”

“A little better than that. I can exhibit 80% of my strength. Any more than that and my seal will lose effectiveness…” Cabourn forced a bitter smile, “Leylin actually dared to kill my kin! I will definitely kill him!”

Under Leylin’s all-encompassing toxic attack, Giant, and Caesar, peak rank 1 Magi who were seriously hurt and in a coma, were obviously not spared.

In addition, since the little boy who Leylin had previously killed did not come back to life. Caesar’s three spirits were all dead. In other words, he had really died!

Cabourn was Caesar’s father, and was not on good terms with Leylin. In this situation, he had another grudge, which was for the death of his son!

“It looks like we need to work together!” Desmund looked grim.

“En! I have no idea how that freak trains.” Cabourn and Desmund inched a little closer to each other.

“Sigh…”

Leylin sighed at this moment and approached Cabourn and Desmund.

“Kill!” Leylin initiated the first attack, and huge black fireballs filled the sky like large stars.

At this point, Leylin’s conflict with these two rank 2 Magi could no longer be resolved peacefully. This fight would only end when one side was completely eliminated.

After being promoted to a rank 2 Magus, the might of the rank 1 spells that Leylin used had also obtained a huge boost.

The Latent Fireball now held a power that was more than several levels stronger than when Leylin had used it while being a rank 1 warlock.

Huge waves of black fire streaked through the sky, almost evaporating the molecules in the air into nothingness.

“He’s only just advanced and has yet to record the spell model of his rank 2 spell. Beware of his poison innate spell!”

Cabourn and Desmund exchanged glances. One person produced tremendous amounts of lightning, while the other sent out greyish-black tornados that charged towards Leylin.

Lightning, tornados, and black flames mercilessly collided against each other.

Silver spiritual power split the air, giving rise to a huge spiritual force maelstrom!

Under the manipulation of solidified spiritual power, the rank 2 Magi exhibited magic that far exceeded the might in rank 1 Magi, reducing the Four Seasons Garden’s headquarters into rubble.

Three large silver hands that were over ten metres long wrestled like giants from ancient times.

“Toxic Bile!”

This fight continued for over ten turns, and with a glint in Leylin’s eye, a formless ripple of poison dashed towards the two opposite rank 2 Magi.

This time, even the air slightly rippled.

“Be careful of his poison attack!” Cabourn and Desmund retreated as if they had seen a poisonous snake.

*Weng Weng!*

Formless ripples smashed into the two Magi’s innate defensive spell formations, producing sounds of corrosion.

A strange glint flashed through Leylin’s eyes, and the formless ripples turned into transparent hands that grasped towards Cabourn.

*Pak!* The innate defensive spell formation in front of Cabourn could not withstand the attack from this transparent hand, and a large hole was made.

“Ah! Omni-Decay!”

Cabourn looked torn as he yelled the incantation.

Black tornados whirled in all directions, looking like a black flower bud that was blooming.

*Rumble!” The large transparent hand and black flower collided. Both attacks dissipated, and the stray energy spread outwards.

A transparent tear in the sky exploded, and black spatial cracks formed.

Leylin and Cabourn attacked in two different directions.

At this moment, a sinister smile flashed in Leylin’s lips. With a wave of his hand, a large amount of red powder spread into the air like a red cloud of fire, “Scorching Touch!”

Two lines of fiery energy shot out, and in an instant, they streaked through the air and appeared before Cabourn.

The energy fluctuations from the attack caused Cabourn’s face to change, “Rank 2 magic! How can this be? Hasn’t he only just advanced?”

*Pu!* *Pu!*

The two fiery streaks drilled through Cabourn’s lower abdomen and right shoulder, creating two large wounds that had been charred black.

The reason why Leylin had been in a tussle with these two rank 2 Magi was to stall for time, so that he could analyse the rank 2 spells in the Book of Giant Serpent!

After obtaining the Book of Giant Serpent, Leylin had received three rank 2 spell models. However, while he was still a rank 1 warlock, the A.I. Chip had been unable to make anything of them.

Only now, after his advancement, could the A.I. Chip finally analyse these spell models.

Leylin chose a fire elemental offensive spell and ordered the A.I. Chip to analyse it. With the powerful calculative abilities of the A.I. Chip, the spell model was finally analyzed, and the information was sent to Leylin’s mind.

“Thunder Tempest!” Upon seeing his ally injured, Desmund immediately charged out to help.

A powerful storm of lightning surged up like a wave and swept towards Leylin.

“Kemoyin’s Scales!” Leylin steeled his expression, and fine black scales appeared all over his body.

After advancing to a rank 2 warlock, the scales on Leylin’s body emitted an even deeper black luster, and there were even incomplete patterns on the surface of the scales, which vaguely formed dark elemental rune barrier.

The barrier instantly shaped into a huge, solid black runic shield that situated itself in front of the tempest.

Leylin did not care for Desmund’s attack from behind, and his eyes turned into amber vertical pupils that stared straight at Cabourn, who was quickly retreating while spitting out blood.

“Eyes of Petrification!” From Leylin’s amber vertical pupils, two lines of petrification rays caught up to Cabourn, who was in the middle of retreating.

“Ah…” Cabourn let out blood-curdling screams and covered his eyes, from which a layer of ashen-white stone skin began to extend.

The power of a rank 2 warlock was even more powerful then a rank 1 Magus, and the two rank 1 innate spells Leylin originally had had received a huge boost. Even a rank 2 Magus was affected.

Leylin’s speed increased rapidly, and in an instant, he caught up to Cabourn, who was still fleeing.

There was no trace of emotion in his eyes. The fiery red Scorching Touch was casted again.

Three fiery streaks combined and became as thick as a person’s arm, and penetrated through Cabourn’s brain.

*Bang!*

Cabourn’s head exploded open like a watermelon, and red and white cerebrospinal fluids and blood dripped all over the ground.

*Boom!*

The large black shield shattered, and lightning leaked through the cracks and headed towards Leylin.

*Tss tss!*

Blue lightning exploded behind Leylin, and he turned pale.

Chapter 268: Obliteration

In a region called the Land of Eternal Light.

A castle-like building that was upside-down was somehow standing upright. The defensive runes on the surface of the building constantly flickered. This was where the Botelli Family, who were rumoured to hold divination abilities, resided. Though their power had declined in the past few hundred years, they still retained some of the power from when they were at their peak. Beside the gate to the castle were two strange stone guards.

In front of the gate were two statues with large swords plunged into the ground. These two statues were over ten metres tall and two to three metres wide. Whether it was their appearance or weapons, they gave off an intimidating aura.

Within the castle, in a basement filled with white chilly air.

It was filled with translucent blocks of ice. At the centre of the cold room was a transparent ice coffin. With a pair of hands placed on her lower abdomen, a girl of noble blood and an elegant temperament was quietly lying within.

Though Jenna was still in a coma, the curse on her body was already beginning to spread. Black lumps of flesh and veins constantly spread. On Jenna’s face, black gas would not dissipate, and it looked something like little snakes constantly spiralling.

With these snakes attached to her, Jenna’s eyelids kept moving and she looked to be in immense pain.

It had been almost a month since Leylin had set up the curse, and it was already on the verge of completely exploding.

Without a cure, Jenna would likely end up like Manla, who had turned into a set of dried up bones!

*Boom!* The door to the ice room was pulled open, and the old woman who had met with Leylin walked in.

“Jenna, the guide of our generation! Based on the will of the mighty Mother of Peace, you shall continue to exist in this world!”

The old woman mumbled, and then placed a blood-red key on the freezer.

*Weng weng!* Red rays were emitted from the key and began to seep into the ice coffin. The red light covered Jenna’s body in an instant.

Under the illumination of the red light, the black gas on Jenna’s face began to vanish. The terrifying might of the curse waned at a rate that could be seen by the naked eye.

“The talisman to undo the curse provided by Leylin is effective, as expected!” The old woman looked at the freezer that was emitting red light, and her expression brightened.

After having traded to Leylin the incomplete high-grade meditation technique that was inherited generation to generation in exchange for the talisman, she was able to rush back before the curse completely exploded!

“Leylin Farlier, you sinner! You shall be punished and judged by the Mother of Peace!” The old woman made a few hand signs and prayed in a low voice.

*Drip! Drip!*

Droplets of blood-red liquid formed from the key and penetrated through the layer of ice, and dripped onto Jenna’s pale, snow-white neck.

*Tss tss!* White gas rose from the area on Jenna’s neck that was covered by the blood-red liquid as it began to recover at a visible rate.

*Weng!*

Jenna, who had been unconscious all this time, suddenly opened her eyes!

*Boom! Boom! Boom!* The ice coffin shattered into pieces, and strange undulations traveled throughout the ice room.

The old woman was extremely familiar with this energy fluctuation. This was a phenomenon that happened when their guide was making a prophecy!

“She’s going to start now?” A bewildered look appeared on her face.

“I see countless deaths! Demon king! A demon king with toxic abilities is approaching…”

Jenna’s eyes suddenly rolled back to show whiteness, and a low and gasping voice was heard.

“Toxic? Demon king? Could it be…” The old woman was startled and suddenly recalled the latest news.

*Weng Weng!*

The blood-red key from before suddenly hovered in the air, producing glaring rays of light.

“A tracking imprint? This is bad!” The old woman’s eyes widened!

At this moment, outside the upside-down castle, Leylin in black robes appeared.

“Is this the rumoured upside-down castle? It really is quite strange!”

Leylin lifted his hood and sized up the building in front of him, sighing in admiration.

After killing two rank 2 Magi, he knew that he would be chased by both light and dark Magi factions. Hence, he had changed his clothes and escaped out of the secret plane via another exit.

Though there were strict testing methods at each entrance, these were all tests that picked out the aura of precious materials gathered from the Eternal River Plains’ secret plane, preventing them from being smuggled out.

With Leylin’s abilities as a rank 2 Warlock, it was naturally effortless for him to escape.

As for the sensing of any items, Leylin had placed them in the spatial leather pouch. With the isolation from spatial runes, even the most refined detection spell formations would not discover any traces.

Leylin raised his right hand, and on his wrist, a red key-shaped imprint was pulsating with light.

“It’s here!”

Leylin grinned as he looked at the tracking imprint.

The place where Jenna’s family was located was hard to find. It could be said that even Hyder needed the old woman’s directions in order to enter. There was no real map.

In the trade with this old woman, Jenna’s family’s grandmother did not have good intentions and wanted Leylin to take this incomplete high-grade meditation technique and be taken over by it. Leylin, similarly, was not kind and added a tracking imprint into the talisman.

With the help of the imprint, he was finally able to locate the nest of Jenna’s family.

“Though the high-grade meditation technique, Sacred Flame, is incomplete, it is still unique! Its nature is extremely troublesome, and only one person in the world is able to train in it at a time.”

Leylin’s lips curved as bloodlust overcame in. He did not have a good impression of this egocentric family. Since he’d found where they were, it was natural that he would want to get things over and done with.

“Halt!” The two statue guards at the gate came to life and their muscles rippled as they yelled in a low tone.

“Two magical beings? Together, their power is almost equivalent to a rank 1 Magus!” Leylin’s eyes flashed, already pinpointing information about these guards.

“This level of defense for a Magus family is not half bad!”

Leylin waved his arm and two large black fireballs flew out, meeting the large statue guards that had whipped out their weapons.

*Bang! Boom!*

The fireballs smashed into the large stone swords, and like water engulfed the bodies of the guards. The two guards immediately turned into two huge, black torches that burned furiously.

Under the attack of Leylin’s Latent Fireball, the two statue guards that had been around for thousands of years instantly turned into a pile of black powder.

“Enemy attack!” “Who is it?”

Countless urgent voices sounded in the castle, and then the mournful, piercing sound of a copper bell. The runes on the surface of the castle began to move.

For the defense of such an ancient family, even a peak rank 1 Magus would not be able to penetrate through if it was completely activated.

“Hah…”

Leylin let out a long sigh, and streaks of silver spiritual force extended from his body. His body then mysteriously hovered in mid-air, forming a huge silver face.

“Toxic Bile!”

From the lips of the large silver face, a cold incantation was exclaimed.

The poison from the terrifying ancient creature, the Giant Kemoyin Serpent, soundlessly penetrated throughout the insides of the castle!

The runes outside were entirely useless towards poison attacks. Every single person inside, whether it was an acolyte, servant or even official Magi collapsed to the ground, their bodies beginning to rot.

Not only the castle but in a range of half a km away, all the plants were beginning to dry up and rot.

Silence! The eerie silence of death! It shrouded the area, with the castle at the centre of it all.

In this large area, no being was lucky enough to survive and sunk into the eternity of death.

*Bang!* The old grey gate that still was still full of patterns that had an ancient aura silently toppled.

Under the corrosion of the poison, not only the defensive formation, but even the building itself was affected by the destructive force.

In the granite that seemed to be extremely solid, there were hundreds of thousands of little holes that were the result of the corrosion. The entire building swayed and looked on the verge of falling. Leylin felt as if at a light push, the entire castle would fall with a huge rumble.

In the corridor that was filled with a putrid smell, rotting corpses were everywhere.

Leylin followed the tracking imprint and advanced further, finally reaching the ice room that was far into the castle.

He entered the ice room filled with chilly white gas and saw the two corpses.

The old woman had died extremely painfully, holding test tubes that held all types of antidotes. Of course, there did not seem to be any use in it and her flesh was still rotting.

As an official Magus, her resistance was obviously more powerful than a regular person. Even when dead, her body was still more difficult to destroy.

Chapter 277: First Glimmer of Dawn

*Ding ling ling!*

Accompanied by ringing sounds, an old Magus suddenly appeared on the high platform.

His golden attire looked extremely formal. Beside him were two female servants, who were more attractive than him, holding silver plates. They displayed something that looked like a root and showed it to the Magi below. Surrounding them were multiple projections of enlarged images.

“The Devil’s Antenna is an object retrieved from the body of a beast that had the strength of an official Magus. It has been well preserved within a liquid, and its worth is from two hundred to five hundred thousand magic crystals. It’s a pity that it’s of no use to me anymore…”

Leylin merely scanned the item that appeared on the platform, and immediately lost interest.

“Before the trade meeting begins, is there a need for this auction? How pointless…”

Though Leylin found it boring, the item on the platform seemed to be extremely attractive to the rank 1 Magi below. The shouts of people haggling could be heard, and the auction was extremely lively.

The items on auction by Iron Crown could be said to be of good quality and quite inexpensive, making them highly sought after by the rank 1 Magi.

Magic artifacts, high-level slaves, precious materials, knowledge, and even potions that could increase one’s spiritual force were displayed one after the next, allowing the Magi below to compete with them and choose.

These were obviously not attractive to the rank 2 Magi. Neither Leylin nor the other rank 2 Magi in the VIP rooms shouted out a price.

Leylin simply closed his eyes and rested, using the A.I. Chip to simulate the spell models of rank 2 spells.

Though the spell models of the three rank 2 spells in the Book of Giant Serpents were already in his head, he had realised the other uses of the simulation methods of the A.I. Chip while mending the teleportation spell formation.

Through the A.I. Chip’s simulations, he could actually accelerate his own understanding of the activation and firing of these spells, allowing the once robotic movements to be more agile.

This was a function that the A.I. Chip did not have before and was something that had been created after his advancement.

With this function, Leylin’s understanding and manipulation of rank 2 spells could almost surpass that of rank 2 Magi who had been accumulating knowledge over many years.

“However, the number of rank 2 spell models that I have is just too small…”

Leylin practised Scorching Touch once more and furrowed his eyebrows.

A rank 2 Magus would usually be backed by a powerful organisation that would have no lack of spell models as they would have been accumulated over time.

However, Leylin was different since he was now going solo. Tthe difficulty of this path was exacerbated by the strict regulations for rank 1 Magi in the south coast which were even worse for rank 2 Magi.

Even when he was in Four Seasons Garden, Leylin didn’t even have the qualifications to come into contact with rank 2 spell models.

From killing Cabourn and Desmund, he had gained some experience and realisations regarding the use of rank 2 spells. However, what he lacked was the most important thing— spell models! Leylin only had these experiences as a reference.

“It’s not quite possible to buy this sort of thing using magic crystals. Perhaps if I lie low for a period of time, I can try to use other methods…”

As the auction went on, some items that could attract rank 2 Magi began to appear, and some prices were shouted from several VIP rooms.

At this moment, the announcer’s voice from below attracted Leylin’s attention, “Middle-grade magic artifact— Sabre of the Dawn! This is a sabre found in an ancient ruin, and it is said that its previous owner was a mighty Branded Swordsman. Starting price: five million crystals, or any precious materials of the same value!”

Leylin opened his eyes, and through the transparent glass screen, focused on the platform below.

At this moment, there was a dull-gold metal long sword put on display by the servants behind the announcer.

This long sword was around 1.5 m long and two fingers wide. For Branded Swordsmen, such as Number 2 and Number 3 who used swords that were the size of regular humans, this was merely pocket-sized.

However, a hint of glee appeared on Leylin’s face. On the surface of the long sword of the Rays of Dawn, there were some strange runes which were quite similar to the runes he had branded onto the bodies of Number 2 and Number 3.

“Looks like it’s the real deal!”

He nodded, and a slither of spiritual force quoted a price through the communication device, “Five million magic crystals!”

A middle-grade magic artifact naturally was not so valuable, but this long sword was evidently worthy enough to do research on, which garnered the interest of the rank 2 Magi.

Quickly enough, a price was quoted from a VIP room not far from Leylin, “5.5 million!’

Leylin’s face darkened and he looked towards that VIP room. It was a pity that he could see naught but a blurry shadow.

The glass in the VIP rooms had naturally been processed. Guests could see outside through the glass, but people on the outside could not see anything inside the room.

“Six million!” Leylin immediately increased the price. Other than the magic crystals he possessed, he also had materials he had obtained from the secret plane and the wealth of two rank 2 Magi. This would obviously cause rank 2 Magi to be jealous, and it was natural that he could be so generous.

As if able to sense Leylin’s resolution and immense wealth, the rank 2 Magi nearby stopped raising the price and this long sword became Leylin’s.

“The guest at VIP room 7, please take note! Our staff is bringing your auction item to do the exchange. Please prepare magic crystals or items that are of similar value…”

News travelled through the communication device, and after just five minutes, an expressionless man brought the servant who had been holding the silver plate to Leylin’s room.

“May I know where this long sword was created?” After the delivery, Leylin’s eyes flashed as he questioned them.

“My apologies! This belongs to the client and it is our duty to keep this a secret for him!”

Though they were speaking to a rank 2 Magus, the staff still rejected Leylin’s demands. This exhibited their manners and professionalism.

“Very well!” Leylin nodded and waved for these two people to take their leave.

Next, he picked up the long sword on the table, and gold rays shined in Leylin’s hand.

A regular middle-grade magic artifact could no longer satisfy the needs of a rank 2 Magus. What was more useful was a high-grade magic artifact or even a magic device!

However, Leylin had no desire to use it. He was merely interested in the runes on this long sword.

“A.I. Chip! Scan and record the runes, and then compare it with the runes of the Branded Swordsmen!” Leylin thought in his mind.

[Beep! Recorded runes, now comparing with the runes of the Branded Swordsmen…]

The A.I. Chip loyally intoned. Right after, Leylin received the results, [Similarity to fire elemental Branded Swordsmen runes recorded by Host body is 67.1%. Similarity to foundation metallic runes: 34.2%. Similarity to basic sharpness: 13.9%. Estimated to be the runes of the weapons of the Branded Swordsmen! Estimated time required to perfect and alter: 294 hours!]

“Like I thought!”

Glee appeared on Leylin’s face. The information he had on the Branded Swordsmen was extremely limited. Even with the A.I. Chip perfecting and supplementing information, he was still only able to gain the fire elemental runic spell formation suitable for males.

As for the runes for other elements and the weapons suitable for Branded Swordsmen, he had no clue at all.

Now, with the appearance of this long sword of the Rays of Dawn, Leylin could finally see some hope.

He also had another thought. The Fallen Star Pendant, which was a magic artifact that had accompanied him all these years, was beginning to be unable to meet his needs. He had hence sent it back to his family.

He now lacked an offensive-type magic artifact.

Perhaps, he could carve these branded runes on a magic artifact by imitating those on the long sword and create a weapon that was meant for him!

Leylin touched his chin and pondered over the feasibility of this plan.

While Leylin scanned and analysed the sword in his hands, a few Magi were quietly discussing in the VIP room that had been competing with him for this magic artifact.

“Torp, why aren’t you quoting another price? It’s just six million magic crystals. That’s nothing to you, right?”

A female in purple-gold Magus robes spoke to a red-bearded old man, a bewitching aura surrounding her.

“The magic crystals aren’t much, and I don’t actually want that magic artifact that much. I just want to analyse the runes on it, and I’m sure this kind of special magic artifact has very strict requirements for users. I’ve even come to suspect that those who aren’t Branded Swordsmen will be unable to use this long sword… The ancient Branded Swordsmen have already vanished from the south coast for thousands of years. It’s not worth it to spoil our plans for this item.”

The red-bearded Torp touched his beard.

“En! You are truly a Master Blacksmith! To be able to glean this much information from just a look…” The woman seemed to be in awe and then continued on worriedly, “I keep having this feeling that the plan is much too hurried. Will he really come…”

“Don’t worry! He’ll definitely be here!”

The red-bearded Torp spoke with conviction, “We’ve put out bait this time that is definitely irresistible to him. In order to use that item more effectively, he’ll definitely come!”

“That’s great!” The woman patted her chest, and then glanced at Leylin’s room with some conjectures in mind.

“Say, do you think he’s inside? Should I sound him out?”

“Don’t do it!” Torp immediately stopped her. “Don’t act rashly. If it really is him, would he dare be so bold as to compete with us? Besides, offending an unfamiliar rank 2 Magus would probably be unfavourable to us…”

“Hehe, I’m just joking. You actually took it seriously…”

The woman giggled coquettishly, and her figure disappeared into the darkness, leaving behind the old man who looked to be in a difficult position.

On the platform, the last item on the public auction was sent out. The announcer went on, “The auction has ended, and we will now enter the segment of the exchange meeting. Those who wish to leave may exit through the passages at both sides.”

*Rumble!* Along with his words, the large doors at two ends of the hall opened loudly.

Chapter 281: Sage

　　

“Shadow Stealth!”　　

After standing up, Leylin used the spell that had the most outstanding concealing abilities out of all of the the rank 1 dark elemental magic he knew.　　

With the added bonus from his solidified spiritual force as a rank 2 Magus, Shadow Stealth was now terrifyingly formidable.　　

Leylin’s figure disappeared from the VIP room in an instant, such that even the rank 2 Magi outside were not able to detect him.　　

　　

“Alistair actually sided with the dark Magi. With him as the leading cause, this sets the background for the Third Magus War.”

　　

Leylin was unmoved by this, his body like a mirage as he hurried along.

　

“He’s not my business anyway. I just need to know if he has anything I need in his possession!”

　　

The essence from the Wisdom Tree must have some extraordinary effects for ancient Magi to view it so highly.　　

　　

Though Leylin possessed a high-grade meditation technique, he wouldn’t mind some extra assurance for when he wanted to break through.　　

　　

*Boom!*　　

　

Alistair leapt, his powerful hind legs leaving behind two deep pits in the ground.　　

　　

With much momentum, he fiercely jumped out of the hole and began to run wildly on the field.　

　　

“He’s over there!”　　

　　

Following closely behind him was that group of rank 2 Magi from the light Magi alliance. Upon seeing the situation, the leader immediately waved his sleeve!

　

*Weng weng!*　　

　

A concentrated volley of countless bugs was produced from his sleeves, and immediately after, a huge grey cloud floated out from the large sleeves of his robes.　

Upon closer inspection, this ‘cloud’ was actually comprised of many densely packed bugs.　　

　　

These bugs had two compound eyes, and their mandibles were fierce and sharp. A pair of translucent wings flapped at a high frequency, producing waves of an ear-piercing sound that would cause one to feel fidgety.

　　

“Go!” This light Magus pointed at Alistair.　　

　　

The bugs chirped in a way that shook the heavens, forming the image of a human face without eyes, and chased after Alistair, who was currently still in his werewolf form.　　

　　

The huge human face streaked across the sky, looking like a black cloud of gas in the air. It quickly caught up to the werewolf who was fleeing, opened its mouth, and roared at him.　　

　　

“Awooo!” The werewolf faced the heavens and howled, gathering two large masses of wind-elemental energy particles that turned into wind blades, one horizontal and the other vertical. It turned into a huge cross shape, and chopped towards the human face in the air.

　　

The wind blade trembled slightly as it streaked past the face. In that moment, the bugs scattered and then regrouped, completely unharmed by the attack.　　

　　

“Chi chi…” Along with the cries from the numerous bugs, a great grey ‘flood’ was spat out from the human face, which engulfed the werewolf within.　

　　

Upon closer inspection, within the ‘flood’ were several worms that were even tinier than most insects, their sharp mouths glinting with light.　　

　　

*Chi chi!!!*　　

　　

The grey worms wrapped around the werewolf in an instant, and the horrifying sounds of something being gnawed into were heard.　　

　

“Woo woo…” From within the grey worms, the werewolf’s pitiful howls could be heard.　　

“Alright! Now that he’s been caught by the Death Insects, he can’t run!”　　

　

The light Magus who manipulated the worms grinned, “Go, get him! Steal the treasure and essence of the Wisdom Tree!”　　

　

“As expected from the ‘Death Bug Manipulator’, Jajone!” The rank 2 Magi following him exclaimed in admiration and hastened towards their target.

　

At this moment, a beautiful melody from a recorder travelled from some distance away.

　

The formless sound waves swept through the area, and swarms of grey bugs fell one after another.

　　

*Boom!* The surface of the earth cracked open, and two rank 2 Magi donning the robes of the dark Magi rushed out, accompanied by two huge white fireballs striking the human face in the air.　　

　　

“Ah…” The human face emitted a sound similar to the shrieks of a female, and the face then began to distort.　　

　　

In merely a couple of seconds, the face was shrouded with white flames, and large groups of Death Bugs dropped.　　

　　

“It looks like you’ve long since sided with the dark Magi!”　　

　　

The huge face formed out of bugs seemed to be connected to the spiritual force of the light Magus; after it had been burnt through, he visibly paled.

　　

However, he cared not about his injuries, and instead focused his attention on Alistair, who had escaped from the attack of the worms.　　

　　

The werewolf was now in a pitiful state. More than half of the pretty fur on his body had disappeared, revealing patches of pink skin and flesh.　

　　

On his body were some very large wounds, revealing muscle tissue that had been severely damaged. One could even see bone.　　

　　

*Chi chi!* The blood vessels and muscles visible on the wounds constantly wriggled, and layers of flesh covered the injury and stopped the flow of fresh blood. At areas which were barren of fur, a fine layer of fur began to grow.

　　

The abnormal healing ability of werewolf exhibited its strength here.　

　

“Let’s go!” With a wave from a rank 2 dark Magus, countless white ribs and bone spurs appeared in front of the light Magi, forming a large wall.　

　　

The wall seemed to have a life of its own, cunningly moving and trapping the light Magi within.　　

Then, with Alistair in tow, the two dark Magi left.　　

　

*Bang! Bang!*　　

　

From within the white bone cage, the dull thuds of people ramming into the cage were heard. One after another, hemisphere-like shapes appeared all around the cage, and around these shapes were even some minute cracks.　　

These cracks increased in size, and eventually, the cage exploded open!　　

The white dust from the broken spurs dissipated, revealing the figures of a few light Magi.

“There are still rank 2 dark Magi reinforcements! The situation is getting more troublesome! Send out the signal!”　　

　　

The Magus who was the leader of the light Magi roared.　　

　　

A Magus nodded and swiped upwards, and a shooting star with alternating red and green colours streaked through the sky.　　

*Xiu xiu xiu!*

　

Minutes later, thirteen Magi in black robes with iron crowns on their heads arrived at the scene.

　　

“Alistair has already sided with the dark Magi. There’s now a rank 3 Magus holding Lord Hoduke back, and there are also two dark Magi who took Alistair away!”　　

　

The light Magus looked to be in a difficult position.　　

　

“It’s the same situation that we are in! Don’t worry though. We’ve sprinkled large amounts of the pollen of the Nine Threaded Flower at the auction area. As long as he was there, he’ll definitely be unable to escape the pursuit of the Patchy Bees.”　　

　　

A Magus whose crown was a lot larger than everyone else answered.　　

　

“We are extremely confident in the setup of the Great Sage.” The leader of the light Magi bowed, displaying his respect towards the sage.

　　

These thirteen Magi were actually sages of Iron Crown, and were absolute existences in terms of their might!　　

　

Their neutral stance also caused the light Magus leader to have to do away with his haughty attitude.

“Now that the dark Magi are also involved, we may not be able to provide you with more help. You know that the very reason why we have been able to maintain our reputations as towering existences is our neutral stance!”　　

The Great Sage continued.　　

“Great Sage…” The leader of the light Magi’s face fell, and turned icy. “We signed a contract stating that you would pursue Alistair. What do you mean by those words, Great Sage?”　

“But… what about the dark Magi?” The Great Sage looked to be in a difficult position. Meanwhile, the leader of the light Magi had a vile look on his face.

“Just attack. We will take on the pressure from the dark Magi. The conditions in the contract we agreed on can be altered, and I can even concede on some matters…”　　

　　

The leader was silent for a moment and then chose to make a compromise.　　

Besides, they did not have much time left.　　

After hearing this, the Great Sage of Iron Crown smiled, looking as if a weight had been lifted off his shoulders. 　　

　　

He produced a transparent glass bottle from within his robes, a creature with numerous compound eyes at the centre within the bottle. This creature looked like a bee with an image of a black eye on its yellow wings, and was quietly resting within the glass bottle. Traces of intelligence and quick-wittedness flashed through its eyes.

　　

The Great Sage opened the neck of the bottle, and after flying in circles a few times, the little creature, the Patchy Bee, began to fly in a certain direction.　　

　　

“It has found them!” the Great Sage exclaimed, dense metal plating appearing on his body and forming the armour that Knights usually wore into battle.

　　

*Bang!*　

　　

The white skeleton of a large horse rose from the ground, green spiritual flames burning in its eye sockets and being snorted from its nostrils.　　

　　

“My old buddy, I’ll have to use you again!” The sage in armour stroked an old and tattered pair of reins and sighed with regret.　　

　

He fiercely rode the skeletal horse, and roared from deep within his throat. “Iron Crown!”　

　

“Glory for life! Advance for our responsibilities!” The sages present answered in a loud voice.　

　

The skeletal warhorse neighed, and black liquid metal covered the entire body of the horse. In an instant, the skeletal warhorse turned into a giant metallic beast with sharp barbs protruding from the surface of its body.

　　

*Lu Lu!*　　

　　

One after another, metallic warhorses struggled out of the ground and carried the other sages. Some of the sages wore dazzling magic robes, while others donned metallic armour. Powerful spells were sent out in a constant stream.　　

　　

In an instant the thirteen sages with iron crowns turned into Steel Knights possessing immense power!　　

“Chase after them!”　　

　　

Following the orders of the Great Sage, the thirteen warhorses charged forward, leaving behind traces of burning hoofprints.

　　

“The inheritance from ancient Magi! This is definitely a branch of the ancient Magi!”　　

　　

The light Magi’s eyelids twitched as they uttered these words in their hearts.　　

　　

In the south coast, there was a rumour floating around about the Magi organisation with a neutral stance, Iron Crown. These thirteen sages of Iron Crown had received the power of the inheritance from some ancient ruins, and were henceforth able to set up and establish Iron Crown!

Chapter 284: Prowess

“What’s going on?”　　

　　

The Great Sage was surprised, and all of a sudden, his body lost all its strength.

　　

*Boom!* Multiple steel creatures fell to the ground; the spirit flames in their black eye sockets died out. In a few seconds, they turned into dried up bones once again.　　

　　

“Old friend!” The Great Sage wailed sorrowfully. His connection with his steed had been completely severed. In other words, the spirit of his companion of many years had been destroyed and no longer existed in this world.

　　

“Who is it?” His eyes turned red.　　

　　

That dark Magus and Siley turned in the same direction to look at Leylin, who had a helpless look on his face.　　

　　

“It’s you!” The Great Sage’s face began to twitch. “You wretched trash! You dare…”　　

　　

“How pointless!” Solidified blood-red rays shot out of Leylin’s eyes, and the red light on his wrist was now extremely intense, to the point that it hit its limit. *Bang!* The early alert warning system crystal exploded, turning into sparkling powder.　　

　　

“Shadow Domain!”　　

　　

“Toxic Bile!”　　

　　

Total blackness filled the entire region, and behind Leylin, a large number of shadows that looked like snakes forming the terrifying features of a Devil King.　　

　　

The large shadow was like a beast that swallowed everything as it spread, the terrifying sounds of corrosion and the low huffs of those meeting the face of death sounding at the centre.　　

　　

*Bang!*　　

　　

A moment later, the black shadow disappeared, leaving the thirteen sages with no light in their eyes as they collapsed. Even the spirits in their bodies had been eaten through by the poison.　　

　

“Demonic Poison King! It’s Demonic Poison King Leylin!”　　

　　

In an area not too far away, the few light Magi who were planning to take advantage of the decision turned pale in fear at the rotted corpses under the black mist.　　

　　

Though they had heard of Leylin’s nickname as the Demonic Poison King before, they had never understood how terrifying he could be.　　

　　

“Ley-Leylin, you…”　　

　　

Not just that dark Magus, even Siley was a little stunned as he looked at Leylin, whose eyes were still shooting out blood-red rays.　　

　

The thirteen sages of the Iron Crown were a firm force that had been safeguarding this region. Every one of them had the strength of a peak rank 1 Magus, and their leader, the Great Sage, was even at rank 2!　　

　　

Siley knew that if he were to be trapped by this group, things would very very troublesome. Even fleeing would be an issue. The terrifying vitality of the spirit beasts was something that Magi who developed their strengths based on spells were unable to contend against.　　

　　

Now, however, this little group of Steel Knights that had been around for hundreds of years had died, just like that? And their killer was a newly-advanced rank 2 Magus, Leylin?　　

　　

Siley scratched his bald head, wondering if he had been caught in some Rank 3 Magus’ illusion.　　

　　

“Who else is there?”　　

　　

Leylin’s expression was a little strange and he began to roar, the blood-red in his eyes more prominent as they swept in the direction where the light Magi were hidden.　　

　　

“This is bad! He’s found us!”　　

　　

The leader whispered softly, and the entire group rapidly withdrew a large distance. It couldn’t be helped! Leylin’s poisonous attack that could affect a large area had terrified them.

　　

“Hah…”　　

　　

Leylin’s current situation was not good. Not only were there a few small wounds left behind by the retaliation of the Steel Knights, his expression was also crazed. White streams of air exited from his orifices.　

　　

[Liveliness of blood cells in host’s body has exceeded threshold! Beginning procedure to forcefully control situation!]　　

　　

All of a sudden, a flash of bright blue rays covered Leylin’s body, and his body temperature lowered. The white mist condensed into fragments of ice inside and scattered all over Leylin’s body.　　

　　

“Damn it, I got emotional again!”　　

　　

Under the control of the A.I. Chip and the stimulus from the biting cold, Leylin was finally able to regain his senses, eyes flashing with intelligence.　　

　　

“I can’t fight anymore, or else I’ll descend into a crazed state and go on a killing rampage till I die…”　　

　　

Leylin surveyed the area, keeping the sight of the battlefield in his mind.　　

　　

Though walking the path of a warlock with a bloodline allowed him to possess an incredible might, to the point that he could use his innate talents from his bloodline to achieve victory against experienced rank 2 Magi or even kill them and gain a reputation for himself, this branch of ancient Magi, the Warlock, had quite a few flaws.　

　　

The issue of becoming overly emotional was one of the problems.　　

　　

Compared to the rational Magus, Warlocks were easily affected by the external world and were often extremely emotional.　　

　　

Slaughter and battles would easily result in fury for Warlocks, causing them to descend into a crazed state and lose part of their rationality. If he were to be surrounded by enemies, he would not be able to escape at all.　　

　　

“My bloodline is much too pure. The moment it flares up, even the potion of tranquility will be rejected from my body.”　　

　　

Leylin checked his stats.　　

　　

[Leylin Farlier. Rank 2 Warlock, Bloodline: Giant Kemoyin Serpent. Strength: 21.1, Agility: 14.4, Vitality: 27.9, Spiritual force: 104.3, Magic power: 53 (Magic power is in synchronisation with spiritual force) Status: Large amounts of adrenaline is being secreted. Similarity to emotional outburst of Warlock: 98.7%. Dispelling potion of tranquility.] 　　

“A.I. Chip, use Plan C!” Leylin could only laugh bitterly and give out the command.　　

　　

[Received authorisation, beginning small operation on Host’s body.]　　

　　

The A.I. Chip loyally answered. In that moment, Leylin’s pupils turned sky blue, and cold energy particles were produced from all over his body.　　

　　

“He seems to have a problem! Go!!!”　　

　　

The light Magi who had been pursuing them saw Leylin acting weirdly. Excited, the light Magus who was the leader waved his sleeves and countless flying bugs came together to form half a human face, flying towards Leylin.　　

　　

“You just don’t know when to stop!”　　

　　

A fire rose in Leylin’s heart, but with the force from the chilliness, it was quickly suppressed.　　

　　

His right hand slashed downwards, and a formless, translucent ripple spread like a wave in the air.

　　

The formless ripple immediately collided with the sea of bugs.　　

　　

*Bang!* The half-formed human face stopped moving for a moment, and large amounts of flying bugs fell to the ground, their compound eyes no longer moving. The bodies became stiff and began to rot.　　

　　

*Huahuahua!* Like rain, the bugs fell from the sky and formed grey droplets.　　

　　

The formless poison seemed to be able to go through the void and connect to the Magus’ spiritual force, corroding his actual body.

　　

The Magus who manipulated the flying bugs staggered back, black tendrils that looked like snakes spreading on his face.　　

　　

“Quick, protect me and help me leave!” At this moment, the leader of the group of light Magi finally regretted his greediness. Even when Leylin was in a strange state, he was not somebody he could handle.　　

　　

“You’re thinking of leaving?” Not far away, Leylin’s lips curved up in a sly smile, and the black defensive item on his hand exploded. Black rays were pulled into a shape, turning into a longbow.　　

　　

“Toxic Bile!”　　

　　

Leylin used his innate rank 2 spell once more, his left hand pulling the string and releasing an arrow in the direction of the fleeing light Magi.　　

　　

*Beng!*　　

　

With vibration from the string, a formless toxic arrow streaked through the sky, distorting the air as it passed.　　

　　

On its way, the ground was charred black, plants died, creating a unique path that showed the arrow’s route.　　

　　

”No! You can’t kill me! My father is-” The light Magus who was in the middle of escaping was so terrified that it seemed as if his spirit had departed. Next, his body trembled and his expression changed.　

　　

*Ka-cha!* The clothes on his back were ripped open, revealing a translucent palm.　　

　　

This palm was the size of that of a regular human, and it grabbed towards the transparent toxic arrow.　　

　　

*Beng!* A formless ripple spread, and the surrounding Magi quickly retreated, fearing the toxins.

　　

“The protection from a rank 3 Magus?” Leylin watched on not far away, his desire to kill even stronger now, “Nobody can save you today!”　　

　　

He pulled the string again. *Bzz!*　　

　　

Along with the sounds of vibration, the toxic arrow that had been at a deadlock with the transparent palm exploded, forming countless tiny arrows that went flying in all directions.　　

　　

*Tss tss!* The translucent palm exploded in such a manner that there were numerous holes in it, which caused it to break down. From within, the roar of an old Magus could be heard.　　

　　

With an expression full of disbelief, that light Magus stiffly collapsed.　　

　　

On his back, a large wound from the explosion had been inflicted. His innate defensive spell that he had been so proud of had not been the slightest bit useful.　　

　　

“You- you actually killed him! His father is a rank 3 Magus!”　　

　　

Siley’s voice trembled.　　

　　

Leylin, who was still under the influence of the warlock bloodline effects, paid no heed to this. He turned, cold glaze piercing as he focused on Siley.　　

　　

Siley quivered, suddenly remembering that his life was still in the hands of his opponent. He forced a smile, “Alright! I was just pointing it out. You can do whatever you want!”

　　

Hesitation and struggle appeared in Leylin’s expression, and dense black gas wrapped his body.　　

*Whoosh whoosh!*　　

　　

Strong black gales blew madly towards the distance, and in a moment, disappeared into the horizon.　　

　　

“That crazy guy is finally gone!” Siley and his partner glanced at each other, and then Alistair who was heavily injured and unable to get up, with bitter smiles.

　　

“What should we do? Jajone’s dead! Lord Eric won’t let us off!”　　

　　

The other light Magi made sounds of indignation in unison.　

　　

“Kill those dark Magi and avenge Jajone!”　　

　　

A light Magus stared hard at Siley and the rest with deep hatred.　　

　　

Siley steeled his expression and stood with his partner, a ring of defensive energy particles appearing.　　

　　

*Pu! Pu! Pu!*　　

　　

In that instant, the looks on the faces of the Magi present changed. The fierce toxins suddenly flared up.

　　

In the havoc that Leylin had wreaked previously, the Magi present had somewhat been affected by the toxins of the Giant Kemoyin Serpent, and this was difficult to remove.

　　

The light Magi had been affected by the attack towards Jajone, and their injuries were even more serious.　　

　　

The two groups of people exchanged gazes, and eventually decided on leaving in a huff, rather than clashing.

Chapter 285: The Chase

In a grassland filled with blood-red pastureland.　　

　　

An old male Magus with a head of white hair and a kind smile was guiding a few acolytes along the pasture. In their hands were a few metallic items used for harvesting.　　

　　

“The reason for our existence is to seek truth! The path of a Magus is a continuous search for the truth, researching about phenomena and objects, and finding the rules in them and applying these concepts to ourselves. This is the source of motivation and strength for Magi!”　　

　　

While walking, the old Magus taught the acolytes who were following behind him.　　

　　

“I’ve already told you about the unique characteristics of the Bloody Grass. However, you’ve only seen pictures and samples. Now, I’ve brought you here, where it is naturally grown…”　　

　　

“Arnold! Take a look at this. Is this Bloody Grass any different from the rest?”　　

　

The old Magus asked a male acolyte with freckles on his face.　　

　　

“Yes! It’s thinner than others of its kind, and the veined pattern of blood on the surface isn’t very clear. It might have met with some natural predator, specifically… specifically…”　　

　　

Arnold was still a large boy, with some hair growing above his lips. He walked ahead and extended his right hand towards the Bloody Grass, wanting to take a closer look.　　

　　

*Xiu!*　　

　　

In that instant, a red shadow shot out from the Bloody Grass, heading straight for Arnold’s face!

“Ah…” Arnold staggered and fell back, alarmed.　　

　　

*Pak!* A black flash of light was shot out from the old Magus’ hands, striking the shadow down.

　　

It was a red beetle-like organism with grey spots on its back. Its sharp mouth let out cold glints, its teeth that were half the size of its body still moving.　　

　　

“This is the Sawtooth Beetle, the natural predator of the Bloody Grass! It loves to gnaw at the roots of the Bloody Grass. If it is cultivated by hand, one must patrol every day and eliminate this sort of insect!”　　

　　

“Arnold! You didn’t even perform the most basic defence before observing the grass. This carelessness will cost you your life in the future!”　　

　　

The old Magus shook his head and then headed off into the distance.　　

　　

Arnold turned a little red as he rubbed his head, quickly stood up and caught up.　　

　　

“Hey, big guy! You really are lucky! The spiral sawtooth attack of the Sawtooth Beetle is something even level 2 acolytes might not be able to take on! If not for mentor, you would now be a cold corpse…”　

　　

A female acolyte approached him, snorting in disdain.　　

　　

“Hehe…” Arnold scratched his head, making him seem even more thickheaded.　　

　　

“Let’s go! How could you even become an acolyte with that level of intelligence? It’s basically a disgrace to us and to our mentor!” A boy wearing fancy clothes and seemed to have received education on the etiquette of the nobility walked past, leaving Arnold far behind.　　

　　

“Mentor! The Bloody Grass can strengthen one’s body to a certain extent, and is a huge temptation to some high-energy beings. It is usually found in places where high-energy beings hunt, so should we be a little more careful?”　　

　　

The acolyte of nobility ran in front of the old Magus.　　

　　

”You’re on the right track, but I’ve already scouted the area. The only high-energy being here is just a Gale Shackled Weasel, which is about the limits of what you are able to handle with your abilities!”

　　

The old Magus nodded, praising him.　　

　　

“Though Bloody Grass can strengthen the body to a certain extent, its poison is too strong for us humans. It needs to be processed before it can be turned into a potion! Your mission now is to harvest enough Bloody Grass to brew a standard portion of body-strengthening potion, as well as remove the poison within!”　　

　　

The old Magus began to issue the task.　　

　　

“Understood, mentor!” A few acolytes immediately brought out their apparatus and separated, with the old Magus at the centre so that he was able to help every one of them in time.　　

　

“Good!” Seeing this, the old Magus nodded in satisfaction.　　

　　

*Xiu!* A Sawtooth Beetle shot out of the Bloody Grass, brushed past Arnold’s face and scared him so much that he fell.　　

　　

“Haha! Look at that idiot! Mentor had already demonstrated that there could be beetles hidden in the Bloody Grass that looked less healthy, and yet you still try to harvest it!”　　

　　

The acolyte of nobility coincidentally walked past. He raised his hand and chanted a few syllables, and a corrosive ball shot out, putting an end to the beetle before mocking him relentlessly.　　

　　

“Look! I’ve almost gathered the required amount of resources, and you haven’t even filled the bottom yet!”　　

　　

The acolyte opened his bag and proudly showed it to Arnold.　　

　　

“Don’t bother with him! Levi, come help me! The roots of this Bloody Grass are too hard!” The girl from before hummed in dissatisfaction.　　

　　

“Alright, alright, I’ll be right there!”　　

　　

Levi quickly cast Arnold away, approaching the girl and being particularly attentive to her.

　　

Though they were still children, the youngsters of the south coast usually matured early. There were already indications of this early on.　　

　　

Upon seeing this, the old Magus reminiscenced, “This is youth…”　　

　　

He mumbled to himself, producing a pipe with golden decorations on the surface and beginning to smoke. White circles of smoke were constantly puffed out and appeared in the air.　　

　　

However, while he was recalling the past, a slight tremble of the ground began.　　

　　

“Huh? This is?” The old Magus immediately put out his pipe, this peculiar situation immediately arousing his interest.　　

　　

In the next few seconds, the tremors became more intense till the ground began to shake substantially.　　

　　

From a distance away, a group of strange beings, such as two-headed wolves, four-legged mutated elks and all sorts of high-energy beings, normal beings, carnivorous and herbivorous animals banded together that formed a wave that was hard to avoid.　　

　　

At the very front, the old Magus even found a few large terrifying beasts that gave him a sense of danger!　　

　　

“Assemble! Assemble here!” The old Magus yelled, his voice a little hoarse from his nerves.　　

　　

“What the hell is going on?”　　

　　

The acolyte of nobility, Levi, raised his head and stared at the scene, stunned. All of a sudden, he was drowned by the large numbers of Sawtooth Beetles that flew out from the Bloody Grass. The girl with him could not escape the fate of death either, the sound of flesh and blood being gnawed on constantly being produced.　　

　　

The group of beetles were like grey spots constantly rising from the Bloody Grass, forming a cloud that entered the wave.　　

　　

“What’s going on? Why are there animals fleeing from danger in this season? Is there some extremely dangerous being chasing after them?”　　

　　

The old Magus wondered to himself, not even sparing a glance at Arnold who had been running pitifully.　　

　　

*Xiu xiu!*　　

　　

A human figure streaked through the sky at an incredibly fast rate, creating two air waves that had long ripples trailing behind.　　

　　

“You can’t escape!”　　

　　

A massive voice travelled from behind the figure. Following the sound, a large bundle of white light immediately appeared in front of the black figure, turning into a large shield.　　

　　

“Scorching Touch!” With a wave of his hand, two streaks of red rays shot out from the shadow and created two large holes in the shield. Under the constant shimmering of the white rays, the shield quickly returned to its prior state.　　

　　

Under the hindrance of the shield, the black figure stopped, revealing the appearance of a young Magus. He had black hair, his features handsome yet sinister.　　

　　

Behind him, a line of white light brought with it immense pressure as it burst towards him.　　

　

*Weng!* A formless energy boundary dissipated in all directions with the light at the centre. A fantastical land of light and beauty suddenly descended upon this region.

　　

“This is… the domain of a highly ranked Magus! It’s a rank 3 Magus!”　

　　

The old Magus gaped, his eyes on the verge of popping out, “Who in the world is he chasing after? Is it also a rank 3 lord Magus?”　　

　　

The rays dissipated, revealing the figure of a blonde Magus.　　

　

“Poison King Leylin! You dare kill my blood! Even though Jajone was just trash, our family name must not be tarnished!　　

　　

Countless rays were emitted from his body, forming a huge pike made of countless other pikes.　　

“Heavenly Pike!” The large numbers of pikes shot towards Leylin like raindrops.　　

　　

“Toxic Bile!” Leylin spread his arms and a wave of toxins rippled towards the pikes. *Tss tss!* A large amount of white gas sizzled out, and the sounds of corrosion was produced from the pike formed of heavenly rays. It quickly began to fill with holes.

　　

However, though the pike’s power seemed to have been weakened, it still charged towards Leylin.　　

　　

“Kemoyin’s Scales!” From the surface of Leylin’s skin, countless black scales with incomplete runes on it emerged. The black light exploded from the scales, forming a huge shield in front of him.　　

　　

*Ka-cha! Ka-cha!*　　

　　

The pike penetrated the shield with black runes, focusing on Leylin’s body and created a large number of sparks.　　

　　

An unnatural flush appeared on Leylin’s face, and he retreated. While flying backwards, he waved fiercely.　　

　

“Latent Fireball!”　　

　　

Large amounts of black flames wrapped the shield of light from before, combusting fiercely.　　

　　

The shield of light had become slightly thinner after the attack of the Scorching Touch. Now, with the attack from the Latent Fireball, white rays constantly flickered and eventually exploded, turning into little milky-white lights that were burnt till nothing was left by the black flames.　　

　　

“Light Domain!” The blonde rank 3 Magus suddenly spread his arms, looking ready to give a hug.　　

　　

*Boom!* The boundaries of light shifted such that it increased in area, including Leylin within.　　

A huge suction power exploded from the light Magus, and Leylin was involuntarily dragged closer to him.　　

　　

“As expected of a rank 3 Magus! Though this light domain is but an imitation, it is still slightly able to suppress my strength!” Feeling the rapid increase of the number of light elemental particles in the air and the huge decrease in dark elemental particles, Leylin’s expression became grim.

　　

“Die!”　　

　　

A white bundle of light carrying with it a terrifying destructive power rose from the rank 3 light Magus’ hand, advancing towards Leylin.

Chapter 286: Possession

“Activate gravitational spell formation at full power—100 times gravity!”

Leylin pressed his temples and ordered.

*Weng weng!*

A large, dark brown formation lit up and rose from the ground and tore apart the milky white domain.

The light Magus was stunned for a moment, the ball of energy in his hands changing its course and missing Leylin.

“An ancient spell formation? When did he set that up?”

The light Magus saw the terrifying formation that spanned for kilometres, shock apparent in his expression.

“I’ll take advantage of this! Suction spell formation!” An inverted “L” shaped rune brightened on Leylin’s body, and as if he was being sucked in by a black hole, he turned into a black streak and vanished.

“What an interesting little guy! It’s a pity that all your methods are useless against me!” The light Magus calmly looked in the direction in which Leylin had fled, and suddenly laughed, shooting a glance at the old Magus from the corner of his eye. He turned into a ray of light and quickly left the area.

“Poison? Then he should be the Demonic Poison King Leylin, whose name has been going around! I wonder which faction and organisation that rank 3 Magus is from…”

The old Magus mumbled to himself in a daze, not noticing the look of envy in Arnold’s eyes.

……

*Boom!* A black shadow slammed into the spell formation, the powerful suction spell formation smashed to pieces.

Leylin let out a long sigh, “A rank 3 Magus is someone I can’t deal with yet…”

In the beginning, under the influence of his emotional state, Leylin had killed off Jojane, who had a powerful backing. Under his enraged state, he had not even taken the most basic protective measures.

When he had killed Jojane, the death mark from a rank 3 Magus was left on Leylin’s body.

All Magi usually had this method. For Leylin, a mark from a rank 2 Magus basically had no effect on him. However, the mark from a rank 3 Magus was evidently not so easily dealt with.

Leylin forced a smile and took a look at his sea of consciousness.

Within the crimson sea was a little, maggot shaped, milky white ray of light. While Leylin was not paying attention to it, it would expand.

A large amount of time and spiritual force would be needed to wear down and expel this mark.

This was the best solution provided by the A.I. Chip, but Leylin would be found by his opponent every so often. There was not enough time to deal with this.

After a few battles, Leylin had a better understanding of his own strength.

In his current state, he was a terrifying existence to rank 2 Magi who were lucky enough to rank up.

With a high-grade meditation technique, as well as a powerful bloodline, Leylin’s advancements in rank as a warlock always brought immense benefits and increases in strength.

However, for similar rank 2 Magi who also possessed high-grade meditation techniques, the gap was not so obvious.

“In my current state, I am considered an elite amongst rank 2 Magi. However, in the face of any rank 3 Magi, I have no confidence at all. Even being able to escape would depend on my luck!”

Leylin shook his head and walked out.

In front of him was a small, desolate little town, with dust, rubbish and all sorts of vines growing on the ground.

“No! The mark on my body is constantly emitting waves to track my location. No matter where I am on the south coast, I’ll easily be found. I need to go to a place far, far away, to the point that the distance can interfere with the mark’s transmission of information!”

Leylin’s eyes showed his resolution. This was the desolate town where the Ancient Spirit Slaying Sect’s secret plane had been!

“If this really doesn’t work out, I can just use the teleportation spell formation and leave this place! If I’m quick enough, he won’t be able to find out about this place, and I may still be able to return!”

If the Magus did not find out about this secret plane, Leylin could remove all traces of the mark, and then confidently strut back into the south coast.

The moment the entrance to the secret plane was found, no matter how much Leylin did not want to do so, he could only hold back the pain of having to abandon this place, destroy the teleportation spell formation there, and leave this place forever.

“I didn’t think I’d need to use my last resort so soon!”

Leylin laughed bitterly, and from a spell formation at the villa, entered the secret plane. While going through the spell formation that went through the void, Leylin moved his hand and a red ray disappeared into the wall.

“I haven’t been able to obtain probing spells or spiritually branded slaves. If I’m going over, I’ll need to do it myself. Though I’ve already ascertained that the teleportation spell formation is alright after checking with the A.I. Chip, gambling like this really leaves a sour taste in my mouth…”

Leylin furrowed his brows and came to the secret room in the narrow pathway.

Though he was sure that the teleportation spell formation was fine, the state of the surroundings around it might not be alright.

What he could confirm, though, was that the other side of the spell was in a place that was very far away. As long as he escaped and broke the connection between the two spell formations, he would be able to break away from the chase of the rank 3 Magus!

“I’ll take a look over there, and if it really isn’t a good environment there, I can still come back!” Leylin consoled himself.

*Pu!* All of a sudden, a bright, milky-white beam shot out from Leylin’s body and up into the sky, heading upwards in a straight line as if penetrating the hindrances of the secret room.

Leylin covered his head and staggered back. In his sea of consciousness, that milky-white light was spreading outwards, and no matter how Leylin used his spiritual force to obstruct it, it was of no use.

Leylin seemed to see a blonde rank 3 Magus rushing towards him.

“The time he takes to detect me has shortened. He’s found this place!”

Leylin’s expression turned grim, “I’ll have to use my last resort and completely give up on this place!”

Not only that, even the teleportation spell formation had to be destroyed as well. If not, the Magus could give chase through the spell formation. With the mark, it was impossible for Leylin to hide.

*Tss tss!* Numerous black tendrils of smoke were emitted from Leylin’s body. Meanwhile, in his sea of consciousness, a vast amount of red rays charged towards the milky-white spiritual force and encircled it, temporarily isolating it from external influences.

*Rumble!*

The secret plane began to shake as if there was a powerful existence attacking the area from outside.

“Alric is attacking the secret plane!” Leylin grit his teeth as the crimson ring on his finger exploded.

The alert spell formation that the Gargamel had set up on the wall had been damaged by Leylin in the past. However, the moment the red rays shone, it began to work once more, and a hidden spiritual force travelled through a special path.

*Hualala!*

In an area surrounding the little town, the grass and soil flipped over, and a strange ‘corpse’ crawled out!

This ‘corpse’ was shrivelled up and small, and resembled an old woman. Moreover, it had a couple of deformities. Not only were there two extra arms and legs, there was also a young face growing at the back of the head of the old lady.

It looked like a body that was shared by two people.

“The alert system set up by Master has been activated! The only person who can find this place has to be Leylin!”

Wisps of green light shot out of the old woman’s eyes. “It has to be him!”

“Leylin? The offering that escaped?” The young woman’s face behind the old lady opened her eyes.

“Yes! If not for him, you would have gained a body of your own and not have ended up in this state.”

The old woman grit her teeth, a deep-rooted hatred apparent in her eyes.

She was Old Devil, the female Magus who had conducted secret dealings with Leylin in Nightless City. She had tried to use him as an offering to the Gargamel in the secret plane, in order to allow her daughter, Jaye, to regain her physical body.

Unfortunately, due to Leylin’s escape, her wish had been realised with a strange method.

Somehow, the Gargamel had forcibly induced half a corporeal body onto the old woman’s body, and had placed Jaye’s spirit within.

It could be said that Leylin had a played a very big part in causing the two of them to end up in this way.

“I want to kill him!”

Old Devil roared.

“Have you forgotten Master’s orders? He’s an offering for Master, so only Master is qualified to enjoy him!” Jaye’s eyes, behind Old Devil’s head, suddenly glazed over as she muttered.

“No! I wouldn’t dare offend Lord Gargamel!” The old witch quickly knelt down and begged for forgiveness.

“Then say your prayers, and report the happenings here to the great Lord Gargamel!”

Jaye closed her eyes after speaking, and the next time she opened them, she seemed to have turned into another person. “Mother! My illness seems to be getting worse…”

After implanting the spirit, the Gargamel had mixed in a few things into Jaye’s spirit, and had set up a core of consciousness that would oversee the old witch.

Old Devil, whose daughter was being controlled, had no choice but to submit to the Gargamel.

“Oh, Great Gargamel, home of all spirits! You are the master of all, as well as the beginning and ending of all. Please listen to the prayers of your servant…”

The old witch took out something like a communication device and chanted a long verse of prayers from a scripture.

*Weng Weng!*

After Old Devil explained the current situation, the communication device began to vibrate.

“Yes, Lord Gargamel! It will possess me!”

The old witch was stricken with fear, but her body involuntarily knelt to the ground—after the modifications, her body was now no longer her own.

A powerful spirit that was brimming with evil thoughts used a special method to rush out of the communication device and possessed the old witch’s body.

Old Devil’s body trembled violently, her eyes rolled back, and white foam frothed at her mouth.

Finally, her body was wrapped up in a black spiritual body and turned into a large, black, human figure.

On the figure’s face, there was a mask of a devil’s skull with a horn on it, which looked immensely strange.

*Chi chi!*

The Gargamel that had possessed Old Devil’s body made a sound and charged towards the secret plane.

Chapter 290: Assistance Required

Leylin had previously seen information regarding the resources of the subterranean world in an ancient book.

Legend has it that the ancient Magus World was only a small part of the surface of the earth, and before the ancient Magi’s focus had switched to the other worlds, their goal had been the subterranean world!

The ancient Magi all wielded formidable power; even the sun and the moon would lose their splendor when put in front of these Magi. Many of the natives of the subterranean world had been subdued by them, and these Magi had then exploited layers and layers of the subterranean world to obtain endless wealth and resources.

It was recorded that the ancient Magi had exploited the 7 layers of the subterranean world!

It was said that the further down the layers one visited, the more powerful the ethnic race of that layer would be, and that at the core of the earth, there was an extremely terrifying female existence.

But these did not stop the ancient Magi from venturing further, and finally, the whole subterranean world had acknowledged them as their conqueror. This was all a part of the golden age of the ancient Magi.

Later, the still-dissatisfied Magi shifted their attention to different worlds, and conquered world after world until they ran into that extremely powerful world!

After what was known as the Final Confrontation, although that opposing world did not end up getting any benefits, neither did the Magus World—they deteriorated instead. Even the passage that led to the subterranean world had been destroyed by this war. Since then, the subterranean world had only appeared in legends.

At the least, within the entirety of the southern coast, Leylin had not seen any of the subterranean world’s life-forms, nor had he heard of any passages to the subterranean world.

“From the previously gathered information and the sights seen, this must be the subterranean world; I just don’t know which layer this is! However, based on the dangerous life-form that approached, it ought to be, at most, the third layer, else I would have ran into many dangerous, high-energy life-forms. Also, the probability of the life-forms I ran into being from the first or second layer is really large…”

Leylin kept on pondering this over.

Although he was uneasy that this place was a barren region, Leylin continued travelling. The recent appearance of the grey boar supplied him with huge confidence to proceed on his journey.

While walking the whole journey, Leylin also made a record of his surroundings.

At the location of the ancient magic spell, which Leylin had named “Giant Stone Hills,” the signs of life were so weak that, at most, one could see only moss and some insects, and nothing else.

As Leylin went about his journey, the signs of life gradually increased, and later, he saw something like bat-like birds.

He would occasionally see the grey boars and as he travelled further, the rate of encountering them grew higher.

Thus, Leylin was certain. He had already walked away from the life-restricting region and come to the outside world.

[Beep! Discovered energy waves! The estimate is that these waves are the aftermath of level zero magic. Direction: 15 degrees east, at 3,123 meters.]

Now, the A.I. Chip had issued a message.

“Huh?!” Leylin’s thoughts shook: “Finally, there are some traces of an organism with energy!”

He quickly packed up and soon went in the direction from which the energy waves were emitted.

There was still a grave injury upon his body, not to mention that due to his sea of consciousness solidifying large amounts of spiritual force, he could only display the approximate might of a level 1 Magus right now. However, he did not pay any attention to this trivial matter, and rushed to the scene of those energy waves.

What appeared in Leylin’s sight was the scene of three males and two females confronting a high-energy organism.

These five people seemed to be a standard small squadron. Two males dressed in leather, who were at the very front, served as human shields, constantly swinging their huge iron swords. They, at the very least, had the power of a Grand Knight.

The other three wore gray robes that looked like what the magician apprentices of the southern coast wore, but the style of these robes was very old-fashioned; they were simple and unadorned.

“There are humans here! And they are acolytes!” Leylin inwardly felt elated at this prospect.

What the five acolytes were confronting was an organism that was similar to the huge grey boar, but with a physique that was almost a dozen times bigger, and 3 pairs of huge, crescent-moon-shaped teeth beneath its snout. Hard fur grew all over its body, and it was entirely covered in pine resin, mud, and other forms of muck. It formed thick lumps that, like a battle tank that had donned armor on. The level 0 magic spell that had been previously used by those apprentices seemed to have only left burn marks in the region; it had been incapable of breaking through even the outermost defences.

“Hoo hoo…” Two puffs of white gas were emitted from the nose of this organism that looked like a suckling pig. After pawing the ground, it suddenly charged, and its whole body was like a derailed train as it ran towards those two Grand Knights.

“Ah!”

The floor shook, causing one of those Grand Knights to lose his footing. Soon after, he slipped and was sent flying by this huge boar-like beast. Upon having been gored upon his waist and back by the organism’s huge tusks, blood poured out from his wounds like spring water.

Seeing this scene, the other Grand Knight let out a loud shout and immediately retreated, thus exposing those three apprentices.

With the Grand Knight no longer impeding it, the boar fiercely bared its teeth at those apprentices with a blood-thirsty glint in its eyes.

The two female apprentices were scared and kept retreating backwards. *Thud! Thud!* The two of them tripped on something and fell down, expressions of despair coloring their faces.

The remaining male apprentice displayed a gentlemanly bravery, quickly appearing in front of these women with an expression of firm resolve. Still shouting something, he lifted his hand, from which small fireballs were emitted and aimed at the middle of the nose of that big-headed boar.

*Pat! Pat* The big boar’s nose was blackened, but that did not slow down its assault speed by even a bit. On the contrary, the boar seemed to have been infuriated by that male apprentice, and its charging speed even seemed to have increased a little.

That male apprentice smiled helplessly, and then turned his head toward the two female disciples behind him and muttered something; his demeanor gave one the feeling that this youth was not afraid of dying.

*Hoo hoo!* The wild boar got closer and closer, and the three apprentices could now see clearly the blood vessels in the big boar’s eyes and the thick pores below its fur.

Of course, what they would find very hard to forget was the cold radiance of the three pairs of snow-white, fierce, crescent-moon-shaped teeth of the boar.

“Shadow Binding!”

At that moment, Leylin suddenly made his appearance, and several tentacles made of shadow extended outwards from below the belly of the wild boar, and transformed into several hands that firmly dragged the boar by its front hooves.

*Peng!* As if a magnitude 9 earthquake had suddenly occurred, that boar, which was charging at a high speed, suddenly fell down while making a huge noise; even the sounds of bones breaking could be heard from its body.

Soon after, the three apprentices saw a youth in leather armor walking out from behind the fallen boar.

Several black, shadowy ropes trussed up that fallen boar, not even leaving the smallest of weaknesses in the bindings.

“Are you alright?” asked Leylin, with a gentle smile on his face.

Those three apprentices saw Leylin, their expressions those of shock, and they opened their mouths to say, “gnkmfsk……”

The smile on Leylin’s face drooped, and then he sighed. “This is really not the common language of the continent!”

What Leylin had just spoken in was the common language of the southern coast magicians, but what these 3 apprentices had spoken was not a language that Leylin recognised.

“This language’s endings sound a bit familiar to the Metiya language, but the syllables in between resemble the language of the highlands…”

Leylin did not feel surprised in the least about the differences in the language. After all, after the ancient era, the subterranean world had been isolated from the earth’s surface. It would be strange if the language was still similar.

“Hello! I am a nomad. Can you tell me what is this place?”

Leylin immediately switched to another language—this time it was the ancient Byron language!

The ancient Byron language brought with a strange power; it held power over rules and regulations. It could draw upon the power of the energy particles within the atmosphere and was the foundation of all magic spells.

Thus, the ancient Byron language was also a language that all magicians were required to learn.

Whether it was the surface world or the subterranean world, the ancient Byron language was passed down from the ancient Magi, and there would not be even the tiniest bit of disparity in its usage.

Sure enough, upon hearing Leylin asking in the ancient Byron language, those 3 apprentices immediately reacted, and finally, that male apprentice took the lead to reply, “Respected Sir! Hello! This here is the Woody Wastelands of the Eastern Twilight Zone.”

He gave a respectful salute. Although Leylin’s actions were suspicious and the language that he initially used to speak was very different from their own language, from the way Leylin had easily subdued this huge, 6-toothed boar that had almost caused a complete wipe for their team, it was obvious that the other party’s strength was superior to theirs.

This was the wilderness, where the strong preyed on the weak. If they got on bad terms with Leylin, then they would be killed, and no one would come to know of it. Thus, this male apprentice’s mannerisms were very deferential.

“Eastern Twilight Zone?” Leylin frowned, and the A.I. Chip quickly searched through the storage database but did not find any details related to this.

“You might need this!” Leylin pointed at the Grand Knight who had been sent flying, and threw a blood clotting medicine towards them.

“Thank you!” Those two fallen female apprentices also stood up, and one of them immediately clutched the medicine and smeared it on that Grand Knight’s injury. After hesitating for while, she bowed to Leylin.

*Hiss! Hiss!*

At that time, a snake formed entirely of black gas slithered forward and spat out an armoured Grand Knight who had lost consciousness from within its mouth.

“This one is also your partner, right? I had also conveniently picked him up.”

Leylin pointed at the Grand Knight who had just been spat out, and those three apprentices, who had been scared by the sudden appearance of that huge black snake, retreated many steps.

“This coward!” Leylin heard that female apprentice mutter, but he only smiled indifferently.

After that, he asked, “Oh, by the way, do you know which towns are close to here and where the Magi’s Bazaar is?”

These 3 apprentices looked each other in the eyes, and then that male apprentice, seeing Leylin’s agreeable demeanor and speech, gathered his courage and stepped forward as he said, “The closest town from here is Potter Town in the west, and its distance is one and a half days from here. About the Magi’s’ bazaar… the official Magi’s meeting point is located only in the capital city of the Twilight Zone….”

Chapter 293: Opening A Shop

The subterranean world was shrouded in darkness.

The towns and cities here where there were sun stones were the areas in which human traffic was high.

In the human cities of the Twilight Zone, the sun stone would be changed every 12 hours to be maintained, and kept the same light conditions as the surface of the earth.

However, a small area like Potter Town wouldn’t have a high-grade sun stone. At most, it would be the size of an egg.

Based on rumours, the larger a sun stone was, the higher its value and better its function was; it was said that at the capital of the five regions, there was a sun stone the size of a small mountain!

The moment a sun stone was lost, the entire area would be engulfed in darkness and surrounded by countless dangers. Hence, at every area populated by humans, the sun stone was always placed in an area with the highest level of security.

Seeing the darkness outside the window, Leylin heaved a gentle sigh and pulled the curtains shut.

After setting up a defensive spell formation, Leylin sat up on the bed and began to meditate.

Dark red specks of light were pulled out of the air one after another, and gathered at Leylin’s body.

In his sea of consciousness, the silver-white crystals became even more solid, and the slight cracks at the sides seemed to be repairing themselves.

As for the mark, with the seal from Leylin’s solidified spiritual force, that milky-white light had become dimmer. He could tell that in the near future, the mark would be completely destroyed.

“It’s going well!” After seeing this, Leylin, who had been on edge this entire time, could finally relax.

Afterwards, he collapsed onto the bed and went into a deep sleep.

Morning! With the regular pattern from the alarm clock, a ray of light passed through the curtain and entered Leylin’s room.

“I finally got some rest!”

Leylin opened his eyes, feeling extremely comfortable. The tiredness accumulated from camping outside for a month dissipated with just a single day of rest.

This had to do with his frightening vitality. Even in his heavily injured state, all of his fatigue could be restored with a night’s rest.

“Good morning, Sir!”

In the dining area within the inn, the slightly plump boss lady brought oatmeal bread and milk for breakfast, a smile on her face.

A few children with sullen, yellow skin and some dust on their face were all gathered at a corner, staring hard at Leylin’s breakfast with desire apparent in their eyes.

However, they only dared look from afar, gulping down some saliva but not approaching him to beg for some food.

Whether it was Leylin’s elegance or his armour, all of it was something that regular people did not possess.

These people usually held a lot of power and a high position. They had once seen someone with a huge hammer use his black hand to crush a child’s head because he was annoyed by him!

After that incident, that murderer was merely imprisoned by the enforcement team for a few days and subsequently released after paying a fine.

Hence, these children had a clear understanding of the situation: never provoke anyone with weapons!

“Go away! Don’t bother this lord who wants to enjoy his meal!”

Seeing these children harrassing her important guest, this lady boss shouted.

“It’s alright!” Leylin picked up a slice of oatmeal bread, “Let them have it!”

“Yes, of course! My lord has such a kind heart!”

The plump boss lady’s expression revealed her thought that this was a waste. However, she still tore the bread into several pieces and gave them to the children, “You’re so lucky to have met such a kind-hearted lord! Eat and leave!”

The children quickly stuffed the oatmeal bread into their mouths, the aroma of food spreading inside their mouths. They cupped their hands over their mouths, on the verge of tears.

The children had argued and even almost fought amongst themselves for just a bit of bread.

There was a boy who was a little older than the rest of the group who had kept the oatmeal bread he had received in his clothes, probably to bring it back for someone to eat.

Though Grey Spotted Mushrooms could fill one’s stomach, they tasted horrendous.

In addition, not everyone was able to even eat Grey Spotted Mushrooms. From the state of the children’s clothes, they must have come from poor families, and might not have even had decent meals.

Leylin merely glanced at them for a moment, and then shifted his focus away.

He tossed out a piece of gold, which flew through the air and fell into the palm of the lady boss’ hand.

“I really like Potter Town and wish to settle down here. I also want to open a shop here. Do you know what procedures I have to go through?”

Until his injures completely healed and he regained his strength as a rank 2 Magus, Leylin decided to temporarily live in seclusion.

He had a long life anyway and could afford to waste this bit of time.

“You want to open a shop here?” The lady boss was shocked, “What kind of shop do you want to open?”

“What do you think of a weapons shop?”

Leylin spoke nonchalantly. The purpose of this was to have a cover while he analysed the long sword of the Rays of Dawn. Hence, he had chosen a weapons shop.

He could clearly see that the Woody Wastelands was near Potter Town, and was an area where adventurers would go to. It wasn’t a bad idea to make and sell some weapons here, and it would definitely be profitable.

“A weapons shop…” The boss lady hesitated, “My lord, you’ll need to go through the department of internal affairs and the guards. Also, weapons are restricted items, so you’ll need to get approval from the capital and Joseph…”

“I see.” Leylin stroked his chin, and asked where the department of internal affairs, guard post and the baron’s residence were before leaving the inn.

In just a few days, a weapons shop called “Blazing Hammers” covertly opened on the commerce street in Potter Town.

For others, it might be a little troublesome to go through so many procedures, but Leylin was a Magus. With just some spells to confuse the target or alter memories, a lot of issues could be solved.

Besides, he could afford to spend a lot of money, so the opening of the shop was obviously a smooth sailing process.

The shop took up a large amount of space. At the front was the counter and shop, and behind was the storeroom and smelting room, as well as the rooms of Leylin and a few workers.

The moment one entered, they would see sharp weapons displayed on the wooden shelves lining two walls, glinting in the light. An icy feeling spread in the room.

“This is a first-rate steel weapon!”

A huge man who dressed like a mercenary entered immediately attracted to a large steel sword.

“This tempering technique is usually only found in a few large weapon shops!” The huge man caressed the sword, the silvery blue luster at the edges causing his eyes to be fixated on it.

The price marked on the shelf almost had him biting his tongue, “Fifty gold! This really is the price that would be found in the capital! But this is just a small town…”

The people in the Twilight Zone naturally had their own currency. The gold and silver used here were even more valuable than that of the south coast, and the currency was completely different.

In order to help mask his identity, the gold and silver pieces that Leylin used were actually the money he had gained from the south coast, the shapes of which he had forcefully changed to match the currency used here.

“What would you like?”

An intelligent-looking young man wearing the uniform of an attendant, who Leylin had hired, quickly asked with a smile.

“That sword is too expensive!”

The large man waved the sword around for a while, reluctant to part with it. “Can it be cheaper?”

“My apologies!” He had an apologetic smile on his face. “Our shop does not allow bargaining. This is a rule set by our boss!”

The large man’s face turned red, and he almost had the urge to cause a ruckus. However, he suppressed it.

Those who could make a living off of selling weapons usually had very powerful backgrounds; he wasn’t planning on dying just for this.

In addition, the shop owner wasn’t any regular person either. It was said that he was an adventurer of noble blood who had retired. Not only had he taken care of the department of internal affairs and the guards with an insane speed, even the baron had treated him as an important guest.

What was even more shocking was that the shop owner had a terrifying might that far exceeded that of the average adventurer.

This man had personally witnessed the young, black-haired shop owner take care of a few thugs, who wanted to extort protection fees, in a few seconds. They had subsequently been taken away by the guards, who had been informed and had arrived very quickly.

It was said that their fate was to become a labourer until their deaths!

These methods had intimidated a lot of people; after caressing the sword for a long time, as if it were his wife, the large man eventually reluctantly left.

Before leaving, he even had the young man reserve the sword, saying that he would return once he had enough money.

That night, after the last customer had left, the young man closed up and went to the room at the back.

*Knock knock!*

“Boss, can I come in?” The young man tried to make his voice sound calm.

Every time he saw his boss, he felt like he would suffocate. The imposing aura from his new boss was too intense; the young man swore that he had once seen a real count, but even he had lacked the elegance and dignified aura this man exuded.

“Perhaps my boss really is the successor of a very ancient noble family, and is merely experiencing the life here!” The young man thought in his heart, before thinking it funny. He was imagining the wildest of fantasies.

“Is it Baelin? Come in!” A very youthful voice sounded.

Baelin composed himself, opened the door and entered.

In the room, a handsome man in a loose robe was lying on a soft chair, occasionally drinking a beverage with peppermint mixed into it. He even had a huge black book in his hands.

He was literate and had books! This was the biggest sign of nobility in the Twilight Zone!

Chapter 294: Meteor Sword

“Baelin! Is anything the matter?”

Leylin gazed at the servant the baron had introduced to him and smiled.

“No, I’d just like to report the situation in the shop to you!” Baelin tried his best to be less nervous.

“Though there are a lot of people who show interest in our shop, boss, your prices… they’re a little too high, so it’s not good for business. I even think our shop will make a loss this month…”

“Is that so! I understand. You can go back now!”

Leylin waved his hands, looking as if he hadn’t been paying attention.

“Alright, you’re the boss! You call the shots!” Upon seeing this, Baelin could confirm that this Lord Leylin was probably a successor from an ancient noble family who was out here to experience life. If not, he definitely wouldn’t be taking things so lightly.

After Baelin left, Leylin started reading the book in his hands again.

On the yellowed parchment paper, red runes constantly moved like flames.

“To make a weapon from the Rays of Dawn is extremely difficult!” Leylin sighed.

The reason why he had opened this shop was to have his own smelting area while he recuperated. He could do some experimentation here.

As for those blades outside? They were only the products made on the side during experimentation.

Two years passed in a blur.

The residents of Potter Town were already used to this Master Leylin, the boss of the weapons shop.

Leylin rarely went outside, and barely took care of his weapons shop. Everything was left to Baelin, and he only would occasionally come over to supervise.

As he masked his identity well, nobody found out he was a Magus. At the most, they thought he was a young master from a noble family that was a wastrel.

In time, the words “Blazing Hammers” at the top of the shop were beginning to become mottled and show signs of decay.

The shop still had that lifeless aura to it. Though the weapons were known to be of superior quality, the prices were so expensive that people could only shrink back.

Leylin had no plans on relying on this shop to earn money. If the prices were too low, not only would business pick up, the other shops in the same industry would become jealous. Though he wasn’t afraid, Leylin didn’t want to stir up trouble over these small matters.

“Brother Baelin! I’m here again!”

Along with the voice, a boy with brown hair walked in through the entrance to the shop. He wore a linen short-sleeved shirt with some patches on it, and his eyes shone with intelligence.

“So it’s Longbottom!” Baelin had no choice but to greet him.

“Hehe, Brother Baelin, let me help you!” Longbottom snatched the cleaning rag from Baelin’s hands and began to wipe at the wooden shelves and cabinets.

His movements were practiced, and he was very familiar with the places that were often overlooked. Evidently, this was not the first time he was doing this.

After wiping the shelves and cabinets until they were sparkling clean, Longbottom expectantly looked at Baelin, waiting to be rewarded.

“Ugh, not again. Not again!” Baelin held his head, helpless.

“I told you! You’re only allowed to use it for five minutes, and you can’t tell anyone about this! You especially can’t let the boss find out!”

If not for this little kid’s beautiful sister, Baelin wouldn’t bother with him.

“I know, I know!”

Longbottom quickly nodded his head like a chick pecking at rice, and came before a shelf and took out a silver cross blade.

This cross blade was quite short, which was very fitting for Longbottom’s stature. It was about two fingers wide, and the hilt was made from pure silver. There was even a red diamond embedded within, making it seem very luxurious!

Evidently, with Longbottom’s financial background, he would definitely not be able to buy it no matter how much he saved up.

Longbottom held the cross blade carefully in his hands as if he were clasping some precious treasure.

“Hah!”

Longbottom slashed forward while holding the blade with both hands, making a crooked attack.

“Sigh… Little Longbottom, I’m not trying to be mean, but you’ll never be able to become a knight by learning with those normal soldiers!”

Baelin couldn’t help but shake his head. Potter Town was but a small one, and only the guards of the baron were knights. The rest were all made up of peasants, so what power could they have?

This Longbottom had wanted to become a knight from a very young age! For this reason, he would secretly watch the soldiers’ training.

After discovering this place, he would come over to help free of charge, with the price of having Baelin lend him something in the shop for him to play with for a while.

Out of everything in the shop, Longbottom’s favourite weapon was this cross blade.

“Brother Baelin, then who should I learn from?” Longbottom held the blade, his expression desolate, “I’m only the son of a regular hunter, and we can’t pay the expensive fees to go through training…”

Longbottom had someone in mind.

Ever since he had found out that the boss of the shop, Master Leylin, was a powerful knight, he was even more diligent in coming over. He might even become like the main characters in stories about knights, having a great talent in this area and ending up with Leylin taking a fancy to him!

“Sigh…” Looking at this, Baelin could only sigh. In Twilight Zone, it was extremely difficult for a regular person to become outstanding.

“Little Longbottom, I think you should give up on this impossible dream, and come over here to learn how to read from me every day!”

Baelin proposed seriously, “Though I don’t know that many letters, it’s enough for you to be able to read the accounts. When the time comes, you’ll be able to find some kind of bookkeeping job.”

“Thank you, Brother Baelin!” Longbottom was extremely touched. Even if he wanted to study from someone, he would need to pay an exorbitant fee, yet Baelin was actually willing to teach him for free. This was something that he was very grateful for.

“It’s nothing, it’s nothing!” Baelin turned red, “It’s for my own sake too. If boss were to see this, I might not even be able to keep my job…”

“See what…”

Leylin’s voice sounded, and Baelin was stunned.

Baelin stiffly turned back to the sight of Leylin, who had just entered.

“Bo- Boss! Why are you here now?” The smile on Baelin’s face was extremely stiff, and he was even stuttering while speaking.

He had let others play with the products in the shop, and that was already a huge offense. Leylin could fire him just like this! However, the pay here was so high to the point that Baelin was not willing to give up this job!

Baelin inwardly grumbled. Leylin had always been reclusive, and often stayed in his room or the smelting room, not making himself known for days on end. How could he be so timely today and meet with this sight?”

*Thud!*

Longbottom’s hands trembled, and the cross blade fell, producing a low thud as it hit the floor.

“Mas-Master Leylin!”

Longbottom called out while stuttering. For regular people like him, Leylin, the boss of a weapons shop, was an incredible person. Longbottom now felt like a thief who had been caught on the spot, and even his calves began to tremble.

“Oh?” Leylin shot a glance at the blade, and smiled at Baelin, “It looks like you’ve been having a lot of fun while I wasn’t around!”

“Boss! No, my lord! Please forgive me!” Baelin was so scared that he quickly knelt, while Longbottom’s body was already limp and he was unable to speak.

“I’ll settle this matter with you later!” Leylin glared at Baelin and spoke to Longbottom. “Kid, you have been touching the things in my shop as you pleased without gaining permission. How are you going to make it up to me?”

“My—My lord…” Longbottom’s teeth chattered and his voice sounded like he was crying. There were only regular people in his family, and they were perhaps even of a lower status to others. What could he give to make it up to Leylin?

“Alright! From today onwards, you are to report here and do some odd jobs here for two hours every day as compensation!

Having teased him enough, Leylin touched his chin and made his decision.

Longbottom was stunned. What terrified him the most was that Leylin might have wanted him to pay money, and then get the guards to throw him in jail. Odd jobs? What kind of punishment was that?

“What are you in a daze like that for? Quick, thank my lord!” Baelin quickly reacted and pressed Longbottom’s head down.

“Thank you so much, my lord! Thank you so much!” Longbottom only now reacted, gratitude apparent on his face.

To have a good reason to touch the weapons in the shop was basically a dream for him. He was even able to make a connection to Leylin, a legendary, powerful Knight. It was something he never imagined would happen!

“Alright! Come and work here starting tomorrow afternoon!”

Leylin nodded, turned, and went to the back of the shop.

Actually, Leylin had long since noticed Baelin and Longbottom’s actions, but he couldn’t be bothered with them. However, a few of his experiments were going quite well, and he was in a good mood.

After he entered his room, Leylin thought, “A.I. Chip! How’s the progress of the weapon blueprint simulation?”

[Beep! Weapon blueprint simulation: 100%. Completed setup of blueprint and runes!]

The A.I. Chip quickly intoned, and then sent an image of a weapon before Leylin’s eyes.

This was a black cross blade that looked to be very ordinary. It could be said to be ordinary to the extreme, but the cross section was filled with lines to loop energy, as well as runes.

[Design of exclusive weapon is complete, named “Meteor”] the A.I. Chip’s robotic voice sounded.

In these two years, Leylin had finally completely analysed the middle-grade magical artifact that was the weapon for the Branded Swordsman— the Rays of Dawn. He had combined all his knowledge on smelting and spell formations, in order to create his own exclusive weapon!

Chapter 295: Toying

Weapon | Meteor Sword (Warlock class-specific)
Length | 1.67m.
Width | 0.03m.
Carvings | High-grade energy converging runes

Fire elemental brand runes

Dark elemental amplification runes
Grade | High-grade magic artifact

The long sword the A.I. Chip projected in front of Leylin constantly rotated, and listed large quantities of data around it.

“The design is completed. All that’s left is to find the materials and actually make it.” Leylin was excited.

However, when he entered his sea of consciousness, this joy quickly dissipated.

After two years, the silver-white crystal in his sea of consciousness was still as resilient as ever, and had only shrunk a little in size.

The spiritual force it produced allowed Leylin to increase his might from that of a regular rank 1 Magus, to the strength of a peak rank 1 Magus.

As for the cracks at the edges of his sea of consciousness, they had yet to be completely restored.

The mark left behind by the rank 3 Magus, Alric, on the other hand, had been completely expelled by Leylin.

However, the stubbornness of the mark of spiritual force left behind by the rank 3 Magus had exceeded Leylin’s expectations. He had estimated that it would take around two months to dispel, but in reality, it had taken an entire year before he was able to completely remove the mark from his sea of consciousness.

“Perhaps I should find an opportunity to make contact with the Magi of the subterranean world!”

Due to his serious injuries, Leylin could only display the strength of a regular rank 1 Magus. Hence, he had chosen to lie low. However, now that he had regained enough of his strength to reach the peak of rank 1, he could be considered the best in the Twilight Zone, and it was natural that he would want to explore.

In addition, the progress of the reparation of his sea of consciousness was going very slowly, which made Leylin furrow his brows.

He was prepared to find some methods out there to hasten this process. If not, and he were to rely on just time, he had no idea how long this would take.

At this thought, Leylin began to feel jittery.

His expression twitched, and he untied a black water flask and took a drink. Leylin’s facial muscles then relaxed, and he forced a smile, “Also, I have to find a way to control the overly emotional side effects of being a Warlock!”

For Warlocks, the ancient bloodlines did give them formidable power, but they also negatively impacted their emotions

These emotions would lie dormant deep in one’s blood or even one’s spirit, occasionally causing trouble and causing the Warlock to sink into a state of extreme emotion.

For the Magus who sought truth and control, this was not tolerable.

Hence, Leylin had been searching for a method to solve this problem.

“The inheritances found in the south coast are only useful up to a certain point, and the items left behind from the ancient era are very few. There is very little information regarding Warlocks, and there doesn’t seem to be any sorts of methods there. But this place is different!”

Leylin’s eyes shone with hope. “This is the Twilight Zone, a part of the subterranean world! Due to the lack of connection with the outside world, it has very little external influences, and preserves the inheritances from ancient times in their entirety. In other words, aside from the central continent, there are still places that might have research material regarding warlocks; this must be one of those areas!”

At this thought, Leylin touched his chin.

“Potter Town is in a very remote area, and the resources at the Woody Wastelands can, at most, attract only a few acolytes. I haven’t seen any Magi here. It looks like I have to go deeper into the Twilight Zone…”

Potter Town was only a small town in the vastness of the Twilight Zone, and while he had stayed here for over two years, Leylin had seen very few Magi.

Apart from this town, there was an even bigger city. If he advanced layer by layer, he would find the eastern capital!

Leylin was sure that there were many Magi in the city!

The rules in the subterranean world were different from the south coast. The existence of Magi were made public; they would not hide in some unknown location and isolate themselves from the world.

The Magi who wielded power were naturally of a high status. Even the nobility had to bow to them.

“Though the population of Twilight Zone is only half of the south coast, with the extensive spread of high-grade meditation techniques and their simplified versions, there are still many instances of Magi appearing. The hierarchy of Magi is similar to that on the south coast, though I don’t know how many rank 3 Magi there are, or if there are any Morning Star Magi here…”

Leylin propped up his chin using his hand, sinking into deep thought.

……

The candle on the table burned with dull yellow flames, reflecting Leylin’s long, flickering shadow onto the wall…

During the afternoon of the next day, little Longbottom punctually came to the shop.

“You are very punctual! I like kids who obey rules!”

Leylin was bored to death, so he took over what had been Baelin’s position, and was yawning at the counter. He pointed towards the storeroom at the side. “Your task is to move those metals over there to the backyard!”

“Boss! Is this…” Baelin endured for a while, but could not take it any longer, and pointed to the storeroom as he spoke to Leylin.

“Every single one of those metals is even heavier than Longbottom’s own bodyweight…?”

Following his finger, one could see, through the half-open door to the storeroom, chunks of metal that were the size of a human head.

This were the raw materials that Leylin used while smelting. They were very dense, and their weights were terrifying.

When they had been transported here, Leylin had called for three strong men, and it had taken an entire afternoon for them to transport them. In Baelin’s eyes, Leylin was obviously making things difficult for the little kid by assigning him to such work.

“It’s his choice whether he wants to do it or not!”

Leylin shrugged his shoulders, found a chair, and began to doze contentedly.

“Brother Baelin, I want to give it a try!” Seeing the mountain of metals, he gulped, but at the sight of Leylin beginning to nod off, he made his mind and began to work.

The metals were very heavy, and just lifting it a centimeter off the ground caused Longbottom’s arms to tremble.

*Thud!* Longbottom curved his back and slowly moved to the open space at the back, the metal sounding a low thud as it fell.

“Hah…” Just moving one piece of metal was enough to cause Longbottom to pant, large drops of perspiration dripping from his face.

“Longbottom, you can’t continue, or else you’ll sustain long-term injuries…”

Baelin naturally knew that the terrifying amount of work he had to do would permanently harm, or even disable, a growing child’s body!

Even if he wasn’t doing this for Longbottom’s pretty sister, Baelin felt that he could not let this youngster he got along with to continue like this.

“No!” Longbottom looked in the direction of Leylin, who had stalked off, with a resolute expression on his face.

In that whole afternoon, the residents of Potter Town could see a strange sight at Leylin’s weapon shop.

A petite young boy was slowly working, moving pieces of black metal that were half his size.

That day, after completing two hours of work, Longbottom’s arms and legs constantly trembled, and he had no more strength to fiddle with any blades, dragging his fatigued body back home.

This went on for ten days, and only then did Longbottom finish moving all the metals to the open space at the backyard.

“You really work very slowly!”

Leylin judged, dissatisfied. “Next, I want you to move them back to the storeroom. Is that understood?”

“But Master Leylin…” Upon hearing this task, Longbottom’s body trembled. This physical labour had caused him a sore back, and it was so painful that he could not sleep at night. And now, he had to move them back? Longbottom felt like he would die from the fatigue!

He wasn’t just having fun here. He still needed to help his parents with work!

“Boss, you’re just toying with him!”

Baelin could not take this any longer, and jumped out while roaring at Leylin.

“Shut up.” Leylin spoke indifferently, but his glare caused Baelin to retreat while holding onto his chest and being unable to say a word.

“I’m the boss here, and what I say goes!” A teasing smirk was still about Leylin’s lips. “Youngster, you can leave right now, but if you do, you are to never return to my shop again!”

Longbottom was quiet, and then went to the metals without a word, and began to work.

“What an interesting fellow!”

Leylin poured himself a cup of peppermint beverage, leisurely watching Longbottom moving back and forth.

Leylin still needed to prepare for a period, and was quite rather bored. He only needed to pay brief attention to the calculations of the A.I. Chip, and could find time to toy with this youngster.

This labour was not something a child would be able to handle. In addition, it was easy to sustain injuries while working. Leylin had already discovered some bruises on Longbottom’s calves and arms.

“How long can he sustain this for? I look forward to it.”

Leylin touched his chin, a profound smile on his face.

For the next few days, Longbottom’s eyes were lifeless and he wobbled as he walked, causing people to be worried that this kid might just collapse and die.

An unexpected person also visited Leylin’s shop.

“Esteemed Master Leylin!” A beautiful young girl wearing a coarse sackcloth as a skirt curtsied towards Leylin.

“Could you please forgive my brother? Longbottom has been doing physical labour here for about fifteen days, and I’m afraid that he might not be able to hold on…”

This young maiden sobbed while she produced a white handkerchief.

After opening it, Leylin found that there were some silver coins and copper, as well as a small broken piece of gold coin that was about a quarter of the original size.

“If it’s for what he has done wrong, I’m willing to compensate you here…”

Leylin glanced at this young maiden and shook his head.

Chapter 296: Plot Twist

“I’ve mentioned it before. This is a mutual agreement. If your brother doesn’t want to do this, he’s free to leave at any time!”

Leylin spoke slowly.

“If you don’t believe me, you can ask him!” Leylin pointed at Longbottom, who was standing towards the side.

“Sister!” Longbottom ducked his head, a little afraid, but he sounded resolute, “It’s my own choice to work here at Master Leylin’s. It has nothing to do with him. Please don’t stop me.”

“You…” This young maiden was exasperated and pulled at Longbottom’s arm, revealing a large bruise, “Look at this. How are you still engrossed in these Knight fiction novels…”

“Cough cough!” Leylin suddenly coughed, interrupting her.

“This is my shop. If you wish to discipline your brother, please do it elsewhere and do not disrupt my business…”

Leylin said this boldly, though there were no customers in his shop right now.

“My- My apologies, my lord!” The young maiden covered her mouth, realising that her words just now were offensive to Leylin.

She bowed, revealing her fair breasts and quickly left with Longbottom in tow. The sounds of them arguing could still be heard.

Baelin watched her back, looking enchanted.

”What a pure, kind-hearted lady! Don’t you agree?” Leylin looked at Baelin, revealing a smile full of bad intentions.

“Of course! Miss Venus is a very diligent young lady, and works at three jobs outside in order to help with her family’s finances.”

Baelin subconsciously answered.

“Hm, I have no right to say anything about her kindness, but regarding her purity?” Leylin’s grin widened.

“Boss! You can scold me, but you can’t tarnish her reputation!” Baelin clenched his fist, and even his face turned red.

“Oh, love. Love! How beautiful it is! How vibrant, for it to even attract a moth into the flames! To make cowardly little lambs turn into savage, mighty beings!”

Leylin chanted some proverbs, and without waiting for Baelin to ask, he continued, “While Miss Venus was wearing coarse clothing, although she had tried her best to hide it, there was still the smell of cheaply-priced perfume. It’s not from today, and there’s still some eyeshadow on her face. Her handkerchief is a good quality product from Old Walker’s shop; she seems to have too much money… In just that short contact with her, she seemed to have tried to entice me at least three times! This must be some occupational habit…”

With every sentence that came out from Leylin’s mouth, Baelin felt like a sledgehammer had struck his chest, and he fell back.

However, Leylin continued on with a fatal blow, “If I’m not wrong, you might find Miss Venus at midnight at the well-known Night Warbler alley…”

“No! What you said can’t be true!”

Baelin’s face distorted, but his pale expression evidently meant that he believed Leylin’s words. He was stunned and suddenly roared, dashing out of the door.

“Hehe… The senseless dreams of youths!” Leylin laughed, having a great time.

“It’s really quite fun to destroy fantasies and let youths find out about the cruelty of life as soon as possible!”

Longbottom quickly returned with two very red handprints on his face. He didn’t say anything to Leylin and began his daily work.

As for Baelin, that poor fellow was said to have drank at a bar for an entire night. He only came to the shop the next day but was chased out by Leylin, who looked at him in disdain, wanting him to take care of the lingering smell of alcohol, lest he wouldn’t need to return.

*Boom!*

Seeing the last piece of metal moved to the storeroom, Longbottom, who was riddled with scars finally sighed with relief, glancing at Leylin with expectant eyes.

“Youngster, you’re smart and can persevere! From hereon, I declare that you are able to come to my shop for five minutes every day when nobody is around, and browse my products.”

Leylin tried his best to resist his laughter while announcing.

“Huh?” Longbottom raised his head, stunned.

“What’s wrong? Did you think I would take you in as my disciple and help you become a knight, and then you’d be a head above the rest, marry a princess, and live happily ever after?”

Leylin had on a teasing smile, “Kiddo, you’re still too immature.”

Longbottom turned pale in embarrassment now that his plan had been seen through.

“You liar! You’re a liar!” He yelled, and quickly ran out.

*Pak!* As he had run too quickly, he had tripped by the road and fallen onto the ground, getting soil all over him.

“Haha!” “Haha…” “Come look! Isn’t that the fool from Blazing Hammers?”

The pitiful sight of Longbottom attracted the unfeeling attention of the passersby.

Under their ridicule, Longbottom yelled and frantically left as soon as he could.

Leylin supported his weight by the door, beaming as he watched.

“Boss, you’re so mean! No, you’re terrible!” Baelin stood behind Leylin with dark circles under his eyes. His face had become gaunt as he muttered at Leylin.

“Hehe… It’s not like this is the first day since you became acquainted with me!” Leylin shrugged and came to the backyard.

He produced a black cross blade, the design of which was extremely similar to the Meteor long sword designed by the A.I. Chip. However, there were no energy waves emanating from this sword at all.

This was the imitation that Leylin had made using the design for the Meteor” sword. Only the outer appearance and weight were similar, and there were no energy runes or anything of the sort within.

“Hah!” Leylin lifted the blade and thrust forward, doing a move that looked like it came straight out of a textbook!

The sharp blade slashed out and cut the air, producing a piercing, explosive sound.

Though the Meteor long sword had yet to be made, Leylin had begun to make preparations beforehand so that he could get used to the weapon quicker.

Thrust! Slash! Strike!

Leylin suddenly turned into multiple figures on the ground, each of which held poses that were paused in mid-air.

At the end, Leylin leaped, “Cross Slash!”

A huge cross streaked across a huge rock in the area.

*Bang! Bang! Bang! Bang!*

Under Leylin’s Cross Slash, the rock turned into four large parts.

“This…” Baelin was dazed at Leylin’s terrifying might and gaped like a huge toad.

“I’ve seen the knights from the baron’s residence attack, but their offensive power isn’t to this extent. Could Master Leylin be a legendary Grand Knight?”

Baelin was so stunned that he could not even close his mouth.

“What? Do you want to learn?” Leylin picked up a white towel and wiped his hands. Seeing Baelin in this state, he smiled and asked.

“Yes! …No, I… Don’t…” Baelin was confused, and his speech became incoherent.

“So? Do you want to, or do you not want to?” Leylin grinned.

Baelin only managed to react after a long while, still disbelieving that he would get such an opportunity. He was afraid of being cheated by Leylin. “Boss! Oh, no, master! I mean, I’m already 19 and I’m quite old. I’ve never had any official training and can only recognise a few words. Isn’t it best to start training to become a knight as soon as possible? If you want a disciple, I think Longbottom is even more suitable than I am…”

Though he said this, Baelin’s breathing became rough in the face of such a huge temptation.

“If you really want a reason, there’s only one.” Leylin spoke slowly, and Baelin’s ears couldn’t help but perk up.

“Because I’m happy! Is this reason enough?”

Leylin beamed. Warlocks were really quite impulsive beings.

In addition, Leylin felt that it wasn’t good to keep suppressing the emotions of a warlock. He needed to find some way to vent, and since he found Baelin pleasing to the eye, he decided to do as he wished.

“Alright! In the face of such a mighty reason, Baelin could only laugh helplessly.

“If Longbottom found out that this was the reason, he’d definitely cry himself to death!” Baelin thought inwardly.

“So? Do you want to learn?”

“Of course! I do!” Baelin agreed right away. He would be an idiot if he were to reject at this point!

*Pak!* A wooden sword was thrust, striking Baelin’s face.

This poor guy collapsed, finding it difficult to climb back up.

“Your footwork is too slow. You need to ensure your footsteps and breath are in sync. Understood?”

Leylin was dressed in black as he stood in front of Baelin, “Get up!”

“Un-understood, my lord!” Baelin sucked in a cold breath and was somewhat able to get up. Leylin had been controlling his strength well; he had used just enough strength to cause Baelin pain, but not inflict internal injuries.

When Leylin had first agreed to train him, Baelin had planned to call Leylin ‘Mentor’, but Leylin naturally did not want a disciple, and had rejected his idea without a second thought.

After an hour of swordplay practice, they came to the breathing method.

“For knights, what they are training is their life energy, which is also known as their life essence!” Leylin instructed with zeal.

“About 5cm below the lower abdomen, in an inverted triangle area. This is where we think we can cultivate the spirit. Training to become a knight happens by manipulating the frequency of breathing, adjusting the secretions within the body, and hence producing more life essence.”

Leylin began to impart his knowledge regarding the cross blade breathing technique, which he had reorganised, to Baelin.

He was now extremely knowledgeable, and the information stored in his mind was plentiful. He also had experience from grooming his Branded Swordsmen. He had simply optimized his Farlier Family’s Cross Blade breathing technique and had upgraded it quite a bit.

Based on Leylin’s estimations, his version of the breathing technique could probably be considered the best, even amongst Grand Knights.

Chapter 297: Baelin and the Girl

“Breathe out! Breathe in! Focus! Pay attention to the frequency!”

Baelin had taken off his shirt, revealing some muscle that he had gained after all these days of training. He sat cross-legged, closed his eyes, and inhaled deeply; the muscles on his body shook as he breathed.

“No, your abdominal muscles are moving incorrectly!” With a swing of his arms, a wooden sword mercilessly hacked at Baelin’s lower abdomen.

Baelin’s face twisted, and the muscles there withdrew. *Hah!* Two white streams of air exited from his nostrils.

“Remember it? This is the feeling!”

Leylin patted using the wooden sword.

“Hah…” After training a complete round in the breathing method, Baelin expelled a long breath, some black impurities could be found in the white gas that he let out. He opened his eyes.

“Are you a pig? It took you ten days to understand the surface of this simple breathing technique!”

Leylin scolded, and Baelin could only rub his head and laugh, continuously apologising.

After so many days of training, he could feel the sturdiness of his body increasing. With the help of the breathing technique, he could begin to feel some warmth flowing in his body.

The intoxicating feeling he gained from achieving power made Baelin addicted to it. Even if Leylin wanted to kill him now, he wouldn’t leave no matter what.

“Go. A thousand times of the sword swings, and five thousand squats!” Leylin pointed, and Baelin immediately complied.

“I didn’t think that this random fellow that I decided to teach would actually have some talent!”

The corner of Leylin’s lips curved up into a smile as he watched Baelin perspire in the small field.

Baelin was evidently suited to the path of the knight. If Leylin had not used the A.I. Chip, Baelin might not even be able to scratch the surface of the improved cross blade breathing technique in ten days and grasp life essence. However, he had done it!

“However, I’ve never really had the talent to become a knight. In comparison, this speed would probably mean Baelin is an unprecedented talent! I wonder how his spiritual aptitude is?”

The spiritual aptitude of regular people was not very obvious. Unless he had access to specific spells or supplementary tools, even Leylin could not tell the talent that one had for magic.

“It looks like I have to stay here for a period of time…”

Leylin’s expression darkened. Though he had planned on looking for other Magi, the sudden explosion of his emotions due to his Warlock blood had delayed his schedule.

Leylin could only use a few common methods to slowly let out the emotions in his heart. Also, he could only brew a few potions of a higher grade than the potion of tranquility to suppress his symptoms.

His plans after arriving in the Twilight Zone would be related to the obtaining of high-grade meditation techniques. He would not allow himself to wander around while he was still in this highly emotional state. If he did, there was an 80% chance that things would turn out like when he was robbing the essence of the Wisdom Tree and incited the anger of multiple people, who then chased after him.

Unwittingly, six months passed.

Without knowing it, since the whole process was so smooth, Baelin activated the life energy in his body and became a real knight.

This miserable fellow saw that he was unable to withstand even one move from Leylin and thought that he was still a regular human. Therefore, he worked hard towards his goal of becoming a knight

The one effect of his becoming a Knight was being able to withstand one strike from Leylin before collapsing.

As for Longbottom, Leylin did not see him anymore. It was said that that kid, who was unwilling to admit failure, had followed a bunch of traders going to trade at a city, and was hoping to get lucky.

It was a pity that Leylin had seen plenty of youngsters struggling outside with their dreams in mind. Out of a hundred, ninety would die without reason, and the majority of the remainder would become beggars, disabled, thieves, or criminals.

Only one percent would be successful.

Leylin had listened to Baelin talk about this for a while and had thrown this matter to the back of his mind.

“Hah!”

Baelin brandished the large steel sword in his hand, the blade glinting with a cold, sharp light, roaring as he charged towards Leylin.

“Kill!” He struck with his large sword, which in its wake brought a fierce gale.

On the other hand, Leylin was holding a wooden sword and shook his head, “Too many excess movements!”

With just a gentle thrust forward, the wooden sword entered the metallic rays of light.

What seemed to be a gentle, slow attack from the wooden sword pushed Baelin’s steel sword away, and the wooden sword pierced Baelin’s armpit!

“Ugh…” Baelin groaned and collapsed.

“Disappointing! Too disappointing!” Leylin bluntly struck him down.

During his free time after researching, he would tease this guy. It was one of the many pleasures he had in his spare time.

“My lord, can’t you let me win a little?”

Baelin huffed and puffed, complaining as he sat on the ground, “I’m always defeated in one blow! Gosh! I feel like I haven’t been improving at all…”

“Stop with the nonsense! Continue training. To punish you for being unable to withstand one move, you are to do a thousand more push-ups!”

Leylin tried his best not to laugh as he showed a poker face.

In fact, Baelin was improving extremely quickly. He was on the verge of advancing to become a Grand Knight. On one hand, this had to do with the effectiveness of the breathing method Leylin had provided. On the other, Baelin’s talent and diligence could not be disregarded.

Leylin reclined on a deck chair, watching Baelin sweating, but his thoughts were all on the A.I. Chip.

[Beep! Based on the real-time monitoring, host body’s secretion of adrenaline is at a low level, and mental status is becoming stable. Estimated to reach normal level in 341 hours!]

Through the diagrams and curve that the A.I. Chip analysed, Leylin was overjoyed to find that after all his efforts, his emotions were stabilising.

“Based on this pace, I’ll be able to completely suppress the explosion of my emotions in ten or so days…” Leylin grinned.

“Boss! Is the boss here?”

At this moment, a young man’s voice travelled over, “We want to buy something. Is the boss of Blazing Hammers around?”

Upon hearing this voice, Baelin stopped his training. “Oh, my heavens! There’s someone actually coming to boss’ shop? Has the sun risen from the west?”

Due to Leylin’s unconventional pricing, only a few items were sold every year despite the excellent quality of the weapons in the shop.

“What are you talking about! Go and entertain the customer!” Leylin’s sword knocked on Baelin’s head.

At this moment, Baelin remembered that his real identity was a worker employed to man the weapon shop. He immediately put on a white shirt and jogged out to receive the customer.

Leylin was a little curious and followed him out.

“My lady, please come in!”

Baelin seemed to be fawning over a girl of noble blood, who was wearing sophisticated clothing and had a ring with strange inscriptions on it. He made eyes at Leylin, indicating they were going to make a huge sale.

Behind this noble girl was an old man with silver hair that seemed to be a butler. Behind this man were two young guards wearing armour made of iron mail. The one who had shouted was evidently one of the guards.

On the shoulder of the guard, there was a large crest with sun vines adorning it. In the middle were a sword, shield, and a crown!

Leylin was learned in the area of the coat of arms, and naturally knew that no matter which society they were in, only the first-rate nobility were able to use a crown in their crest.

“Interesting! A daughter of a noble? She even has an acolyte and two knights protecting her!”

Leylin gazed at this group of people with interest. The butler behind the girl was obviously a level 3 acolyte, and he even had a low-grade magic artifact, judging from the energy waves it gave off.

The guards behind them were guards with the strength of knights.

Even this girl herself also produced undulations from energy particles and had the power of a rank 1 acolyte. All sorts of amplification type rings were on her fingers.

At this moment, the four guests were surprised at Baelin, who was treating them so politely—not every shop had a Knight that would service guests!

Baelin, who was still oblivious to everything, was politely introducing to the girl, “My lady, if you wish to go to the Woody Wasteland, I recommend this steel sword! Its workmanship is first rate, and there won’t be any nicks even after killing thousands. If you couple it with these arrowheads, it’s even more perfect…”

Baelin’s saliva flew everywhere as he opened another cabinet, revealing a bunch of arrowheads that looked completely new and was giving of a turquoise luster.

This eagerly attentive display that might even be seen to be overly humble had Leylin laughing inside. The two soldiers behind the girl turned, a little embarrassed at seeing a knight just like them, who seemed to be tarnishing their reputation.

In fact, if not for their owner being right in front, they would long since have drawn their swords and taught this fellow who knew nothing about the dignity of knights a lesson.

“Look!” The noble girl spoke to the old butler behind her.

The butler with the strength of a level 3 acolyte went forward, touching the steel sword with his wrinkly hands and then touching the arrowhead, shock apparent on his face, “The quality is not bad! It can even be compared with the works of the Great Master Yoda.”

“Oh?” The surprise was evident on this girl’s face. This was the first time she had seen her butler praise any item, and even more so comparing it to Great Master Yoda? That was a Master who had earned a reputation in the eastern capital from forging weapons, and was extremely popular with the public!

“Who forged the weapons here?” She asked, looking at Baelin. After all, his bulging muscles were very enchanting.

Leylin, who concealed his power very well, was naturally ignored.

“Oh, those!” Baelin was about to brag about his boss, but upon seeing Leylin’s warning look, he corrected himself, “That’s obviously a secret!”

Chapter 298: Rescue

“Is that so?” The girl lifted her brows, and even Baelin couldn’t bear to keep eye contact.

“Please pass on this message to that great master! I would like to meet him, and our Argus Family welcomes him to our door!” She spoke in an aloof manner.

The guard behind her immediately took out a sculpture that looked similar to the crest on his shoulder and passed it to Baelin.

“This! This! And those arrows. We want them all!”

The girl pointed at the display cabinet.

“Alright, alright!” Baelin was so excited that he was flushed red. He didn’t even have the time to analyse the crest in his hand, and immediately packed up the swords and other weapons, passing them to the guards behind her.

“The total is 1050 Gold! Thank you for your patronage!”

Baelin nodded at the girl, and the butler passed a small bag of gold coins and a purple-gold card to him. Baelin was on the verge of becoming stupid as his hand trembled while holding the bag.

The girl saw his movements and a glint of mischievousness appeared in the young noble’s eyes.

“I wish to go to the Woody Wastelands! Can you be my guide? I’ll pay 10 Gold per day.”

“Ten- Ten Gold?” Baelin’s breathing became rough.

While working in Leylin’s shop, the pay was 3 Gold per month; this was already a pay grade that made the residents of Potter Town incomparably envious.

Ten Gold a day? This was something Baelin had never even dreamed of!

“But!” Baelin looked at Leylin and gritted his teeth as he rejected the suggestion. “My apologies, my lady! I must work here every day…”

Though Baelin wanted to make some quick money, he was still able to make a distinction between the present and the future.

Leylin was currently teaching him how to train to become a knight! This was only available in specific noble families of the Twilight Zone, and he would not have another chance to get it, even with over a thousand Gold!

If he gave this up just for a little Gold, that would mean giving up his future as a Knight; Baelin felt that he would completely regret that choice of action.

“Interesting, interesting! I never thought I’d discover such an intriguing shop on this trip!”

The girl laughed like a skylark.

“My name is Jenny, and I live in the largest inn in the town. If you change your mind, you can come look for me at any time.”

After the girl and her companions left, Baelin carefully placed the gold and purple-gold card on the table.

“The purple-gold card that is valued at a thousand Gold! It’s the first time I’ve ever seen this, and in addition, there are so many gold coins. My lord! We’ve struck it rich!” Baelin’s eyes were full of little stars.

“Yeah, yeah!” Leylin nodded, paying no mind as he kept the purple-gold card.

“The rest of the gold shall be yours as a commission!”

“Oh, boss, let me praise you! You’re really the master of fairness, the embodiment of compassion…” Baelin immediately began to cheer.

He tossed the crest up and down in his hand, puzzled. “This seems quite familiar! I recall hearing something about this Oscar Family from somewhere before…”

Suddenly, he shrieked, “Damn it! Sun Vine Argus! It’s the marquis family in the eastern capital! What did I just give up…”

However, although Baelin sighed, he did not pursue this matter any further.

After all, they weren’t going to take him in as a servant, but only as a guide. It would be a very stupid decision to reject Leylin’s teachings here.

The appearance of the Marquis’ daughter here obviously made her the topic of conversation in Potter Town. Leylin could hear the latest news about this group from Baelin.

“My Lord! My Lord! Apparently, Miss Jenny came to this place in order to prepare to obtain a very special birthday gift for her mother! She’s preparing to look for it in the wastelands. What a filial daughter she is!”

“Haha… I found out that Miss Jenny is looking for a special plant called the Dragon-Blooded Flower Bud! It’s said to help women maintain their looks for ten years, and can even be sold off at an auction in the eastern capital for almost a hundred thousand Gold! After offering a reward for it, all the adventurers, mercenaries and even residents of the town have begun to pour into the Woody Wastelands to look for it, dreaming of getting rich quickly!”

“My Lord! I just saw Miss Jenny entering the Woody Wastelands while being guided by the baron’s knights…”

Baelin was as excited as a sparrow, chirping in front of Leylin; Leylin just rolled his eyes.

“Have you completed your homework for today?”

With that single sentence, Baelin completely quieted down and scratched his head.

“No, but I’ll be done soon!” Having said this, Baelin quickly rushed to the training grounds and began to wave around a large sword that was about the height of a person.

“You still have the mind to think about running around outside of training. You seem to have a lot of excess energy!” Leylin grinned, “I’ll multiply the tasks you have to do for today.”

“Oh! No!” Hearing Baelin’s anguished wailing, Leylin felt his mood improve.

“Oh, Dragon-Blooded Flower Bud?” Leylin touched his chin and searched up some information recorded by the A.I. Chip from the ancient ruins.

He seemed to have seen records about this sort of precious plant in ancient books. It was said that it lived in a very harsh environment and needed to coexist with a high energy being, taking in the blood of this being every once in awhile, or else it would wilt.

“I remember that the high-energy being coexisting with the Dragon-Blooded Flower Bud is called the Goat-Horned Earth Dragon. It’s said to be a mix between an ancient dragon and some demon, though I have no idea how true that information is…”

Leylin pondered deeply, “In addition, the beautification effect of the Dragon-Blooded Flower Bud is just a side effect. The main use of the Dragon-Blooded Flower Bud is to combat specific toxins…”

“Interesting. I was just searching for a good reason to enter the eastern capital!” Leylin glanced at Baelin who was still wailing but did not dare stop training, a fierce light glinting in his eyes.

Three days later, a small group laden with injuries returned to Potter Town, bringing back horrifying news.

The team with the Marquis’ daughter had met with unexpected danger while chasing after the Goat-Horned Earth Dragon and were stuck somewhere. Even the baron’s knight team captain had sacrificed himself.

This team had risked their lives to return and seek help.

The entire town sank into terror. The fury of a Marquis was something Potter Town could not take on, and the person most afraid of the headstrong daughter were the owner of the area, Baron Joseph.

“My lord! My lord! I heard that…”

Baelin rushed into the yard like a gust of wind, to the sight of a plump man in luxurious clothes, constantly using a gold-coloured handkerchief to wipe the sweat on his face.

He was instantly like a duck held by the neck, his words stuck in his throat as he bowed, “Hello, Sir!”

This plump man was obviously Baron Joseph, the man in charge of Potter Town. Even Baelin’s current job had been introduced to him by this man. For Baelin, someone with land and an inheritance could be said to be an amazing person, and as a result, he was so shocked that he quickly greeted the baron, his head at his chest.

“So it’s Baelin! Do your job well!”

Baron Joseph did not seem to have any interest in conversing with him, and instead bowed towards Leylin with a smile, “Well then, I’ll leave it to you, Great Master Leylin!”

In order to settle down, Leylin had used mental spells as well as having left a very powerful image in Joseph’s mind.

Hence, now that he had met with trouble that he could do nothing about, Joseph quickly came to Leylin as soon as he could.

“My lord! What happened?”

Baelin waited until Joseph left before asking.

“What else could it be other than to save that willful girl?” Leylin spoke indifferently, picking out a shining set of armour from the storeroom.

“Ooh, ooh! Oh! My lord, are you going to take action?”

As Leylin’s shop assistant and semi-disciple, Baelin was very curious about Leylin’s past and his power, extremely excited.

“Bring me, my lord! I’m sure you’ll lack a servant in the Woody Wastelands, right?”

“Bring me! You have to bring me!”

*Boom!* A large set of Knight’s armour was thrown at Baelin. “Try it on!”

“Oh! Alright!” Wearing armour was part of training to become a knight. Baelin had trained a lot, but it was his first time officially wearing armour. He was so excited that he was slightly flushed.

This shiny armour unexpectedly fit him very well. There were even some patterns at the sides of the metal, and the leather plating underneath. Not only was it beautiful, it could also protect a few areas; Baelin loved it.

After training for such a long period of time, Baelin had also grown taller. He had beautiful muscles, and after wearing the armour, he looked extremely brave and courageous.

“How is it? I’m handsome, aren’t I?” Baelin patted his chest narcissistically, and two pieces of metal struck each other, producing a loud sound.

“Next!” Leylin tossed a steel sword to Baelin, and after he had worn and put everything into place, Leylin nodded in satisfaction.

“I can relax now!”

“Of course! Huh? Relax? What about?” Baelin was bewildered.

“Young man, the mission to save the princess will fall to you?” Leylin tried to hold back his laughter, patting Baelin’s shoulder while speaking in a heartfelt, meaningful manner. Baelin was stunned.

“Huh? Huh?! Me?! You want me to go to the Woody Wastelands alone?” Baelin finally reacted, pointing at his own nose.

“My lord, I’m not even a knight! Are you trying to kill me?”

“It can’t be helped!” Leylin spread his hands, “Someone must stay behind to look after the shop! Youngsters like you need to be more energetic!”

“My lord, forgive me for my being so direct about this, but you sell but a few items per year. It doesn’t make a difference whether you watch the shop or not. In addition, there’s a large difference between being energetic and sending myself to my death!”

Chapter 300: Goat-Horned Earth Dragon

“Your goal is to become a Grand Knight! The distant stars are your goal!”

Leylin’s voice was filled with emotion, causing Baelin’s blood to heat up.

“Though your Knight training method came from me and is said to be the best of the best even by the standards of Grand Knights, you lack something important that the strong possess!”

“The strong? Something important?” Confusion appeared on Baelin’s face.

“Exactly! That is real bloody battles and confidence. The Knights who lacked the training methods you have developed their unrivalled confidence through constant bloody battles, smoothly stimulating their life energy and becoming Knights! You lack this process…”

“Hence, you need to take on an even more difficult task to stimulate your potential!”

Leylin’s expression looked like he was trying to tell Baelin it was all for his own good. “How about it? Can you see what I’m doing for you?”

“Though I don’t understand, it seems cool!” Baelin clenched his fists, “I’ll work hard, my lord!”

Next, this little fool who had been duped by Leylin began to truly prepare to leave the following day.

Seeing him in a frenzy of preparation, Leylin shook his head as he gave a gentle smile.

“Youths really forget things quickly. He was duped so easily…”

However, to make use of Jenny, this noblewoman, to enter the capital, Leylin didn’t mind helping them.

“Your sword…” Leylin took Baelin’s steel sword, which he had been holding. Having gone through numerous forging, it still held a cold glint, but a chip the size of an ant had appeared on the blade.

This kind of nick could only be formed from countless strikes made by a Knight using his full power. It was evident that Baelin had met with more dangers in the Woody Wastelands than just those Explosive Flaming Wolves.

“What’s wrong, my lord?” Baelin’s expression displayed his puzzlement.

“This sword is too old and not suitable for your expedition. I’ll give you a new one!” The corner of his lips lifted in a smile.

“Thank you! Thank you so much, my lord!” Baelin was so excited that he was almost incoherent in his gratitude.

After this battle, he finally discovered how difficult it was to groom a knight. On one hand, there was the secrecy of the breathing techniques, and on the other hand, there were the immense expenses in training and obtaining equipment.

Equipment forged by experts had a value of over 100 Gold. However, after explosively using his life essence a few times, a chip had appeared.

Wouldn’t regular weapons have simply snapped?

Knights grew through battles, and he wondered how many of these weapons would have to be used for this growth.

Baelin had originally intended to repair this sword and continue to use it. After all, he was used to living in poverty and couldn’t bear to waste resources. However, Leylin had simply given him another one!

“Don’t worry, I’ll send the bill to Ms. Jenny.”

However, Leylin’s next words caused Baelin’s grateful heart to burst into smithereens, “She’s the daughter of the Marquis and probably has more gold than their family will ever need. It doesn’t matter if they pay a little, right?”

Leylin tossed a new sword to Baelin.

“Aw, my lord! Can’t you let me continue to feel touched by your actions for a while longer?”

Baelin lamented, though his hands were not the least bit dissatisfied as he caught the sword.

*Clang!* Baelin gently caressed the sword, the blue edge of the blade having detailed, complicated patterns, and a cold air was emitted from it.

Based on his intuition after working here for so many years, Baelin could tell this was absolutely one of the best steel swords in the shop.

What he didn’t notice was that before his lamenting, Leylin’s palm had stroked the blade of the sword and left behind a dull red imprint.

This imprint had been carved into the sword itself and disappeared, and Baelin had not noticed at all.

……

Jenny’s team had rested and reorganized themselves in Potter Town and set off.

Though most of the adventurers and mercenaries who had followed her the last time had died or been injured, there was no lack of people who were so poor that they wanted to take the risk and strike it rich.

Jenny had simply given out a large amount of gold and gathered enough people. Of course, their strength was nothing much.

She had little choice. In Twilight Zone, the Goat-Horned Earth Dragon was a very rarely seen high-energy being. Only recently had people found traces of it in the Woody Wasteland.

If she let this opportunity go, she had no idea when she would get another chance to come across it.

Even if Jenny could wait, Marquis Argus — who was being tormented by poison — could not wait that long!

“Baelin, we’re depending on you!” There was another person in the group, and it was Baelin in his new armour. He had repaired it through the night, and he was somewhat able to continue using it. On his back was the sword that Leylin had messed with, giving him a very brave and formidable aura, and even caused some girls in the town to throw him coquettish glances.

Now, however, with just a word from Jenny, Baelin was elated.

Feeling the reverence of the adventurers around him, as well as the ardent pleas from the noble girl, Baelin felt like he had downed several bottles of strong alcohol, and was beginning to feel giddy.

“I never imagined I, Baelin, would have such an impressive moment!” Baelin nodded as he glanced at Jenny, admiration apparent in his gaze, “Don’t worry, I’ll definitely obtain the Dragon-Blooded Flower Bud!”

“Sigh, that pitiful fellow!”

Seeing Baelin so crazy over his young miss, James, who was standing to one side, couldn’t help but sigh under his breath.

So what if he was a Grand Knight? With the might of the Argus Family, they could easily summon a dozen of them! The person they really cared about was Sir Leylin, the person backing Baelin!

In Twilight Zone, only the mysterious lord Magi were suitable for his young miss to bow her head to.

“In addition, our young miss is an acolyte! Though her level is low, not just any regular person can do it.”

James sighed even more deeply.

The aptitude to become a Magus was a very mysterious thing. However, after many years of research, Magi found that if one of the parents was a Magus, there was a high likelihood that their descendants would have an increased aptitude. If both were Magi, the chances of acolytes could even rise up to 33%!

In addition, within this group of acolytes, there was a higher chance of them having outstanding talent.

For this reason, unless there were exceptions, any females in noble families who had the aptitude to become a Magus were not allowed to marry outside of their family. Their only fate was to marry their close relatives and produce an heir who would have greater aptitude!

The Argus Family might be happy to have a female peasant with an aptitude to become a Magus marry into the family. However, they would absolutely not tolerate it if Magi in their family married outside, even if they were merely acolytes!

Of course, neither Baelin nor Jenny was thinking that far.

Even Baelin himself had automatically gotten serious after entering the Woody Wasteland, blindly hurrying in order to preserve energy.

He had grown up in Potter Town and naturally knew of the terrors here. Many areas that seemed to be safe ground might take the lives of any adventurer at any time.

He was Baelin, someone about to become a Grand Knight! How could he die here?

“There’s something in front!”

All of a sudden, the team in front cheered, and Baelin immediately braced himself, approaching them.

“We discovered this! Come take a look!”

Jenny had changed into garments suitable for hunting and now looked more capable and experienced. She was now pointing at a large footprint on the ground as if she had seen some treasure.

Baelin crouched down. In front of him was a footprint almost a metre long.

The owner had left a very deep footprint, with four claw marks sunk deeply into the ground.

“There are five joints in the middle toe, and the smell is correct. This is it! This was left behind by a Goat-Horned Earth Dragon!”

James had also approached them. After using some strange item in his hands to probe it, he spoke to Jenny with conviction.

“What are we waiting for?”

She had a smile on her face. Though her target was right in front of her, she did not impatiently forge ahead.

“We’ll find a place to set up camp for today! All scouts are to move out and follow the footprint, and you must find the lair of the Goat-Horned Earth Dragon!”

Jenny’s purpose in coming here was to obtain the Dragon-Blooded Flower Bud of the Goat-Horned Earth Dragon. This special plant only coexisted with the Goat-Horned Earth Dragon, and it was hence necessary that they find its lair.

“I shall reward anyone who can find the lair of the Goat-Horned Earth Dragon with a hundred gold coins!”

In order to find the Dragon-Blooded Flower Bud as soon as possible, Jenny did not mind giving out large rewards, and it immediately resulted in loud roars.

Many adventurers who were originally not scouts left as well, wanting to try their luck. If they received this reward, and if combined with their own savings, they could practically retire already.

“They…” Baelin had a look on his face that showed he couldn’t bear to watch these adventurers leave.

He was not an idiot. In contrast, he was rather intelligent and knew Jenny’s intention in doing that.

These adventurers lacked strength or any special abilities. Their only function was to act as cannon fodder and bait!

Now that they had entered the territory within which the Goat-Horned Earth Dragon was active, they would inevitably attract its action with all these adventurers running around.

They would be able to find the dragon as long as they followed the blood-curdling screams or blood.

“It can’t be helped, Baelin!” Jenny laughed bitterly, “I’ll make it up to their families later…”

When the sun descended, three people did not return.

Jenny was overjoyed as she chased in the direction that the three had moved in.

“Here!” Baelin picked up a rock on the floor, his expression complicated as he looked at the blood stains and some bits of cloth on that stone.

Chapter 301: Pursuit

Under the bright, flickering torchlight, there were traces of the chaos that had occurred, such as blood and remnant flesh.

It was obvious that before having its meal, the Goat-Horned Earth Dragon had toyed with its food.

At this sight, the faces of the adventurers around darkened.

Outside of this site, there was a long line of bloodstains, causing it to appear as a bloody trail.

“Follow it!”

With Jenny’s command, the group lifted their torches and did as asked.

Twilight Zone was underground and was shrouded in darkness all year around. However, the surviving humans had yet to evolve and have night vision, thus, torches were one of the essential items when exploring in the Twilight Zone.

“The footprints are more concentrated here!”

Baelin lifted his torch with one hand, the other tightly grasping the handle of his steel sword. His joints had turned a little white from using too much strength.

A piercing stench was beginning to pervade the air, to the point that Baelin associated it with the time he had worked at a horse stable when he was younger.

Next, with the illumination by everyone, a small hill made of black rocks appeared. At the foot of the hill was a large cave that extended deeply into the side, hollowing it out.

“We can’t fight it in its lair. We need to lure it out!”

Jenny decided after looking.

With this dim lighting, it was bound to affect the Dragon-Blooded Flower Bud if they were to fight in the small lair. If the bud was damaged, there would be no point even if Jenny and the rest killed the dragon.

“Don’t worry, the Goat-Horned Earth Dragon has very low intelligence and is very sensitive to the smell of blood. We can use that and set up a trap.”

James stood out at this moment and under his command, the adventurers set up a simple trap outside the cave.

As resources were limited and they couldn’t alert the Earth Dragon inside, James chose the simplest trap — poison!

A black being that looked like a goat was forced to drink an entire bottle of a red potion, and was laid across the cave. Its four legs were tied together, and its main artery was slashed open causing fresh blood to spurt out. A small puddle of blood was quickly formed on the ground.

The adventurers beside it had long since put out their torches and patiently waited aside, not even daring to breathe loudly at this point.

Baelin’s hands were on his sword, glancing at Jenny, who was extremely nervous, and James, who looked grim. He himself looked determined.

*Thud thud! Thud thud!*

Only ten or so minutes passed, but in the hearts of everyone present, it felt like centuries had passed. Finally, just when the adventurers were beginning to get impatient, dull footsteps and slight tremors of the ground could be felt.

“It’s here! Get ready!”

The adventurers who were lying in wait outside ducked their heads, retrieving their weapons and bow and arrows, aiming them at the mouth of the cave.

“Hah…”

The sounds of heavy breathing resounded, followed by an increase of the concentration of the strange smell by more than ten times! The goat that was bait could only give a miserable shriek.

*Crunch! Crunch!*

Along with the sounds of chewing, the bleating of the goat stopped.

“Is this the Goat-Horned Earth Dragon?” As he was now a Knight, Baelin’s eyesight was very good. With just the faint light, he could somewhat see the figure of this monster.

This monster was about fifteen to sixteen metres long, and its four thick limbs supported its large body, its sharp claws scratching out a long straight line on the ground.

Above its yellow eyes, two curved black horns were grown, like the symbol of a demon.

With the opening and closing of its mouth, sharp teeth constantly meshed together and chewed the goat into bits, flesh and blood flying.

“On my command. Go!”

James swung his arm, and a rock the size of a fist was thrown to the side of the dragon.

*Rumble!*

Next, large amounts of light and warmth were produced from the stone, like a sun that had fallen to the earth.

Radiance dispelled the darkness and descended upon this piece of land.

“Roar… roar…”

Under the intense glare of the sunlight, the adventurers present closed their eyes, tears on the verge of falling.

The Goat-Horned Earth Dragon that was used to a life in darkness roared instantly became enraged.

“Quick! It has now been temporarily blinded. Move!”

Baelin was clear that when these beings used to the darkness suddenly came into contact with light, they would definitely be blinded for a period of time due to not being used to it, and this was the best time for them to make their move!

Besides, the function of the sun stone was to fill the area with light, which made it more helpful in allowing the group of them to exhibit their abilities!

“To create this chance, Potter Town gave out a year’s supply of sun stones. What a waste!”

There were definitely many adventurers who thought the same way as Baelin, but this thought passed through their minds for a brief moment. Then they roared, brandishing the weapons in their hands and charged towards the huge monster in the middle of the site.

Under the illumination of the light, even the brown scales and veins on the muscles on the back of the Goat-Horned Earth Dragon could be seen very clearly.

*Xiu Xiu!*

The first to attack was a group of mercenaries with bows and arrows. They were obviously a team, wearing a set of uniform with ice-cold glints of their iron arrows being emitted.

The sharp arrowheads brought with them tremendous force as they pierced into the back of the Goat-Horned Earth Dragon.

*Ka-cha!* The Earth Dragon constantly snarled, and most of the arrows were flung away. However, there were a few that obstinately stayed on its back.

“Kill!” By this point, the adventurers had also charged to the front.

“Roar, roar!” The dragon thundered, suddenly turning back and flicking its tail!

The tail was like a large mace sweeping across the area, and the mercenaries that charged up flew away. A few were struck by the tail, and their blood dyed the sky.

“What an astute sense of hearing and smell!” Baelin exclaimed in admiration. The eyes of the Goat-Horned Earth Dragon were very small and had almost completely degenerated. With the sudden piercing bright light, it couldn’t see anything at all, but all beings that lived in the darkness naturally had their unique ways of distinguishing other objects.

Baelin stepped away, dodging the sweeping motion of the steel tail and raised his sword, a thin ring of light produced around him.

“Cross Blade!” In a moment, he used Leylin’s secret killing technique for cross blades.

The immense light formed a cross, slashing towards the Goat-Horned Earth Dragon that was still snarling.

The fierce, immense air pressure attracted the attention of the Earth Dragon and it lifted its right forelimb, mercilessly clawing in Baelin’s direction!

Large black claws clashed with the cross-shaped light, and the sound of glass shattering could be heard in the air.

“Roar…” The Earth Dragon kept snarling, its large black claws disintegrating the move and smacking towards Baelin.

“How powerful and quick!” Baelin exclaimed in admiration and used his sword as a shield in front of him.

*Dang!*

The large claw and steel sword clashed, producing a loud sound and shock wave. Baeflin felt an immense force transmitting from the sword and the sword was almost sent flying.

“Ah!” He gritted his teeth, holding onto the sword for dear life, using the force from the dragon to fall back.

*Roar!* The Earth Dragon was clearly enraged, once again brandishing its steel tail and chopping two mercenaries that had charged forward in two!

The two mercenaries howled, their halved bodies still squirming on the ground, intestines spilling out onto the ground. This gory scene immediately intimidated the rest of the mercenaries and adventurers and they retreated, not daring to take a step forward.

“What should we do? James, that Goat Honed Earth Dragon is almost about to return to its cave. We need to think of a way!”

“Soon! Soon!” James now had his eyes fixed on the dragon, constantly chanting.

“Roar!”

At that moment, the body of the Earth Dragon that had almost halfway returned suddenly changed! Bubbles of pus began to swell and burst, revealing yellow pus.

“Woo woo…” The Earth Dragon’s voice became low and it began to wail in anguish.

“This is a high-energy bacteria solution especially brewed for the Goat-Horned Earth Dragon. It can lower the defence of its epidermis!”

James briefly explained to Jenny, quickly chanting some incantations.

A powerful undulation from energy particles was constantly produced from the old man, who had only seemed to be a butler.

“This is… a mysterious expert! So, Lord James is actually an esteemed Magus!” The adventurers around exclaimed.

In the subterranean world, Magi were widely known and worshipped.

“Mostar Corrosive Ball!” As the incantations ended, James waved his right arm.

A large blue ball arced in the sky, precisely landing on the back of the dragon.

The blue ball spread out, turning into large amounts of sky blue liquid that mixed with the yellow pus. Immediately, it produced a large amount of heat and began to corrode downwards.

“Roar!” The Earth Dragon’s pitiful shrieks increased in pitch, and large amounts of steamed flesh fell from its back.

“What are you waiting for? This is the moment where its defence is at its weakest!”

James placed his hands behind him, looking like an expert. The adventurers seemed to have just awoken from a dream and charged forward once again.

This time, with James’ work, the Earth Dragon’s speed dropped, and the skin and scaly defensive layer had mostly disappeared. The mercenaries could easily slash and create a gaping wound with their weapons.

In just a moment, the entire situation was reversed.

Chapter 302: Breakthrough

“Wooh wooh…”

Under this attack, the Goat-Horned Earth Dragon kept howling and suddenly turned. Uncaring of the serious injuries it had sustained and the people who were pursuing and attacking it, it crawled back into the cave!

“This is bad! It wants to escape!”

Jenny cried out in alarm, and she immediately brought out the bow and arrows which seemed hand-made, that had been on her back.

She took out a green arrow from her quiver, resting it on the bow.

*Weng! Weng! Weng!*

One after another, the various rings she had on her hand began to light up.

“Precise Aim!” “Keen Edge!” “Gale Technique!”

All sorts of buffs were applied to Jenny.

“Miss- Miss Jenny is also a Magus?!” Baelin, who was not far away, gaped, thinking he might be in a dream.

*Xiu!*

Jenny released the arrow in her hand, and a streak of green flew from the bow.

*Pu!* The green arrow of light struck an eye of the Goat-Horned Earth Dragon, resulting in a large amount of red, greenish blood spurting out.

“Roar!!!” The Earth Dragon turned back sharply, charging in Jenny’s direction.

“Good! This is it!” Jenny’s expression revealed her excitement.

“No, leave!” On the other hand, James at the side had paled.

“Roar!” The Goat-Horned Earth Dragon thundered, spitting out a black ball of light.

The large ball of light exploded mid-air, black droplets of flames sprinkling everywhere.

“Ah!” “My eyes!”

The black droplets landed on the mercenaries’ bodies, instantly causing serious injuries. The many adventurers began to howl, and the circle which surrounded the dragon immediately had a hole.

*Hah! Hah!* The Goat-Horned Earth Dragon stimulated its energy to every part of its body and it swelled, and its skin turned red.

Its speed rapidly increased and it charged in front of Jenny.

“Protect the miss!” The one surviving guard brandished his sword with his left arm and dashed forward.

*Ka-cha!* The Earth Dragon opened its mouth full of sharp fangs and biting down, it had the knight in its mouth, constantly chewing. Blood and flesh fell from the gaps between its teeth.

“Ah…” Jenny was so shocked that her legs buckled, and she fell to the ground.

She was but a level 1 acolyte. That attack with the bow was only effective with the bonus from all the rings she had. After that attack, the pitiful amount of spiritual force she had was almost exhausted, and it was not possible to pull off another attack.

Jenny was now a fragile, helpless girl of the nobility as she was paralyzed on the ground, awaiting her unknown future.

“Awoo!” The Goat-Horned Earth Dragon did not have any thoughts of taking pity on her, opening its mouth wide. With its sharp teeth filled with flesh and blood, it snapped its jaws and made to bite her.

“Am I going to die? I’m sorry, Father…” Jenny’s mouth was half open, a teardrop rolling from her right eye.

*Dang!*

The acute pain she had been expecting did not appear, and Jenny opened her eyes, stunned. All she saw was a strong figure in front of her.

“Hey! In Knight stories, there will always be a knight appearing whenever the princess is in trouble, right?”

Baelin laughed, ruthlessly chopping forward with the sword in his hands!

The large steel sword hacked at the surface of the dragon’s head, producing some sparks. Baelin bellowed, life essence bursting out. On the surface of the armour, there seemed to be a protective layer formed of light.

*Roar!*

The Earth Dragon retreated a few steps, snarling at Baelin.

“Oh my! This is the real life version of a brave knight fighting against the evil dragon!” Baelin shot a glance at Jenny behind him, and then took a look at how much life essence he had left, a helpless smile about his lips.

*Whoosh!*

A black figure constantly attacked the Earth Dragon, and everyone else could only see the dust flying at the centre of the site, as well as the constant howls from the dragon.

Under the immense pressure from the Earth Dragon, Baelin felt all that Lord Leylin had forced him to learn suddenly bursting out as he became more proficient at some techniques.

At this moment, he suddenly felt empty, as if he had lost all of the power he just had.

“The burst of power from the secret technique is used up, and my life essence has been exhausted!”

Baelin’s heart sank, and a black shadow like a steel mace pierced through the armour of light, mercilessly slamming on his chest.

*Ka-cha!* The steel armour caved in, and Baelin flew backwards, a large amount of blood spilling from the corner of his mouth.

“No!”

At the moment he was about to die, he seemed to see the gigantic shadow of the Earth Dragon, as well as heard a sorrowful wail.

“What a short life! However, I have no more regrets!”

With a gentle smile, he froze into his image of Jenny crying hard while on the ground into his memory.

“How can my student die in such a pointless way?”

Just as Baelin was about to fall unconscious, time seemed to stop, and his surroundings turned black and white. His body seemed to be stuck in mid-air.

“It’s Lord Leylin’s voice! He’s finally acknowledged me as his student!” Baelin was overjoyed, his thoughts on this while he was on the verge of death.

Next, he felt the steel sword on his right hand constantly becoming warmer till it became burning hot as if he was holding a soldering iron.

*Weng Weng!* The sword constantly shook, and a crimson rune appeared on its own accord on the blade.

“Ahh!”

Baelin felt a stream of heat being transmitted from the steel sword, rushing to his lower abdomen where his life essence was congregated.

*Bang!* Like the sound of a bottle exploding, the bottleneck to becoming a Grand Knight — the issue which had been bothering Baelin for a long period of time — was crossed!

Life energy that was at least ten times more powerful than before congregated from the life essence at his lower abdomen, and flowed through Baelin’s limbs.

“Shaaa!”

Baelin held his sword and slashed forward. On the surface of the steel sword, red rays from the rune suddenly brightened, and the sheen from a sword streaked through the sky, appearing in front of the Earth Dragon.

Under the black and white rays that had frozen time, the Earth Dragon was motionless, allowing Baelin to aim a slash at its neck.

*Whoosh!*

A cold wind blew, and the black and white faded, returning to the usual colourful world.

*Ka-cha!*

A fine red line appeared at the Earth Dragon’s neck.

This line began to spread till it covered the entire neck, and then reddish-green blood constantly flowed out, the gigantic head of the beast fell to the ground.

*Rumble!* After losing its head, the huge body of the Goat-Horned Earth Dragon crashed to the ground, like a little earthquake, causing a large amount of dust to fly.

“What happened to him?” Jenny felt a little dizzy.

“He broke through! He broke through the bottleneck of a Grand Knight!” James mumbled to himself, and then helped Jenny up.

“Haha, I knew I was a genius! How could I just die like this!”

Baelin, who had escaped death, patted his chest and began to laugh.

Seeing him in this state, Jenny felt there was a fire in her chest, almost causing it to explode.

“You idiot!” Jenny threw a white handkerchief at Baelin’s face. Leaving him alone, she entered the cave with James.

“Why is she being like this?” Baelin held the handkerchief in a daze, bewildered.

The surviving mercenaries and adventurers silently cleaned the area.

They had lost a lot of people, and many of them were their friends or even family!

It was very quiet on the battlefield, and not one animal came to disturb the silence.

The sun’s rays were extremely annoying for the beings that were used to the darkness. Potter Town of Twilight Zone had made use of this aversion and used the sun stones to disperse the creatures of darkness, and could thus develop.

James had considered this at the beginning when he threw out the sun stones.

Ten minutes later, Jenny and James came out with excitement.

“Is this the Dragon-Blooded Flower Bud?”

Baelin noticed the plant that seemed like a flower in Jenny’s hands.

This red flower was the size of a bowl, and there were webs that seemed like blood vessels and veins on the petals. It looked very bizarre.

Jenny carefully held the flower bud, as if she were holding some treasure that was as valuable as a city.

“Yes! With this, my father can be saved…” Jenny finally relaxed.

Ever since her father had been poisoned, immense pressure had been put on the shoulders of this young girl. Now, she could finally heave a sigh of relief.

“Thank you!” Jenny was so emotional that she hugged Baelin, leaving him stunned at the spot.

“And all of you!” Jenny turned back to the adventurers and mercenaries, “Your loyalty and devotion to your role has earned you your rewards! I will give out twice the amount promised, and five times that for those who have died!”

“Thank you so much, my lady!” “A kind and generous person!” “May the lord of darkness protect you!”

As expected, Jenny’s declaration made everyone present cheer.

They packed up and began their journey back.

On the way back, Baelin kept swinging the steel sword in his hand, wanting to find any strange marks on it. However, after that one burst, this sword had used up all its energy, and no matter how much Baelin prodded it, it did not exhibit any strange features.

“What a fool! However, only a person with a one-track mind like him is suitable for my cross blade breathing technique!” Baelin’s actions were all seen by Leylin, who was in Potter Town, through a transparent crystal, and he shook his head.

Beside him, a test tube full of reddish green liquid was thrown aside like rubbish.

“There’s not even a sliver of a powerful bloodline in there! To think it even had the word “dragon” in its name!” Leylin sighed.

Chapter 303: Farewell

Not all myths and folklore were true.

On the contrary, many myths have been altered, some even to the extent of the subjective thoughts of the storyteller, hence they were unusually laid with errors.

Only Leylin’s A.I. Chip could analyse and sieve out the most accurate version of the myth from the myriad of mythological information available.

As for now, after the blood analysis of the Goat-Horned Earth Dragon, Leylin discovered that there wasn’t a single trace of an ancient bloodline in it’s blood!

Evidently, the myth of the Goat-Horned Earth Dragon being borne from a giant dragon and another demonic creature was false!

However, Leylin did not harbour much hope from the start. Even if the Goat-Horned Earth Dragon were to contain traces of an ancient bloodline, this strength that did not even reach the stage of an official Magus did not fit his requirements at all.

Back in Nightless City, he was clear that even if he could obtain and purify the blood from creatures that contained an ancient bloodline, the creature had to be of a certain level to be of use.

As for this standard, after the analysis from the A.I. Chip, the conclusion was that these creatures needed to have the strength to at least rival a rank 3 Magus!

In other words, even if the Goat Horned Earth Dragon were to contain traces of an ancient bloodline, Leylin had to find one that was the equivalent of a rank 3 Magus. Then, with the help of the A.I. Chip, the purification of the ancient bloodline would be achieved.

”Aaah, a rank 3 Magus!”

Leylin smiled wryly; he had only recently advanced to a rank 2 Magus and the spiritual force he received from his meditation technique were extremely little. Most of the increase in spiritual force came from the Giant Kemoyin Serpent’s bloodline.

Although there was nothing wrong with a Warlock relying on the strength of his bloodline, Leylin did not want his foundations to be unstable.

Furthermore, he had advanced to a rank 2 Magus by the age of 40. This speed was extremely astounding on the south coast. Even back in the ancient times, it was considered remarkable.

Hence, spending more time for a better foundation was something that he had to do.

As he was now, it was unlikely that he could win against a creature with strength equivalent to a rank 3 Magus, even with the help of his ancient bloodline. Those kinds of creatures were terrifying existences, to the point where most rank 3 Magi would not dare to face off against such creatures directly.

After a brief sigh, Leylin let go of the notion of collecting ancient bloodlines.

After all, the Giant Kemoyin Serpent’s bloodline was enough for him right now.

Moreover, even if he lucked upon another ancient creature’s bloodline, it would only be a very valuable research material for him. Once a Warlock has chosen an ancient bloodline, there isn’t any way to change it.

”However, things do not seem to stop here!”

Leylin, who was observing Jenny through the crystal ball, frowned as if discovering something.

Under the control of his spiritual force, the images in the crystal ball began to change from Jenny’s party to the top of a different hill.

At this moment, under the shroud of darkness, there were two black figures conversing on the hill.

”Can’t you do your job properly? You actually let them get the Dragon-Blooded Flower Bud?”

The man who spoke had a gruffy voice and his silhouette was extremely fuzzy. He even wore a mask to hide his features.

However, Leylin’s gaze pierced through the darkness and the mask to see the countenance of the man.

The face belonged to a sinister-looking old geezer that had a black skull branded on his forehead. It seemed to have been branded using a hot piece of metal. There were also writhing burn marks that filled the surroundings of the skull.

Moreover, there was an energy wave that was not weaker than James. He was a level 3 acolyte and apart from having no magic artifact, his strength was not below that of James.

”I… I did not want that to happen to…” The youth beside him shuddered, and even he started to stutter.

”The earlier Explosive Flaming Wolves were already extremely risky, if we were to strike again, they would most likely discover us. Moreover, the Goat-Horned Earth Dragon was extremely difficult to lure… Your subordinate, I, thought that the Goat-Horned Earth Dragon alone would be enough to stop those people…”

”Although the Goat-Horned Earth Dragon was still in its adolescent stages, the might it had far exceeded that of a level 3 acolyte, only an official Magus would be able to take it down!”

The old geezer acknowledged the young man’s deduction.

”So then, how did they manage to kill the Goat-Horned Earth Dragon?” The youth was puzzled. “Even if a Knight manages to breakthrough, he would at the very most be a Grand Knight, which wouldn’t be enough to change the outcome…”

”I can sense that the air was filled with extremely strong energy waves… It’s definitely a powerful existence aiding them secretly…”

The old geezer looked miserable. The strength revealed was only the corner of an iceberg, yet it could make his hairs stand on end. It felt as if as he had returned back to his life as a helpless child. He had this premonition that if this force wanted to kill him, it would not have any trouble at all. As for the ability to be able to do that, the person behind this force must have reached the might of a rank 1 Magus!

”What should we do? Should we continue?”

The frightened youth went into shock. He knew the identity of this old geezer, but this was an existence that could make even the old man tremble in fear. That existence ought to be an even more powerful magician.

Once he thought of this, cold sweat began to drip down his body. He had an urge to turn around and run, never to participate in such a mission again.

However, very soon he mocked himself for this thought. Being a covert member of this large organisation, how can one leave that easily? Just from the information he held at his fingertips, he was already familiar with the nature of the big boss. If one wants to run or retire, the only way to do it was to lie in a grave.

”No matter what, we cannot allow that girl to bring the Dragon-Blooded Flower Bud back to the eastern region! This is the command of the big boss!” The old geezer was extremely stern.

”Let’s go…”

His cloak swiveled as he vanished into the darkness with the young man.

”Interesting! How very interesting!”

Leylin smiled wryly after seeing this scene. He had no interest in the petty struggles of these mortals but felt rather intrigued by the one pulling the strings from behind.

Power determines everything! In this subterranean world, for the Argus Family to be this powerful, there must definitely be an official Magus supporting it from behind the scenes!

Perhaps, this is an opportunity to interact with the Magi in the subterranean world!

Leylin rubbed his chin and entered into a deep thought.

……

”Teacher! Teacher! I have returned!” Baelin dashed in quickly into the little shop with forge and anvils, smiling triumphantly. “I have also advanced into a Grand Knight and plucked the Dragon-Blooded Flower Bud for Jenny!”

As for Leylin, he sat at the counter concentrating on brewing his tea filled with yellow fellow petals and green buds, all this while not lifting his head.

”After cultivating in the breathing technique I’ve taught you, you managed to advance into a Grand Knight only now? What a big idiot you are! Also, when have I ever accepted you as my disciple?”

Baelin’s smile turned stiff.

”So… So when I slain that Goat-Horned Earth Dragon I heard your voice!”

The youth began to mutter to himself, “Back then you have admitted that I was your student, and even helped me to defeat…Argh!”

*Pak!* Leylin used a vine to lash at Baelin’s head.

”This is your imagination, kiddo! Want to be my student? Cultivate for another ten thousand years first!”

Under the relentless verbal abuse, Baelin’s head drooped.

He was extremely embarrassed now and had the urge to find a hole and hide in it. After slaying the Goat-Horned Earth Dragon, he knew that he had hallucinated, but he still wished to make use of this opportunity to make Leylin his master. These were also incited by Jenny and James.

Evidently, this shameless plan of his failed!

Leylin would never acknowledge him as his student, which left Baelin standing there, not knowing what to say.

”Haha… Mister Leylin is really a strict teacher!”

At this moment, Jenny walked in and reduced the awkwardness for Baelin.

”I am just educating this silly little chap!” Leylin smiled humbly.

As for Baelin, he heaved a sigh of relief and stood at the side.

”Actually… For Baelin to be able to advance to a Grand Knight at his age, he is considered to have a remarkable talent! Even in the aspects of the more mysterious arts, I believe he will have exceptionally great talent…” Jenny deliberated, “Mister, why don’t you give him a chance?”

Although Baelin did not quite understand what Jenny meant, he still looked gratefully at Jenny.

“I am rather strict when it comes to the selection of my students!” Leylin shook his head and expressed his rejection on the matter.

Hearing that, Baelin lowered his head again.

As for Jenny, she could only give a comforting gaze to him.

“Your purpose of coming here wouldn’t only be to speak about this, would it?” Leylin sipped on his tea, with no intention to brewing a cup for Jenny as he asked.

”Actually, picking the Dragon-Blooded Flower Bud was only made possible with the help of Mister Leylin. Also, regarding the Explosive Flaming Wolves, I have come here to express my heartfelt appreciation!”

Jenny curtsied and smiled wryly, “With your capabilities, Mister, I don’t think I can offer you anything that you’ll need. However, in the future should you require the assistance of the Argus Family, please send along your requests! I, Jenny Argus, solemnly swear by the name of the Sun Vines, that I will not refuse your bidding!”

Jenny’s face turned solemn as she made an oath.

”Also, I have come here to bid farewell to you, Mister!”

“Wait!” Before Leylin could speak, Baelin opened his mouth in shocked, “Jenny, you… you’re leaving?”

Chapter 304: The Resolution of a Youth

“Yes!” Jenny nodded.

“The Dragon-Blooded Flower Bud will perish soon, and my father will not be able to hold on much longer with his illness!”

”Alright then! I wish you a safe journey back to your home!” Baelin smiled with reluctance.

”Thank you!” Jenny did not speak further.

”Alright! The eastern capital is where the Argus Family is, I will pay a visit in the future!” Leylin sipped on his tea and stretched his right hand, gesturing as a gentleman.

”If Mister can come, then it would be the happiest thing that happened to Jenny!”

Jenny smiled, “How about returning home with me? My father would definitely be excited to be your acquaintance!” She looked at Baelin, “Of course, big brother Baelin, can come too!”

Hearing this, Baelin grew nervous as he looked eagerly at Leylin.

”My apologies! I have no desires to travel right now!” Leylin declined without hesitation, once again making Baelin look down in dismay.

Hearing this, Jenny turned silent for a moment, before she curtsied and took her leave.

”What’s wrong? If you have nothing else to do then get to work!”

Leylin roared at Baelin.

”Yes, Boss!” Baelin replied dispiritedly.

”Hehe… Youths!”

Leylin grinned silently.

This eastern region was one he would definitely pay a visit to. It was not only the centre of the mortals’ government, but it was also a gathering place for the Magi. It was rumoured to have large scale magic bazaars too.

However, going there of his own choice and being invited were two entirely different concepts.

With Leylin’s strength right now, he could do whatever he liked, but it would often attract some unwanted problems.

Furthermore, his injuries had not healed completely. Before finding enough methods to curb the emotional instabilities of Warlocks, he did not wish to have a high profile.

Hence, entering the area inhabited by Magi in the eastern region through the Argus family, was a wise choice.

Through the earlier spying done, Leylin had guessed that Jenny’s road back home would not be smooth sailing. Evidently, Jenny had the same feeling, hence she invited Leylin to travel back with her.

Leylin understood that the most precious things were often unobtainable. Hence he would let Jenny encounter setbacks and beg him before he would help her, creating a false impression in front of her.

Moreover, there was an even better reason now!

Leylin glanced at Baelin who was nurturing his sorrow at the side before his lips curled up at one corner of his mouth.

A Magus who was fed up with the dangerous Magus world and was starting to live in seclusion under his apprentice’s involvement with a girl, would once again enter the fray of the Magus world. Yes, it seemed like a pretty good excuse to return!

As for the age? Magi never bothered with appearances nor age.

As for Leylin, he could also use his bloodline to change his aura, eyes, body shape and appearances in minute proportions, allowing him to look much older than he was. This was enough to fool many Magi.

……

Jenny journeyed with haste. Once she left the town after bidding Leylin farewell, she continued her journey hurriedly.

”Why? You wish to go after her?”

Looking at the horse carriage that was gradually turning smaller in the horizon, Baelin stood rooted to the spot. Leylin could not help himself but mock him.

Provoking this youth daily was part of Leylin’s amusement outside of his cultivation and research.

“I’ll definitely go to the eastern capital. Definitely, but not now!” A flame of hope seemed to start burning in Baelin’s eyes.

“Boss! No, my lord! Please train me more rigorously! I want to be a man whose name will shake the eastern region, and then look for Jenny there with these achievements.”

Baelin half-knelt on the ground, a great ambition, and thirst for power burning in his eyes!

“Haha, that’s good! I like that look in your eyes! Don’t worry, I’ll give you an even more ‘rigorous’ training… “ Leylin seemed to be harbouring some evil designs.

Originally, in such situations, perhaps a young man from a small town would train himself for many years and would then enter the eastern capital, and then take the Marquis’ daughter as his wife. It would be just another common occurrence.

But it was unfortunate — or perhaps one could call it inspiring — that, contrary to Baelin’s own expectations, he would soon be reunited with Jenny!

The night that Jenny left, Baelin, who had been tortured by Leylin for an entire day and was about to crawl into his pitiful bed and get some sleep, was woken up by the sound of a fierce banging on the door.

“Baelin! Lord Leylin!” This was a woman’s voice, filled with fear, and it also belonged to the voice of someone Baelin would never forget.

“It’s Jenny!” He quickly got up at lightning speed and opened the entrance to the shop.

Jenny was standing covered in blood, with James lying on the ground. However, there was a large hole on this poor old man’s chest, with some arrows on his back. By the looks of it, he would not be able to live past tonight.

“Baelin, get Lord Leylin! Save…”

Upon seeing Baelin, Jenny relaxed and immediately collapsed in a dead faint.

“Hey! Who’s going to tell me what’s going on here?” Seeing the soft female body in his arms, Baelin looked ready to break down.

Wait! Wasn’t this how it usually went in tales involving Knights?

Where was the counterattack? Where was the wait? Where was the whole thing about meeting in the capital?

Baelin hugged Jenny tightly, his mind unable to work.

However, at this point, a warm blood gushed out and spilled into Baelin’s hands, causing him to come back to himself.

“Lord Leylin, we have a problem!” The fearful, hoarse voice of the young man seemed to resound throughout Potter Town.

Blood and flames! The glinting from a knife, and then the dazzling rays from rank 0 spells!

This was the last thing James had seen.

Though he had long since known of the malicious ways of Jenny’s two uncles, he had never imagined that they would be so gutsy as to ambush them right in the open, that too on the main street!

Under the sudden attack, Jenny’s temporary guards could not even withstand a single blow.

If not for them relying on the Marquis’ magic artifact that the Madam had secretly left behind for their use before they left, he and Jenny would not even be able to flee!

After that, they returned to Potter Town, escaping and fighting back on the way.

James had simply fainted after telling Jenny to obtain Sir Leylin’s help.

“This is…”

James opened his eyes, bewildered as he stared at the yellow light and the ceiling that he did not recognise.

“Sir James, you’re awake!” Baelin, who was at the side, quickly came over and tipped a bowl of green liquid into his mouth.

“Ugh…” Within the green liquid, there were numerous roots and suspicious things that looked like bugs floating on top. It looked extremely disgusting and the smell that seemed to come from a sewer assaulted his nostrils, almost causing this old man to black out.

“What’s this?” After being forced to drink two large gulps, James finally got the chance to push away the large bowl in Baelin’s hands.

He swore that even if he were to die, he would not want to smell this thing again.

“It’s some herbal medicine that Lord Leylin instructed me to boil. It’s very helpful towards your injuries!” Baelin pushed the bowl towards him, looking helpful.

“No, thank you so much for your help! Does this mean that I’m in Mister Leylin’s shop? How is the young miss?”

James immediately asked.

“Don’t worry, Jenny is very safe!” Baelin was a little confused, “Do you think you could tell me what happened?”

He was extremely curious towards the events that had befallen on them, but he felt sorry if he were to call Jenny awake, which was why he was still rather confused about the situation.

“What else could have happened?” James forced out a smile, and then gave a short summary of how Jenny’s two uncles had arranged an ambush.

“That’s vile!” Baelin felt aggrieved as he mumbled and then pounded on the table.

*Pak!* The sudden force that exploded caused the wooden table to be fall apart.

This loud sound also attracted the attention of another person.

”Sir Leylin, it’s all thanks to you this time!” After seeing Leylin enter, James struggled to get up and bowed.

James himself knew how severely injured he was. After all, it was caused by another level 3 acolyte.

However, being able to treat such injuries, Leylin’s identity had even become more mysterious.

”James, you are still sustaining injuries, so no need for such formalities!” Leylin smiled gently before tapping on Baelin’s head.

”Let us step out and let James have some more rest…”

”Oh! Okay!” Baelin who seemed to be dreaming got up and as he stepped through the door, he comforted James. “Sir James, you should recuperate here quietly, we’re safe here…”

”Of course! I have no doubts about that!”

James replied. How can a place that had an official Magus not be safe? If so, are there any safer places out there?

Apart from that, if Leylin wished to help them, Jenny and those two uncles of hers caught in the internal strife were only as significant as specks of dust.

”But what should we do to get Mister Leylin to help us?” James pondered.

Through some discreet inquiries made during this period, he had a little more understanding of Leylin.

Amongst the people that James knew, this Lord Leylin was aloof, proud and disliked troublesome matters, hence he seldom appeared in public places. The mortal items were just like floating clouds to him.

Apart from training Baelin each day, there was no other recreation that Leylin would partake in.

”Baelin! Right, Baelin!” James clapped his hands, an indescribable light in his eyes…

……

”Speak! What’s the matter?”

Leylin looked at Baelin, who seemed to be struggling within during the journey to the training grounds, and smiled.

“My lord, I’d like to take your leave for a period of time and escort Miss Jenny to the eastern capital!”

Chapter 305: Hitchhike

The young man’s voice was resolute; his fists were clenched and his face flushed. Faint rays of light radiated from his body.

“So stubborn. Are you sure you won’t go back on your words? The moment you go to the eastern capital, I probably will no longer teach you!”

Leylin had a toying expression on his face.

“A Grand Knight isn’t anything much. There are probably a whole dozen in Jenny’s family. Let’s not even talk about the dangers on the way that will probably cause you to lose your life. What are you planning to do after you send her back? Be a captain of some guards at the Argus Family? Or perhaps, even worse, become a mercenary?”

“Have you thought of all these?”

Leylin asked.

Baelin had turned pale, but his voice was steady, “I know all that! But… but if I don’t send Jenny home safely, my heart will never be at ease. I know this for sure…”

“Fine! You can leave, but you are to never return.”

Leylin looked at this toy of his that was full of righteousness and gave an ultimatum before returning to his room.

*Boom!*

The door slammed shut, leaving Baelin standing outside, silently.

“Thank you, Baelin!” At this moment, a small, cold hand covered Baelin’s calloused palm.

“Jen..Jenny, you…” Baelin began to stutter as he spoke.

A finger that was equally icy — and was rather fragrant — was placed upon Baelin’s lips.

“You don’t need to say anything else!”

Jenny mumbled, and then rested her head on Baelin’s shoulders.

“When I was younger, what I liked the most was leaning against my Father’s body and resting my head on his chest. Now, can you lend me your shoulders to rest on for a while?”

“Of-of course. It’ll be my pleasure to…” Baelin stood there in a daze, his nostrils breathing in the fragrance from Jenny’s hair. He did not dare move even a muscle.

……

A night passed and Baelin looked at his crush who had left his side, and also the trace of dampness on his shoulders, before smiling wryly.

“Let us set off!”

On a mini horse-carriage carrying goods, Baelin wore rugged cloth and dressed as a horse keeper. As for Jenny and James, they were hiding inside a compartment of the horse carriage.

On the four sides of the horse carriage, large torches were lit, dispelling the darkness in the surroundings.

“Don’t worry! They won’t be able to discover you!” Baelin tried his best to console them.

As for Jenny and James, they could only look at each other and smile wryly.

As the Lord Marquis’s condition was worsening, Jenny and James only had a short respite to nurture their wounds before continuing on the journey.

Their employed adventurers and mercenaries were slain in the earlier journey, which made it obvious to everyone that someone was obstructing Jenny and her party. There were no more fools stepping forward to be their valiant protectors.

Furthermore, even the Baron who had lost a Knight and most of his elite troops felt a deep remorse. The way he looked at Jenny now was as if he was seeing the god of plague.

To him, the sooner Jenna — who was like a magnet for bad fortune — left, the better it was. In any case, it would be best that none of the incidents were to happen in the area he oversaw so that he can be acquitted of the blame.

This attitude was even more apparent after he received an anonymous letter from the eastern capital. It was to the extent of rejecting to grant Jenny an audience with him.

In this feudalistic area, it was like many small kingdoms which were independent. After seeing the Baron act this way, all of the Potter Town’s citizens did not offer any help to Jenny thereafter.

For this small horse carriage, Baelin had to fork out three times of the market price to purchase it.

The seller even stressed that he would only sell to Baelin; he did not want to even have a buyer-seller relation with Jenny!

They simply had no confidence that Baelin could complete this simple purchase!

However, what else could they have done to ensure their safety?

Looking at the shops selling torches and the weaponry shop which were closed, Jenny and James were in dismay. As for Baelin, he looked even sadder.

However, he clenched his teeth and looked at Jenny sitting behind him, before cracking his whip.

*Pa!*

The horse carriage began to move, taking the three passengers out of this town.

“Wait a minute, can I hitch a ride?”

Just when the town behind Baelin gradually grew smaller and when his indecisiveness was at its peak, he heard a voice that sounded heavenly to the ears.

“Bo…Boss!”

Baelin rubbed his eyes and looked at Leylin wearing black robes with a small knapsack. Immediately, his eyes were filled with guilt and excitement, relief and many other expressions.

“Lord Leylin! We’re extremely grateful for you coming with us!”

At this moment, Jenny and James popped out from the narrow compartment of the horse carriage and smiled, as if relieved of a heavy burden.

From the looks of it, if this mysterious Mister Leylin was to join them, what more did they need to worry about?

It was evident that Jenny and James had joy on their faces no matter how hard they tried to conceal it.

Through Baelin, they have successfully made Leylin, this mysterious person who was most likely a Magus, come with them. Even after returning to the eastern region, involving Leylin in their scheme was extremely beneficial!

As for these petty schemes, Leylin had not even needed to guess before he knew their train of thoughts. However, he did not express it explicitly and allowed Baelin to escort him up the carriage.

With this powerful expert Leylin holding the fort, the other three felt much better in an instant.

They threw away all that was used to conceal themselves, and also changed the interior of the horse carriage to make it seem like it was carrying passengers instead of goods. They no longer had to squeeze into that small space throughout the journey.

* Da Da Da!*

The wheels of the horse carriage spun as the two old horses galloped with all their might to travel forth.

“Master Leylin, why are you willing to give up on your shop and come with me to the eastern capital?”

Baelin glanced at Leylin who was resting at a side, restraining himself as much as he could before he asked.

“Of course it’s for you, you fool! How can I be reassured if I let you go alone?”

Leylin opened his eyes and spoke indifferently.

“Bo-boss, I’m so touched…” Baelin choked with emotion, sparkling tears gathering in his eyes.

“If you thought I’d say something like that, you’re gravely mistaken!” Immediately after, Leylin’s next words caused Baelin to be stunned.

“Business at Blazing Hammers is not doing well. I’ve been wanting to go to the eastern capital and find a suitable place to do some business or open a branch. Since you’re going, I’ll go too since you’re already going there.”

“No, you must be lying to me! You must be here because you’re worried about me, right Boss?”

Baelin looked ready to breakdown, while Jenny and James looked like they wanted to laugh, but did not dare do so.

“Just think whatever you want to think.”

Leylin stared, speechless, at this fellow who was a bit too egotistical.

He spoke indifferently and snuggled into his clothes, seemingly entering a deep sleep.

However, in his heart, he thought, “A.I. Chip, show me my current stats!”

[Beep! Leylin Farlier. Rank 2 Warlock, Bloodline: Giant Kemoyin Serpent. Strength: 21.1, Agility: 14.4, Vitality: 27.9, Spiritual force: 77 (104.3), Magic power: 77 (Magic power is in synchronisation with spiritual force) Status: Sea of consciousness is fragmented. Part of spiritual force is solidified.]

Over these two years, Leylin constantly used potions to heal his injuries. At this point, the injuries on his body had mostly recovered.

However, healing the damage done to his sea of consciousness and his spiritual force was a very slow process, causing Leylin to start feeling impatient.

Hence, after his emotions due to his Warlock bloodline had erupted, he had decided to go to the eastern capital and find a way to increase the rate of this process.

After expelling the mark from the rank 3 Magus Alric, he could now release part of his spiritual force and return his strength to that of a peak rank 1 Magus.

Whether in the south coast or in Twilight Zone, Magi with this power could go on a rampage. As long as one did not meet with a Magus above rank 2, they were basically tyrants!

Though the Twilight Zone had a lot of high-grade meditation techniques, there were still some differences in the overall strength as compared to the south coast.

Leylin, who also trained in a high-grade meditation technique, was very clear about these differences.

The high-grade meditation techniques passed down from ancient Magi could help a Magus get stronger at every rank with all sorts of amazing powers along the way, but there were still a few obvious disadvantages!

After training up to a certain point, regular mortal resources were of no use to them, and only bizarre or even items from another world would be able to help one progress in one’s meditation technique. If not, one would get stuck at some point.

In ancient times, Magi took over world after world and amassed vast amounts of resources. Also, the connection between Twilight Zone and the external world still existed, so this wasn’t a problem. However, the troublesome matter was: Not only had Twilight Zone lost its supply of resources from other worlds, it had even lost contact with the subterranean world itself!

Certain high-grade meditation techniques were extremely harsh when it came to the materials needed, and they also could not be substituted!

Hence, though the percentage of Magi here was a lot higher than in the south coast, there was probably the same number of rank 2 Magi on both sides.

As for rank 3 Magi, Leylin guessed they would be even lesser in number here than in the south coast!

After all, the higher the rank of a Magus, the rarer the materials they needed. This was even more so for Magi who used high-grade meditation techniques.

Without the help from these precious resources, Magi could only use time and make the occasional tiny amount of progress in these techniques. Such a speed would be enough to make a Magus have a nervous breakdown.

Most Magi used most of their lifetime and still could not break through the first level of their meditation technique, and were filled with unwillingness to accept their fate and were full of regrets at the time of their deaths!

Chapter 307: Earthquake

A Magus’ spiritual force and magic power were not infinite.

Even if they had extraordinary strength, they would still suffer from natural limitations.

Even if James was a level 3 acolyte, when faced with a troop of a hundred elite soldiers, he could only retreat.

The opponent’s side had too many people, and even if they lined up for him to kill them, his pitiful amount of spiritual force and magic power would not be sufficient to kill them all.

And if these soldiers were all replaced with cavalrymen?

Hopelessness had already started invading James’ heart. Being surrounded by that many cavalryman, the most he could do was to escape by himself with that magic artifact of his, leaving behind Jenny.

But, we have Lord Leylin with us now. There shouldn’t be any problem.

James glanced at Leylin and forced himself to calm down.

A situation where a squadron composed of magicians and civilian troops fighting each other has never before occurred in the history of Twilight Zone.

After all, no lord would stupidly provoke an official Magus.

Moreover, as far as Magi were concerned, they could use stealth and cast spells and could easily end the life of the perpetrator, so why should he unnecessarily waste his time?

If Lord Leylin really was an official Magus, then they need not be worried about this danger.

James inwardly comforted himself with these encouraging thoughts, and then he heard Baelin’s nervous, almost-filled-with-fear voice asking, “Who are you all?”

Although he had advanced and become a Grand Knight, but it was evident that his attitude had not adjusted to this fact. After looking at the expressionless and dense army, the small city resident’s heart welled up with fear.

With the horses neighing in the background, a small path opened up among the ranks of the calvary. An old fellow wearing a black Chinese suit, and with the mark of a human skull on his forehead, walked out.

“Rhodes, it really is you! You went as far as to dare station some troops here, are you not worried about being punished?” The expression on James’ face was an odd mixture of fury and regret.

“My beloved older brother, it is me!” Rhodes sneered.

“Older brother?” The stunned Baelin had only now discovered that if that sinister mark branded on Rhodes’ face was removed, he would closely resemble James.

“We are all employed by the Argus Family. Thus, there is no need for the soldiers to face off against each other with swords.” James tried one last compromise.

“Brother James! It’s because I want to prove that I’m better than you! Even in the aspect of choosing my leader! It will definitely be the next head of the Argus Family!”

Rhodes’ expression seemed to express a deep-rooted hatred.

“If it is about the matter that happened during our childhood years, I will apologize to you for that. I can even kneel before you. Nevertheless, Rhodes, one must not enter this vortex, as it can kill you…”

“Heehihihiheee… saying these things now, what’s the use?”

Rhodes gave an eerie smile and came over.

“All of you… Annoying!” Leylin, who was in front of the carriage, frowned, expressing his dissatisfaction.

Just as he had thought over and improved his plan, it was suddenly disrupted by this Rhodes and soon, an evil fire approached Rhodes.

“Is this Lord Leylin?”

Rhodes gave a deep bow. In front of this person who had a high certainty of being an official Magus, he did not dare to be disrespectful.

“This is an internal affair of the Argus Family. Moreover, our family’s Lord Siegfried is also a respected Lord Magus. He also wishes he can meet you…”

“No! You lie! Grandpa Siegfried has been deceived by you.”

Leylin still did not respond. Jenny jumped up, in a straight sudden manner like the tail of a kitten when it was frightened or angry.

“The official Magus of the Argus Family is known as Siegfried, eh? It seems he is the common ancestor for both these troops…”

Leylin felt some pity for this Magus.

His own descendants, for the sake of gaining power, were beating up each other. Maybe all of this gives him a headache. Or maybe he doesn’t care about such things.

After all, a Magus’ lifespan was very long. By the time a few generations have passed by, whatever affection and such emotions that said Magus had towards his family would have become very diluted

“I do not care who has Siegfried’s backing, but, I believe you are blocking my way. Now, step aside at once!”

Leylin frankly chided him. The one Rhodes mentioned was just a level 1 Magus, who certainly couldn’t induce fear in him, but he was extremely disgusted with Rhodes’ attitude.

“Hic……” This kind of scolding, clearly made Rhodes feel deflated and he stood there looking foolishly around him. His face also turned red.

His every effort and achievements were like jokes in the eyes of his family.

This is unfair! Again I hear such a tone. And again I am being subjected to such an expression. And in my childhood, my older brother was also the same. Why is he stronger than me in everything? Why do all the good things happen to him and not me?

Rhodes’s eyes turned redder.

Moreover, it isn’t clear whether that Leylin is an official Magus or not. There exists a probability that he is just someone that slut Jenny hired to scare me.

Rhodes firmly waved his hand, “Charge!”

The multitude soldiers received the order and immediately charged forth.

Even if you are an official Magus, so what? Facing so many Knights, your spiritual force wouldn’t last long. After this mission is done with, if worst comes to worst, I will just hide myself within the Argus Family and live comfortably. Anyways, with me under Lord Siegfried’s protection, what can you do?

Rhodes eyed Leylin resolutely, his face turning the shade of an abnormally faint red.

“My lord! Jenny! You both please go ahead.” Baelin then pulled out his long sword and his whole body swelled up like a balloon. He resembled a small giant as he blocked the carriage from harm.

After the enemy made their charge, he made his battle preparations and roused the secret Knight techniques that Leylin had instructed him in.

Also, the reason behind Rhodes’s unusual facial change was immediately accurately revealed within Leylin’s eyes.

“His pupils are unusually dilated. The blood flow in his brain has accelerated by 34%, a clear symptom of damage to his spirit.”

Seeing the deranged-looking Rhodes, Leylin was somewhat clear on why the opponent was acting so unbridled.

The studies of Magi were extremely dangerous. Any forms of expression could very well sacrifice the Magus’ life into it. Furthermore, once there was a slight mistake in important matters that concerned the consciousness, meditation, and spiritual force, many detrimental outcomes could be created.

This Rhodes, clearly received some harm to his sea of consciousness when he advanced to become a level 3 acolyte. He cannot completely control his spirit and his emotions, and so he appears rather nervous.

However, the reason why Rhodes went mad is only a small matter. Leylin only gave him a slight gaze before he focused his attention on the charging cavalry, his mouth displaying a slight sneer.

The charging troops had approximately 200 people. It seems as if the entirety of the Lilan Castle had come to battle. All of them had donned excellent quality armor and the pikes and huge battle axes they wielded carried a sharp, cold glint.

Two hundred mounts charged forth and the ground started to quake and under this mighty launch, Baelin only resembled a small, bemused ant.

This kind of battle formation would even cause a Magus to frown, but Leylin stood calmly as if nothing of importance was happening.

“Why do you all always use a common man’s way of thinking against a Magus?”

He lightly sighed and a faint khaki-colored light fell to the ground from his hands.

*Hissssss!* This light was as tiny as a firefly, and it looked as if a puff of breath blown on it would extinguish it.

After the khaki-colored light appeared on the ground, it promptly vanished from sight, as if it had fused into the soil and immediately ripples of tremors began to disperse out from the place where the light blended into the soil.

*Bang! Boom! Boom! Bang! Bang!*

The tremors began to extend in all directions as if several dominoes had been struck down, and the tremors gained and dispersed more and more power. Finally, there even occurred an earthquake.

*Crrrrrrrrrackkk!* The ground began to split open. The huge shockwaves made the Knights feel as if they were caught in the crossfire of bullets.

The surroundings quickly looked like as if there were waves from the sea surging forth causing continuous tremors.

“Argh!” “Earthquake!” “My horse” “Save me, my legs are broken!”

The rifts began to open from the Knight at the forefront before they soon covered the ground of where the whole cavalry was.

Along with the tremors, many horses stumbled and even threw their Knights atop them down.

The ear-splitting bone cracks, the neighing of the horses were all covered by the tremors that the earthquake caused. Only Baelin and James with a certain level of physical ability could barely make out the noise.

*Rumble*

The shock wave swept away all the soldiers and still continued on further till they dissipated.

As for the consumption of this spell, it was barely five spiritual force points.

Magi wielded intelligence! Not brute strength! What Leylin did earlier was to calculate the conditions of the surroundings, before using very little force to cause a devastating earthquake using the butterfly effect.

Just one strike! A crushing defeat! More than two hundred cavalrymen were now dead. The wails of the injured and broken bits of limbs left Rhodes in utter shock.

“He…How can he be this powerful?”

Rhodes roared within his heart before he frantically turned away to escape.

“Baelin! Go capture him!” Leylin pointed at Rhodes. However, Baelin stood there stupefied, not moving an inch.

“Aren’t you going?” Leylin flicked his finger, only to have a translucent palm slap the back of Baelin’s head.

“Oh! Okay!” Only then did Baelin regain his senses, running towards the direction Rhodes had escaped in.

“Mister Leylin! No, Lord Leylin! Pardon my presumptuous question… But what is your rank as an official Magus?”

Just then, James paid his respects to Leylin using the most revered formality, with Jenny following suit behind.

“Me?” Leylin grinned, “I’m just a rank 1 Magus who is shuffling his feet in front of the door of truth…”

“So you are indeed an official Magus! Please pardon our disrespect to you earlier!”

After hearing the words from Leylin’s own mouth, Jenny and James sighed in relief. They once again bowed to Leylin before an uncontrollable glee filled their eyes.

Chapter 309: Lost

The Argus Family’s Marquis illness demanded immediate attention, and time was running short. If they were unable to send the Dragon-Blooded Flower Bud back to the Marquis on time, he would very likely be poisoned to death.

By then, Jenny’s two uncles would have most likely seized control of the internal powers within the Argus Family.

This was a scene that Jenny was not willing to witness.

However, to let her and James pass through the Weeping Ghost Grounds? That would only be courting death!

Hence, after hearing that Leylin agreed to it, Jenny and James were exhilarated.

“Oh, I got this! So, we’ll pass through the Weeping Ghost Grounds, right? This name is really distasteful!” Baelin spoke casually and returned to the driver’s seat, before cracking his whip.

As a local, the only knowledge he knew of his world was Potter Town and the nearby Woody Wastelands. Due to the limited traffic and deficiency of information that Potter Town received, he had no knowledge of other places.

In fact, this was his first time travelling!

Along with the horse neighing and the creaking made from the spokes of the wheels of the horse carriage, they gradually entered the area of the Weeping Ghost Grounds.

As the Weeping Ghost Grounds was labelled a forbidden area, very few travellers dared to tread through it. The roads had long since been abandoned, with many weeds and shrubs growing on the sides. Baelin could barely recognise the tracks that were once used as they travelled on uneven ground.

As the horse carriage went deeper into the Weeping Ghost Grounds, a layer of thin mist veiled the area, slowly engulfing their surroundings.

At first the mist was rather mild, but as it got denser, their vision was reduced to only a distance of five metres from the horse carriage.

“Lor… Lord Leylin! The mist is too dense now…” Baelin slowed the pace of the horse carriage. To be going quickly under such poor conditions was simply seeking death.

“I got this!”

Leylin waved his right arm, and a thread of grey mist swirled in his palm. It was dispersed in one moment yet they converged immediately after.

“There’s a bit of chilliness in this aura. Also, it’s not purely made from water vapours…”

He then ordered, “A.I. Chip, analyse components!”

[Beep! Mission establishing, gathering source material, analysis beginning…] The A.I. Chip’s voice intoned.

Very soon, a composition image appeared in front of Leylin’s eyes.

[The main component of this mist is water at 98.2%. There are also mixed amounts of salt, protein and other digestive enzymes…] [Through comparison with the database, it is determined to be the tears of a human! Accuracy: 99.99%]

The A.I. Chip’s reply shocked Leylin a bit. After a moment had passed, the corners of his lips curled upwards.

“Using tears as mist? Interesting! I have even caught a whiff of some spirit bodies in this…”

“Lord Leylin, is there anything wrong?”

Jenny and James looked at Leylin, their eyes filled with worry. During the A.I. Chip’s analysis, outsiders could only perceive Leylin staring blankly for a second before grinning to himself.

Weeping Ghost Grounds was a forbidden area established atop countless skeletons. If not for this official Magus, Leylin, standing guard this time, Jenny and James would not have dared to approach this area.

Furthermore, even with Leylin around, Jenny and James were still wary after entering the Weeping Ghost Grounds and did not let their guard down for a single moment.

“Lord Leylin! The mist is too much; I’ve lost my way…”

At this moment, Baelin stopped the horse carriage and turned back with an apologetic expression.

“This… How can this happen?” Jenny and James looked at each other before stepping out of the horse carriage. Very soon, they were stupefied by the amount of mist there was.

In front of the horse carriage were three forked paths, they seemed to be like branches of an ancient tree, winding and crooked, heading towards different directions.

There stood a badly damaged, rotten wooden signpost with countless vines creeping on it.

On the sign, the black words which had almost faded away were the names of the different paths and even had arrowheads pointing to their locations.

“Hut of the Weeping Woman, Paradise of Wailing Creatures, Jones’ Pastry Shop…What strange names are these?” Jenny was bewildered. “I haven’t been here before, but according to the map there should only be one path, nothing like forked paths of any sort…”

“It seems like we’ve met with some trouble!” James sighed exasperatedly, but deep down he felt a little more relieved.

Previously, he did not know what terrors were hidden inside the Weeping Ghost Grounds, which made him be on guard all the time. However, now that trouble had presented itself, he felt a little better.

At the very least, now that some troubles had appeared, their party had to solve them.

“Hng! Petty tricks!”

At this moment, Leylin walked out too. As he saw the sign, his expression showed distaste.

Very soon, a layer of red light flashed past Leylin’s pupils, and the surroundings underwent a tremendous change.

The grey mist immediately thinned, revealing many bizarrely shaped trees. As for the signpost, many tiny three-headed snakes and toads now covered the words which were previously there.

“These are only the effects of poltergeists, affecting the mental soundness of regular humans and even acolytes. If it’s only up to this extent, it would be such a disappointment.”

“Now I will lead the way, and you will just follow my movements.” Leylin let Jenny and James sat in the horse carriage as he took up the role of assistant driver.

“Yes, my Lord!”

After Leylin sat beside him, Baelin inhaled a deep breath, feeling much more relieved than before, “Which way do we go?”

“None of those paths, head to the extreme right!”

Leylin sneered at the originally pitched forks. At this moment, in Leylin’s vision, the three paths had all disappeared, turning into three huge caves that were covered by trees.

If the horse carriage entered those areas, they would definitely meet with a dead end. Once they had deviated from the main path, they would be trapped in there.

“But, those are granite rocks! How are we going to travel through that?” Baelin scratched his head.

The direction that Leylin had pointed in was where a large granite rock sturdily stood, with algae growing on it.

*Pak!* Before Baelin could finish talking, he was smacked on the head by Leylin, “Just go where I tell you to, why do you have so much rubbish to say?”

Baelin wailed, but his experiences and training with Leylin allowed him to quickly follow the instructions given.

The horse carriage moved forward, charging towards the ten meter tall granite rock.

“Hey Hey! There’re only five more metres, should we stop now?”

Baelin questioned Leylin as he rode forward. However, as no reply was given, he had no choice but to grit his teeth and urge the horses forward.

“Three metres! One metre now!” Baelin cried in alarm but at the very end he gave up and shut his eyes.

*Pop!*

As the head of the horses crashed into the granite rock, the expected impact and cries did not happen.

Baelin widened his eyes in shocked, and very soon a strange sight occurred!

The heads of the two horses had already extended into the huge granite rock. Looking at this scene, it seemed like the huge rock had swallowed them.

The huge rock continuously engulfed the horses from their head to their necks, to their back and tails, and finally towards Baelin.

“Yikes!” Baelin unconsciously extended his right hand to block the impact, but very soon a flash appeared in his vision.

*Pop!* A feeling like walking past a wall of water came onto him, as Baelin looked at the surroundings in awe.

After passing through the granite rock, the mist thinned by a considerable amount. With the torches carried by the horses and the frightening physical abilities as a Grand Knight, Baelin’s vision had already extended to over a dozen metres.

On both sides of the road were black birch trees, growing in an orderly fashion. In the middle was a small path, which was where the horse carriage was travelling on. As for the original three forked pitches, they had completely vanished by now.

“Did we stumble upon some strange illusory spell earlier?” As a level 3 acolyte, James was the quickest to understand what had happened.

However, Leylin did not answer his question. On the contrary, he turned even more solemn, much more than when he looked at the pitched forks.

“The direction is wrong! This isn’t the scene that I saw earlier!”

In his earlier observation, the correct path that Leylin saw should have been a small road laid with brambles, but not such a neat and orderly looking road like this.

“Don’t tell me that I have also been influenced by the illusion earlier?” Leylin’s face turned dark.

However, the astonishment deep within his heart far surpassed what his face revealed. He was already a rank 2 Warlock! Although he was injured, a simple spirit body could no longer affect his senses.

“A.I. Chip! Scan the surroundings!”

Leylin rubbed his temples and ordered as a flash of blue light glowed in his eyes.

[Beep! Mission establishing, beginning scan!] [Alert! Alert! Due to unknown interference, the scan is unable to be accomplished. Will try again in 1 second…Bzzt..Bzzt…]

The A.I. Chip responded. However, very soon the feedback received was like a broken tape mixed with a radio with no signals, giving off a buzzy feedback noise.

This piercing noise grew louder and louder, finally turning into the ear-piercing wail of a woman.

“Wuu…Wuu…”

This noise filled Leylin’s head, making him dizzy.

“Have you guys heard anything? I think I hear a woman crying!”

In reality, Baelin muttered. He soon received the responses of Jenny and James, “Us too!”

“Over there!” James suddenly pointed.

Leylin also looked in the direction James had indicated, and under a rotten birch tree, a woman wearing a long black dress was crouching and weeping.

“This voice! This voice! It’s Marsha’s! I won’t ever forget it!”

An incredulous look was on James’ face. He quickly hopped off the horse carriage and rushed to the woman.

Chapter 310: Dreamland’s Creature

“Marsha! My beloved Marsha, is that you?”

Agitation filled James’ voice as he skipped lightly towards the woman in the black dress, reaching out his hands to pull her shoulders back.

Leylin stood on the horse carriage while observing, yet he did not stop James.

The situation right now was extremely strange, and he needed a guinea pig to test the waters.

James used some force to turn the woman in black dress around.

Suddenly, all he saw was a face with no orifices, but only a black swirl on it.

*Xiu!* Horror filled James’ face as he seemed to be pulled into a long black string and was continuously swirled as he was absorbed into the woman’s face.

The whole process was extremely quick, ending just as Leylin was about to lend a hand. However, through a replay, he could clearly see how James was stretched and distorted bit by bit into more than a dozen metres and eventually absorbed into the woman’s swirling face.

This time disorder left Leylin feeling so disgusted that he wanted to puke.

At the same time, his heart sank.

“This is definitely not any sort of spirit body, but a more terrifying existence that I am still unable to comprehend…”

In an instant, Leylin recalled from the A.I. Chip’s database that back in ancient times, battles between two high ranking Magi would often devastate the earth and seas around them. At the same time, they could separate the dimensions of space and time, causing others to perceive things incorrectly.

Especially in such places, there would often be strange beings with terrifying powers.

Some of these existences were extremely weak, such that even a level 3 acolyte could easily eradicate them. However, some others were so terrifying that they could even surpass the powers of the Morning Star Magi, directly causing the stars in the sky to fall!

“This black clothed woman is but an apparition. Once certain conditions are fulfilled, the swirl on her face activates, swallowing any objects that come close to it…”

Leylin made his conclusion in an instant. “Right now, my power is still lacking. Against such an apparition, which obviously isn’t weak, choosing to engage without any further information is simply a foolish act. Run!”

His body instantly turned into black mist and vanished into the thin air.

With the flicker of black light, Leylin’s body appeared several hundred meters away with a black arc that followed behind.

“Wuuuuu!”

However, the ear-piercing screams still sounded in Leylin’s ears, the pitch of which was even higher than before.

Leylin was stupefied as he found himself changing directions and flying towards the woman in the black dress.

*Ka-cha!*

The woman stood up and her skull split open into two halves. From that gaping hole, rows of razor sharp fangs were revealed, as though her face had turned into the jaws of a creature.

*Bang!* The giant jaw snapped shut, and darkness enveloped Leylin.

……

Leylin felt as if he had fallen from an extremely high place and hit the ground before his body shuddered as he regained consciousness.

“I seem to have been swallowed by that woman earlier!”

“Where is this?”

Leylin rubbed his head as he looked at his surroundings.

The room was dark and small, with many spiderwebs at the corners. There was not a single piece of furniture, nor even windows or a door.

It seemed to be a small, sealed basement of the sorts.

Besides Leylin, there also lay Baelin and Jenny. Their eyes were shut tight as they were unconscious. It seemed like they would need a long while before regaining consciousness.

“An even deeper illusion!” Leylin was extremely solemn.

“If the three pitched forks of the road were the superficial layer of this illusion, the women in the black dress was the second layer, and this, the third!”

An illusion! Also, Leylin did not have much interaction with the dreamland, but in ancient times, the Magi had once conquered another large world, in which the inhabitants had wielded dream and illusory powers. Through the powers of the dream realm, they could easily accomplish anything, and were even revered as gods by the ignorant inhabitants of the other planes and dimensions!

Also, through a short paragraph recorded in antique books, Leylin knew that the further one threaded into an illusion, the more difficult it was to escape.

“I’ve got to get out! The third level of an illusion is dangerous enough!”

Black flames ignited in Leylin’s palm, “Latent Fireball!”

The black fireball struck a corner of the basement, creating a deep hole.

“First I must understand the constructs of this illusion!” Leylin rubbed his chin. He had no better solution against such a power, so he could only test things out before searching for other methods.

……

Leylin jumped into the dark hole he created.

“It’s the 193rd time, yet I’m back at this place!” Leylin looked at Jenny and Baelin who were still unconscious, his expression looking extremely severe.

“Through my experiments, I have already understood the three-dimensional constructs in here. As expected, the deeper the level of illusion, the less sturdy the dimensions within are, which will finally turn into chaos…”

If the dimensions here were to collapse, there were only two possibilities. Either one would enter a deeper levelled illusion, or if their spirit was unable to bear the brunt of it, they would directly be swallowed by the caster of this illusion.

“I’ve tried all other places, so I am only left with this now!”

Leylin kicked the unconscious bodies of Baelin and Jenny away, revealing the dusty grey floor beneath them.

With a fireball, the ground was shattered…

*Pop!* The floor of the basement cracked opened, and Leylin jumped into it.

“It’s still the same basement as before, but Jenny and Baelin have already disappeared. Good! Very good! There is finally some change…”

Leylin’s eyes swept over the surroundings. It was still the same cramped basement. However, what was different than before was that Jenny and Baelin’s bodies were no longer here.

“Signs of repair that cannot keep up with the damage done huh? Next, I’ll have to…” As if plucking the strings of a zither, both of Leylin’s hands streaked across the void, creating circles of ripples.

Under the movements of his fingers, the texture of the underground basement resembled water with light ripples.

The greater the area the ripples covered, the more the void contorted, until finally, a pop sound was heard!

The space of the underground basement shattered, and Leylin’s body dropped downwards once again.

……

Mirrors! Bright mirrors were everywhere, reflecting the appearance of a black haired, noble youth.

“This should be the interval between the two levels of the illusion!”

Leylin touched the ice-cold mirror and made a deduction.

Right now, he had momentarily escaped from the illusion. This would definitely draw the attention of the caster.

However, this was the effect he desired!

“Wuu..Wuu…!”

At this moment, the weeping voice of an adorable girl traveled over.

Leylin abruptly turned his head, and in one corner of a mirror, he saw a little purple haired girl wearing a red dress with white socks who was crying.

“Wuuuu… Alice has lost her little bear! Big Brother, can you accompany me to search for it?”

The little girl stopped her crying and looked at Leylin with imploring eyes.

“My apologies, but I cannot!” Leylin shook his head.

”But why?” The little girl was puzzled. “Alice is extremely obedient! Don’t you like Alice?”

As she spoke, more mirror images appeared in the surroundings.

“I want to, but let us speak first!” Leylin tried his best to speak calmly.

He did not have much experience dealing with such strange entities. Furthermore, the other party was a higher dimensional creature. Their trains of thought and level of thinking would be different than humans. Leylin himself did not know if he could convince it to let him go.

“Won’t you accompany Alice to find her little bear?”

“No!” Leylin shook his head his head resolutely. It was rumoured in legends that similar things had happened before. Once one agreed to such a request, it would be treated as them having signed some sort of bizarre contract, and they would fall under the manipulation of others. Some were even indefinitely sucked into other dimensions.

Although there were a few lucky ones who had obtained mysterious strength through such encounters, Leylin was never one who relied on gambling, especially when his life would be at stake!

*Crash!*

Just as Leylin rejected her, countless beetles poured from the mirrors and engulfed him like a tide.

“I’ll still have to attack!” Leylin’s brows furrowed. He knew that he had to demonstrate his strength before the other party would acknowledge him.

“Latent Fireball! Eyes of Petrification!”

In an instant, his whole body was covered in scales, and black flames continuously billowed from his hands. Even his eyes had a mysterious light that shot outwards.

*Pak! Pak!*

Many of the black beetles were petrified as they fell to the ground, turning into a pile of dust. As for most of them, they were burnt into nothingness by the black flames.

However, the beetles still poured out continuously from the mirrors, and what Leylin had managed to get rid of was but one hair from nine oxen.

“The strength of my opponent has far exceeded my imagination!”

Leylin smiled wryly as he tossed a red powder out, “Scorching Touch!”

Two scorching rays of light were released, clearing the path in two directions.

However, Leylin’s face turned pale immediately, and his consciousness wavered. The crystallised spiritual force had even more cracks opened, almost shattered.

Scorching Touch was a rank 2 spell, and right now Leylin only had a portion of his spiritual force solidified. With the strength of a rank 1 Magus, he would naturally receive backlash from recklessly using a rank 2 spell.

This backlash was considered relatively light. If he were to use the innate talent of a rank 2 Magus, it was very likely that his sea of consciousness would undergo drastic changes.

“Chi Chi!”

The sea of beetles cried incessantly, once again pouring towards Leylin.

Leylin, whose spiritual force was already depleted, could only watch as layer after layer of beetles engulfed his body.

Chapter 311: Eastern Region’s Capital City

The black beetles completely covered Leylin’s body; it was as if he was wearing a very thick, black coat.

Numerous beetles tried to gnaw on Leylin’s body; their teeth struck upon his black scales, resulting in crinkling noises.

Leylin’s body emitted a black light and the layer of beetles trembled and fell off, but right after they just extended their exoskeletons and crawled back up.

These beetles eventually even advanced to the only exposed part of Leylin’s body: his eyes! They wanted to completely submerge him in the sea of their bodies!

“I underestimated them,” Leylin muttered. He had not expected that these black beetles would be so troublesome. There was not enough time for him to execute Toxic Bile!

“Ah! How can I die in this place?”

Leylin roared, and at this exact moment, the Giant Kemoyin Serpent’s bloodline within his body began to violently circulate.

Soon, Leylin’s pupils became amber colored vertical slits, and while facing the sky, he let out a loud hiss!.

“Hisssss!”

It sounded fierce, and appeared very sinister! A tremendous, devilish aura was cleanly emitted from Leylin’s body; it was as if a predator from ancient times had been resurrected.

Black energy spewed out of his body and congealed behind his back, taking the form of the Giant Kemoyin Serpent, which hissed into the sky.

*Rumble! rumble!*

Along with this huge shockwave, the beetles, which had forcefully crawled all over Leylin, turned to dust in midair, as if they had all been struck by bullets.

Leylin’s roars still echoed, and the power and emotions in his blood vessels recklessly surged.

*Ka cha! Snap!*

The surface of the surrounding mirrors covered with cracks and then exploded with a loud bang, exposing an opening of hollow space.

“Fu…Fu…”, Leylin stopped his roaring and started panting heavily.

Just now, at the critical moment, the blood essence of the Giant Kemoyin Serpent within his body had exploded, which had also placed a very strong burden on his body.

Currently, Leylin was surrounded by pitch-black nothingness. Spread about on the ground were the butchered limbs of the black beetles.

*Hoo! Hoo!*

The mutilated corpses of the black beetles hovered in midair and formed the black face of a woman, which said, “A Warlock with the bloodline of the ancient Giant Kemoyin Serpent? I also get a whiff of the nauseous odor of spirits from your body.”

Her lips squirmed as she spoke in the ancient Byron language.

It seems like it only likes the pure spirits of humans. As for the bodies of Warlocks, not only do they have a distinct bloodline, their spirits are different from normal spirits as well. Hence it doesn’t like this scent!

Although he put on a calm expression, Leylin was inwardly excited. Using the ancient Byron language, he said, “I accidentally intruded upon your territory. I request that you let me leave; I will also pay a ransom for it…”

This existence wasn’t human, so Leylin bluntly stated his conditions.

“Not bad! However, I do not like the spirit of a Warlock.” The huge human face responded, “As for the price for redeeming your spirit and those of the other two civilians, I ask that you give me those green spirit crystals in your pouch.”

“The green spirit crystals?” Leylin was startled. Immediately, upon his hand, were some beautiful crystals that emitted a green radiance and luster like that of a green diamond.

“Yes, precisely!” The huge human face spoke.

Those are the ancient, pure spirit crystals that I got by killing the Loathsome Evil in the Ancient Spirit Slaying Sect’s secret realm. There are rumors that these crystals are valued equally highly by all existences in the different worlds… A flash of understanding went through Leylin’s mind.

“So that will be the ransom for releasing me and the other two!” Leylin nodded, expressing his agreement. Then he asked, “What happened to that old man in the beginning?”

“He is deeply immersed in the illusion; he has already lost himself within my body….”

The huge human face replied.

Leylin had already guessed that to be so. He sighed, “Send me out!”

……

Hu…”

Leylin opened his eyes and found himself lying on one side within the carriage. Baelin and Jenny were on the other side, and James’ body had silently vanished.

In the same way, the soul crystals also disappeared from Leylin’s hands.

“Here it is, the original location of the three-forked paths…”

By now, the grey mist had settled down for the most part. The three forked paths and the huge granite rock had all faded, and in their place was the original road.

Leylin could clearly recognize the direction, and he quickly drove the horse carriage and left this place.

“This time, it was really dangerous!”

While Leylin kept driving, some traces of fear still lingered. If not for the enemy having disliked the idea of having her spirit contaminated by Leylin’s bloodline, or perhaps even having feared the power of Leylin’s bloodline, Leylin would have also ended up like James, being forever trapped in the body of that huge face made of beetles.

The further he went, the more the mist began to clear up, until eventually, it completely vanished, exposing the view of overgrown fields on both sides of the road up ahead.

“The Weeping Ghost Grounds are truly a dangerous place!”

The traumatic experience that Leylin had just gone through caused him to keep turning around and check behind his back as he continued to drive, up until he completely lost sight of the Weeping Ghost Grounds.

Behind him, the fading gray mist congealed again to form a wall that blocked his view.

I also wonder about the two Magi who had once fought there—what rank were they, and what was the result of their battle? Leylin thought, and then he sighed.

Just the aftermath of a fight had disturbed time and space and had created such a strange place. Leylin knew from this that these Magi’s powers exceeded his own imagination. They were probably existences that surpassed Morning Star Magi!

“There will inevitably be a day when I, too, will reach such a level!”

This time’s incidents only reinforced Leylin’s resolution to become stronger.

“Oh! Where am I?”

After leaving the Weeping Ghost Grounds, Baelin woke up, holding his head with his hands.

“How do you feel? Do you remember anything from before you lost consciousness?” Without turning around, Leylin asked while he brandished his horsewhip.

“My memories are not very clear. I think that we encountered a woman as we passed through the gray mist.” Baelin looked as perplexed as he sounded.

Very soon, the horses’ reins were placed in his hands.

“You woke up just in time! You can drive the carriage instead of me!”

Leylin pushed the whip into Baelin’s hands and sat back to enjoy this free manpower of his.

Baelin’s physique was that of a Grand Knight, and thus, he woke up before Jenny. However, Jenny was still a level 1 acolyte, so she woke up soon after Baelin.

“Very good reaction!”

Leylin looked at Jenny who was still pretending to be unconscious as he touched Jenny’s hand and complimented her indifferently.

“So it’s Mister Leylin!” Jenny shuddered and opened her eyes, “I thought it was the bad guys!”

Afterwards, she opened the carriage window and looked out of it to see that there was no grey mist.

“Have we already left the Weeping Ghost Grounds? Where is James?”

“Yes, we are now in Olive Fields. We will be seeing the capital city of the eastern region of the Twilight Zone in two days at most.”

Leylin slowly nodded, “As for James, you had best prepare yourself mentally…”

A short while later, Baelin, who was driving outside of the carriage, heard Jenny cry out in alarm, “No, it can not be so. You are telling a lie!”

*Bang!* The carriage door opened, from which a tearful Jenny could be seen.

“Jenny, you…” Seeing Jenny look so broken-hearted, Baelin was bewildered.

*Sob! Sob!* Jenny threw herself into Baelin’s embrace and began to cry loudly.

……

The Twilight Zone was divided into 5 regions: the east, west, north, south, and central regions. The capital city of the eastern region was the most flourishing city in all the Twilight Zone and was also the center of politics and business.

Many aristocratic families had set up their headquarters here, forming the aristocrats’ alliance which held a major influence in the entire eastern region.

There were also many Magi conducting research and establishing academies in secret locations there, which caused this place to be a meeting point for magicians.

In the center of the city, there was a sun stone that was the size of a small mountain, which brought eternal light and heat to this entire region.

“The city’s walls are very tall!”

On this day, in the eastern region’s capital city, a country bumpkin could be seen gaping at this tall and sturdy castle wall.

“Enough!” Leylin used the sheath of his sword to hit Baelin on the head, stopping him from continuing to behave like this.

Although the eastern region’s capital city looked huge, as he looked around, it seemed to Leylin that it was the same as Nightless City. As a result, the way Baelin behaved made Leylin feel ashamed.

“You really are causing me to lose face,” he reprimanded Baelin.

Hearing this, Baelin rubbed his head and looked at the surroundings, only pointing at the citizens from time to time. Only after a while did he smile in embarrassment as he said, “Lord! From the day I was born, I have never set eyes upon such tall city walls. I’m really sorry…”

Leylin was rather speechless. If not for the number of people around, he may have even harboured thoughts of killing Baelin right there and then.

“Tee hee… Lord Leylin, Baelin has only seen Potter Town until now. This degree of astonishment is quite a reasonable reaction!”

At this moment, Jenny, who was nursing her sorrow, was amused by Baelin’s behaviour. She sniggered as she helped Baelin out of his predicament.

However, after seeing Jenny answer for him, Baelin drooped his head in embarrassment, not doing any other potential things that could be unbearable to look at.

After all, in front of the girl he loved, Baelin still had to put up some poise.

“Alright! Since we have sent Miss Jenny back safely, we should bid our farewells now!”

The atmosphere in the horse carriage turned silent, yet Leylin still smiled and faced Jenny.

“What?!” “What!?” Two shocked gasps were uttered by the two youths.

“Wh…Why? This is too sudden!” Baelin felt that something was amiss, yet he could not put his thoughts into words.

“Lord Leylin! I still request that you visit my Argus Family. My father will definitely wish to have your acquaintance, and Baelin’s as well!”

Jenny bit her lips.

“From the start, I mentioned that we were only travelling together out of convenience!”

Leylin’s expression turned resolute. “As for you, Baelin, you can return with Jenny! Furthermore, there are already people coming to receive you, Jenny!” He smiled.

*Thud Thud*

Right after Leylin spoke, the continuous thuds of hooves of horses sounded out. The approaching party was a group of white Knights sitting upon handsome steeds. On the tops of their helmets was a white feathered ornament. Their armour had not even a single speck of dust, and even their horses were fully white in colour!

Chapter 315: Secret Knight Technique

“Oh! No no no! I think you’ve misunderstood me!” Leylin hurriedly shook his head.

“While I am acquainted to Jenny, I also have no intentions whatsoever to partake in the Argus Family’s internal strife!”

Leylin made his stand.

With just one sentence, the calamity that was befalling Jenny and her father would be resolved. Even Lucas would not hold any objections anymore. However, what has all this got to do with Leylin?

Not only that, but after influencing Siegfried’s decision Leylin would owe him a favour! Favours are oftentimes the most difficult of things to repay!

Moreover, directly interfering with another Magus’ family matters could be seen as being disrespectful.

Whether or not Siegfried chose to mask his emotions, he would definitely be displeased about it.

Leylin did not concern himself with these issues. On one hand, Jenny’s father had some worldly factions supporting him while on the other hand, Lucas had the backing of Siegfried. There was simply no hesitation when weighing the benefits.

After all, with his years of experience, he was already used to making decisions by weighing benefits. This was also the principle that Magi practiced.

As expected, after hearing Leylin’s words, Siegfried smiled even more broadly. “Leylin, I think you are still unfamiliar with the Magi factions in the capital right? Don’t worry, you can pay me a visit to learn more about it whenever you like. I’ll also bring you to some Magi organisational places for networking and to make some new friends!”

“That’ll be fantastic!” After achieving the goal he came for, Leylin revealed his joy.

Leylin and Siegfried then exchanged some information that they knew about high-grade meditation techniques. Although Siegfried had amassed a bountiful amount of information for 250 years, he was still somewhat amazed by some of the theoretical practices simulated by the A.I. Chip. So much so that he almost wanted to immediately have them undergo practical tests. This was a form of acknowledgement of Leylin’s scholarly knowledge. As for Leylin, he respected the time that Siegfried had placed into his experiments.

After their sharing of information, both parties felt that the time spent was extremely short. Hence, only after setting a date for their next meeting did Siegfried reluctantly send Leylin off.

……

Now that Leylin had neglected to help Jenny’s father, the series of events that happened could only be expected.

During the Argus Family’s council, Lucas had amassed enough backing to take on the role of the next family head and to obtain the status of a Marquis!

During that very same night, the original Marquis died a painful death from a poison attack!

As for Jenny, she was accused of putting poison inside the Dragon-Blooded Flower Bud, thereby murdering her father.

Anyone with a discerning eye could tell that this was the lowest kind of set-up with a childish ploy. However, Lucas wanted to use this very method to know who stood on his side within the family and at the same time establish his dominance!

This deliberate misrepresentation of making a deer out to be a horse was done to punish Jenny, and to set an example for others.

After using a few lightning quick moves to rid himself of the opposing factions within the family, Lucas had a firm grip on the powers within the Argus Family. The entire family implicitly allowed this to carry on, and even corroborated the story of Jenny poisoning her own father!

Power struggles were often this harsh. Win, and become king. Lose, and become a dog. This was but another example of the bloody battles in this dog eat dog world.

“Hu..Huu…”

Jenny dashed rapidly through a dark forest.

This girl of noble birth had now lost her elegant and haughty appearance. Her skirt had already been torn apart by the shrubberies. Blood streaked her face and she had an extremely miserable appearance; worse than a beggar’s.

“Dearest father!” Tears streaked down her face as she continued running.

The events had transpired so quickly that they left Jenny thinking that the whole thing was all but a dream.

Her backing, which was her very own father, had died just like that through a conspiracy. Worse yet, she was labelled as the murderer!

Dear heavens! Jenny did not know how perverted one had to be to brandish her as the murderer!

However, what followed next left her speechless. Under the immense political power, such absurdity was validated by the others, and even labelled her as a wanted criminal.

In fact, if not for the few loyal servants and kin who had tipped her off and protected her along the way, she would definitely not be able to escape with just her strength as a level 1 acolyte.

Of course, after helping her, those close ones encountered terrible fates.

*Plop!* Jenny stumbled on a tree root as she ran. Mud was splashed in the area as this young lady sobbed spasmodically as she knelt on the ground.

Even if she managed to escape this time, what good would there be ahead of her? Be it other nobles or even the common folk, she would be seen as a murderer. Her eventual outcome would either to be caught and be sentenced to execution, or to hide her name and honour in dirt, never revealing her identity. Just from thinking about this fact, Jenny adopted a bleak outlook for her future.

“Wuu…Why…Why did things turn out this way?” Jenny cried.

“Jejeje! Look at the pathetic state you’re in!”

At this moment, a familiar voice sounded behind her back, leaving shudders throughout her body.

She turned around and saw a tall Knight in armour, who had a malevolent scar across his face.

“‘Dagger’ Todd, one of my father’s personal bodyguards, even you dare to betray me?”

This man had the terrifying strength of a Grand Knight, and was even one of her father’s own bodyguards, and as such commanded quite a lot of trust.

Todd only sniggered towards the lamentations of the young lady. However, his smile made his scarred face look even more horrifying.

“In fact, I’ve always been on Lucas’ side. So there is no betrayal per se!”

Jenny’s pupils dilated as she suddenly got a bad premonition.

“And as the reward of being an undercover operative, Lord Lucas has allowed me to seek pleasure with you before killing you!” Todd licked his lips and revealed a wanton grin.

“Five years! A full five years of listening to you call me Uncle Todd! In reality, during my duties I have thought frequently of possessing you, feasting on you, ripping you!”

“You! You sick pervert!” After listening to the man admitting to the desires of wanting her even since she was a ten year old girl, Jenny’s hair stood on ends.

“Yes! I’m a pervert, but what can you do about it? Missy of the Argus Family!”

Todd advanced as he peeled off his gloves, “Relax, I will give you a great time…”

Jenny scuttled backwards, as if Todd was some kind of terrifying beast.

However, Todd was, in this moment, worse than a monster!

“Save me! Help, someone please save me!”

The girl wailed helplessly as tears streamed down her face.

“Stop!”

“At this moment, a extremely youthful voice sounded. What followed soon after was the wind caused from a blade being swung!

“Eh?” Todd jumped back and looked at the lad who had emerged from nowhere.

“Baelin!” Jenny snuggled into Baelin’s arms as she sobbed quietly.

“You bastard, I’m going to kill you!” Baelin stared coldly at the large Knight in front of him. He seethed in fury, for had he arrived a moment later, something bad would have happened to Jenny.

It was the first time in his life that Baelin wanted to kill someone so badly!

“Kill me? Are you able to?” Todd unsheathed the sword hung at his waist. “You must be this missy’s lover! I’ve decided that I will first chop off your four limbs, then take her right in front of you! At the time, your expression will definitely be extremely fascinating to watch. Perhaps, you can even join us…”

Todd licked his lips and smirked.

“Arghhhh….!” Baelin swung his cross blade that carried a flash of white light as he could not bear to listen for a moment longer.

“Grand Knight!” Todd turned solemn immediately.

His giant sword was swung forward as it clashed with the cross blade, emitting sparks.

*Clang Clang Clang!* Todd retreated several steps. “What power!” The vibrations sent from Baelin’s swing left his hands somewhat numb.

“Kill him Baelin! Kill him!” Jenny wailed loudly behind Baelin.

Under the encouragement of his loved one, Baelin advanced and struck, sending Todd staggering backwards by several steps.

“Ping!” Just as the two weapons clashed, Todd suddenly released his giant sword and rushed to Baelin’s side like a sweeping wind.

*Ka-cha!* A black dagger suddenly appeared in his hand and pierced towards Baelin’s heart like a venomous snake!

Baelin struggled to move his body away, and a layer of spiritual life force appeared on his chest. *Pak!* As if thin leather, the dagger pierced through and left a deep gash on Baelin’s chest, allowing blood to flow profusely.

*Shing!* Todd suddenly appeared from a distance away as he licked the edge of his dagger.

“Now you’d know why they call me ‘Dagger’ huh? Because I like to cut the flesh of my prey with this dagger, and then watch them die of anguish!”

Todd’s face turned red and he spoke excitedly, “Your blood is the tastiest I’ve ever tried!”

“Secret Gale Technique!” Todd shouted and spiritual life force wrapped around his calves.

*Shik Shik!* He advanced again, this time even faster than before!

“Damn it! Secret technique, Cross Star!”

After suffering from several more wounds, Baelin could not bear it any longer and shouted.

*Weng!* His body suddenly doubled in size as a layer of translucent armour protected him.

Chapter 316: Chamber of Commerce

”Ka-cha!”

Todd’s black dagger slashed across the translucent armour, but it harmlessly bounced off.

“It’s a defensive secret technique!” Todd’s eyes gleamed.

There were many secret techniques for Grand Knights, but many of them were just a large boost in a single attribute.

For example, Todd’s secret technique focused on speed, raising it to twice his original speed!

From what he could see, Baelin had mustered a technique that boosted his defense.

“Dummy, once your technique wears off, you will still be slain by me!” A sinister smile appeared on Todd’s face.

However, Baelin suddenly moved!

Speed! Baelin was extremely quick; as he moved, his translucent armour created a shrill noise from the wind passing through.

Todd could only see the bare afterimages!

“It’s…actually the two attributes buff!” Todd cried out hoarsely, yet the greed in his eyes only grew more apparent.

Such a technique was of a considerably high grade that existed only in myths. Even the Argus Family had not seen anyone wielding such a technique for the longest of times.

However, Todd did not have much time to think. Baelin had already appeared in front of him as he raised his cross blade, furiously slashing down at Todd.

“Clang!” Todd jumped back and parried with the dagger in his hand.

*Peng!” As the two weapons clashed, Todd’s dagger was sent flying out of his grip.

“There is even a strength buff! Three attributes! A secret technique that buffs three areas!” Todd’s mind was blank at this moment. A two attributes buff was not unheard of, but this three attributes buff of a Grand Knight level was practically unheard of, even in legends!

However, Baelin had no desire to explain things to him.

He charged forward and swung his sword at Todd’s neck.

*Pu!* The head that carried a scarred face was sent flying, as a blood fountain gushed to a metre’s height from the neck.

“Jenny, are you alright?!”

Baelin dispelled the translucent armour and rushed to Jenny’s side.

“I… I’m alright!” Jenny replied involuntarily, before seeing Baelin collapse at her side.

Although the Cross Star was a technique taught to him by Leylin, who was not a Grand Knight, the might of it exceeded that of other Grand Knight techniques, but still retained the same properties of a Grand Knight technique!

As for Baelin, who had activated this technique, he entered a feeble state. Even raising an arm was too difficult for him; only his eyes and mouth could just barely move.

“You… why are you this silly? This does not even concern you…” Jenny wept, and tears once again streamed down her face.

“Keke…I’m fine!” Baelin tried his best to mask his current weakened state, but it was all done in vain.

“I’ve thought about it—let’s seek asylum from Lord Leylin! He will definitely be able to protect you!” Baelin spoke what’s on his mind.

“… We can’t do that!” Jenny wryly smiled and replied.

“Baelin! Can’t you discern the truth from this misfortune? Lord Leylin has already abandoned me!” Jenny smiled bitterly, “You had better return to Lord Leylin, where he can protect you! Lucas won’t be able to cause you any harm…”

“No!” Baelin’s face flushed red. “I won’t leave you even if I die!”

“Baelin!” Jenny crouched down as both of them engaged in a passionate kiss.

After the long and intense tongue fight, Baelin seemed to have changed immediately. “Let us go! To the middle region! To where the dark elves’ kingdoms are! To the area of darkness! Whatever it is, let us leave here to a place where no one can find us, and live happily ever after!”

“Alright!”

Jenny resolutely replied.

The two exchange gazes and smiled brightly.

……

“Huh! It seems as though Baelin has decided to leave!”

Leylin ruminated in amusement as he saw the extremely tidy and neat room, in which a letter lay on the table.

To him, Baelin was only a pet that he was raising while nursing his injury.

As for the current Leylin, he had already returned to the right path, and no longer had time to take care of Baelin. Perhaps it was the best choice to allow him to leave.

Furthermore, Leylin did not have much use for Baelin. Even if he was turned into a Branded Swordsman, the strength of a rank 1 Magus was not sufficient to aid Leylin.

“However, this is my first time having good intentions! I hope you can pass down my cross blade technique throughout the Twilight Zone and not ruin the name of my Farlier family…”

A profound light flashed in Leylin’s eyes.

Through the sense of the Sacred Flame he had, he already knew that Baelin and Jenny were not regular folks. What’s more, they would be taking the stage in Twilight Zone as the ‘main characters’!

One would expect that in the near future, they would definitely not have any sort of peaceful lives—troubles would come searching for them one after another.

“But only then are things interesting! My setup can finally be put to good use!”

Leylin smiled gently, before putting this matter at the back of his head.

Today was the day that he had set with Siegfried to meet other official Magus. Leylin had been anticipating this day for quite a while.

“So it’s here?”

Leylin and Siegfried, dressed in common folk clothes, walked into an extremely lavish shop.

“Gersi’s Chamber of Commerce, the most outstanding conclave in the whole of the eastern Twilight Zone. Some of the nobility even know that there is a Magi organisation supporting this conclave from the shadows…”

Siegfried smiled as he explained this to Leylin.

Although they spoke as if no one was beside them, their voices did not travel far enough for the people in the surroundings to hear.

“As for us, the other Magi who are in small associations or are wandering around, we like to gather here for a couple of days and exchange some valuable insights gleaned from recent experiments or the experience gained from meditation techniques. Sometimes trades will be conducted too. Of course, all these are only restricted to the official Magus level.”

Siegfried wore a large black glove, hiding his metal prosthetic limb within it.

“Welcome! How may I help you?”

Two beautiful maidservants came over and asked after Siegfried stepped into Gersi’s Chamber of Commerce.

“Take me to the VIP room!” Siegfried handed a gold card to the maidservant, whose eyes immediately started to shine.

“My two Lords, please follow me!” She bowed deeply, showing off the curves of her chest. As she led the way, she exaggeratedly swayed her hips.

“How is it? Do you want to play for a while?” Siegfried asked Leylin with a smile on his face.

“I have no such urges now, so maybe after this!” Leylin smiled indifferently and replied.

As the maidservant in front heard Leylin’s words, disappointment streaked across her face.

Although she was somewhat disappointed, the maid still quickly brought them to an extremely lavishly decorated room. “My apologies! As my level is not high enough, our manager will take over and assist you from here!”

The girl bowed again and took her leave.

“Our Magus VIP cards are different from others, so the person who is serving us next will know our requirements and will bring us to the conclave!”

Siegfried explained the process simply to Leylin.

“The membership registration is extremely simple. You need to first reach the rank of an official Magus, and then have another Magus refer you. I’ll set a referral up for you later!”

“I appreciate it!” Leylin smiled gently.

*Boom!* At this moment, an oil painting in the VIP room swung open, revealing a flight of stairs.

“Honoured guests, please follow me!”

An upper-class woman with the spiritual force of a level 3 acolyte appeared in the tunnel. Her skin was flawless and white like porcelain, without any traces of pores.

“Alright!” Siegfried nodded his head and allowed the lady to lead the way.

However, he spoke to Leylin without the lady hearing. “She is an example of the high-grade goods that Gersi’s Chamber of Commerce is offering. If you’re interested, you can apply to purchase a few of them later. The chamber is rather generous to the newcomers’ needs…”

“A slave at the level of an acolyte?” Leylin was in shock. This level of a slave was much better than the ones appearing in the Nightless City on the south coast.

Back in Nightless City, Leylin, who was a rank 1 Magus, had only managed to purchase a level 3, old geezer acolyte who was nearing the end of his life.

Evidently, even though both of them were level 3 acolytes, a charming lady would definitely command a higher price than a dying old geezer.

The passage was rather short, and after a couple minutes, they soon reached the end.

After opening the door, Leylin was brought into a great hall.

The light of multiple sun stones penetrated through the crystals in the four corners of the hall, illuminating every corner of the hall.

At this moment, Magi were seated in different circles while chatting in soft voices.

Upon their tables were several green fruits and drinks. Apart from that, many delicacies that were unknown to Leylin were placed there for the Magi’s taking, yet very few bothered to taste them.

“Come! I’ll bring you to see some of my friends!”

After looking around, Siegfried eyes lit up after he noticed a group of red haired Magi sitting in one of the circles, and he promptly dragged Leylin over to them.

“Here! These are the Magi from the Earth Fire Association, and they are also my friends! As for him, this is Mister Leylin, a wandering Magus who had recently come to our eastern capital…”

Siegfried made the introductions on both sides, and Leylin smiled and sent his greetings to the group of Magi.

Together with Leylin’s disposition as a noble and his increased charisma due to the fact that he was a Warlock, he very soon managed to break the ice and began to mingle with them.

Chapter 318: Research and Experiment

Meanwhile, a magic crystal was tossed onto the table.

Leylin kept the Icy Jade Scorpion’s Breath in his palm with no intentions of returning it.

“Is it just an experiment?”

The purple-haired Magus said with a grin. The magic crystal on the table flew into her hands, leaving behind a flickering black afterimage.

Leylin merely looked at her with a vacant stare, as if what he had said was the truth.

“Alright then!” The female Magus elegantly raised her finger, on which her fingernail had been painted with the red sap of a daffodil, and kept the magic crystal.

“I’m Celine! You can contact me in the future for more information regarding the Icy Jade Scorpion. This is my secret imprint!”

She then passed her secret imprint, which looked like a purple daffodil, to Leylin.

Leylin nodded and left the area, and right after that, a plump Magus walked up to Celine and began to chat with her earnestly.

“Leylin, my friend! Where are you going?”

At this moment, Siegfried strolled up to where he was.

“You came at the right time. Do you know who that purple haired female Magus is?” Leylin pointed at the female Magus who occasionally covered her mouth and giggled while conversing animatedly with the plump Magus.

“Oh! That’s Celine, the inheritor of a small guild. Although the guild’s strength isn’t much, she is a famous beauty of the eastern capital! However, she’s extremely crafty, and many Magi who have harboured designs on her have suffered. She’s not someone you’d want to provoke…”

Siegfried looked at Leylin before grinning. “Why? Are you interested in her?”

“No! We just had some dealings previously.”

After listening to Siegfried’s explanation, he was even more sure that Celine was not a simple woman. The grip he had on the box unconsciously tightened.

However, the Icy Jade Scorpion’s Breath was paramount to his path as a Warlock, so he absolutely could not miss this chance.

“It seems like I’ll have to play with this vixen for a while!”

Leylin smiled as he glanced at Celine.

……

In the eastern capital, within the villa that Leylin bought.

After Baelin’s silent farewell, only Leylin was left as the sole occupant of the grand villa. As Leylin had not bought any slaves, it felt rather empty in here.

At this moment, Leylin had separately constructed a concealed tunnel in the underground cellar.

At the end of the tunnel was a spacious underground lab, at the centre of which was a silver metal experimental desk with test-tubes lying on top of it. All of these things were items that Leylin had brought along with him.

“What a strange item!”

At this moment, Leylin used silver tweezers and held the Icy Jade Scorpion’s Breath as blue light shined in his eyes.

With the aid of the microscopic analysing abilities of the A.I. Chip, the surface on the icy shard continuously enlarged, finally revealing a strange rune with six sides.

Chilliness churned and emanated from this strange rune.

[Beep! The analysis of the components of the Icy Jade Scorpion’s Breath is complete! Creating matrixes and images! Beginning simulation of the experiments on bloodline!]

Soon, the A.I. Chip’s voice intoned.

“Let’s begin!” Leylin inhaled deeply.

[Authorisation received. Beginning the simulation of experiment on bloodline!] The A.I. Chip worked on the data. Leylin’s eyes blurred as he seemed to enter a different dimension. He could vaguely make out a translucent human figure with purple blood running through their veins.

[Injecting the Icy Jade Scorpion’s Breath!] With the A.I. Chip’s voice, two thin metal needles pierced the humanoid figure at the shoulders, and images then showed a strange white liquid flowing into the body.

*Huala!* Once the Icy Jade Scorpion’s Breath had entered the body, it frothed as if hot oil had met with icy water, creating a very strong reaction.

The experimented-on body began to shake violently, and the numbers which represented the data of the figure changed wildly, almost turning into a blur.

[Blood flow and pressure are increased, and burden on the body is multiplied by five!]

From time to time, the A.I. Chip would update and interpret the new figures for Leylin.

“Begin the radiation of energy particles! Stabilise the vitality within!” Leylin ordered once again.

Soon, black Dark elemental energy particles began to emanate from the experimental body, and under such radiation, the body slowly began to stabilise.

Finally, the experimental body returned to its original state, and the purple blood in the body continued to flow, just like wine inside a glass.

The main difference was that the blood had dulled a little and become darker.

[Warlock’s bloodline emotional stability experiment was successful! Estimated time for suppressing the core emotional waves: 345 days, 13 hours.] The A.I Chip gave an accurate analysis of the experiment.

“If the dosage is increased, could it prevent any troubles in the future?” Leylin asked the A.I. Chip.

[Data is insufficient. Analysing the data’s probabilities…] The A.I. Chip once again went into a computing mode.

Only after five hours had passed did the A.I. Chip come up with a reply. [Success rate is 67%. Requires more high-level Icy Jade Scorpion’s Breath.]

“As expected! This kind of Icy Jade Scorpion’s Breath can really cure problems with Warlocks’ emotions.”

Leylin’s eyes shone brightly with happiness.

Although the ancient bloodline Warlocks had powerful physiques and magic capabilities, it was very difficult for them to advance.

However, this was not the main reason why the Warlock inheritance declined!

As a result of their access to powerful ancient bloodlines, a Warlock would also inherit the intact genes—which were deeply imbued with tyrannical and terrifying emotions—of ancient predators.

Because of this, a Warlock’s personality was often irascible, and they were quick-tempered, which was a fatal flaw in the Magus world.

No matter how powerful one was, what was the point in having such power if one could not control their own spirit?

Therefore, the calm and rational Magi could pass on their legacies. However, there were no traces of Warlocks on the south coast and Twilight Zone; perhaps only the central continent had some of the legacies left behind by Warlocks.

“Icy Jade Scorpion!”

Leylin quickly sorted out all the information he had related to this organism.

After being told the name of this crystal, Leylin began an intensive study on the characteristics, habitats, capabilities, etc. of this organism, and gathered all of the relevant data.

“Icy Jade Scorpion, a high energy organism that reaches the might of a rank 1 Magus in its adult stages. In search of fertile lands, they often reside in icy caves! Legend has it that they came from another world back in ancient times, and after entering the Twilight Zone, they underwent some evolutionary changes. Only the special radiation reflected from certain types of topaz are able to sustain their lives and reproduction capabilities. Their crystallised breath is known to have stimulating effects on certain high-grade meditation techniques.”

This was a brief summary of all the information Leylin had gathered.

The icy cave’s resources had already been monopolised by several guilds, and was in the process of being excavated. It would be extremely difficult for Leylin to enter on his own.

“No matter what, I have to obtain the Icy Jade Scorpion’s Breath!” Flames of desire glinted in Leylin’s eyes, “Even if the heavens fall and the earth crumbles, I will not stop under any circumstances!”

Suppressing a bloodline Warlock’s emotional instability proved to be extremely difficult, as even though there were so many ancient Magi, they could only discover ways to suppress it. If not for Leylin having the A.I. Chip and bloodline acting as a reminder, he definitely would not have been able to discover the use of the Icy Jade Scorpion’s Breath this easily.

Leylin did not feel that he would chance upon such a lucky encounter again!

“However, using the Icy Jade Scorpion’s Breath as a suppressant may not work for all Warlocks, and may not even work for others with the Giant Kemoyin Serpent’s bloodline. However, the A.I. Chip managed to find a resource that is able to work specifically for me!”

Leylin’s face was extremely solemn.

There were no remedies to treat the emotional instability of Warlocks. Also, due to the difference in bloodlines, each Warlock had a unique bodily attribute. Hence, Leylin himself was not sure whether the Icy Jade Scorpion’s Breath would be effective.

It was very likely that the Icy Jade Scorpion’s Breath would aid Leylin, but not another Warlock with the Giant Kemoyin Serpent’s bloodline.

In other words, the unique characteristics of this resource made it especially effective for Leylin!

Furthermore, the rise and fall of other Warlocks was of no concern to Leylin! He only cared that the Icy Jade Scorpion’s Breath was useful to him, and that he needed more of it. It would be best if he could find another Icy Jade Scorpion’s Breath of higher quality.

“I’ll have to plan for this! I need a calm and collected mind!”

Leylin looked at the icy shard between the tweezers.

“Through the experimentation on the A.I. Chip, I now know that although the Icy Jade Scorpion’s Breath can suppress my mental fluctuations and allow me to be sane for close to a year, there will also be some side effects. I have to concoct some potions to get rid of these side effects!”

This would not stump Leylin at all. After residing in Four Seasons Garden for such a long time, Leylin was no longer a Potion Master who had just advanced.

The Four Seasons Garden was a large-scaled power that was formed of potion masters. They had various information on all sorts of potions, as well as ideas on concocting ancient potions, and these experiments were not too difficult.

Naturally, Leylin had absorbed all of the information stored within the Four Seasons Garden like a sponge, all while practising his potioneering skills at the same time.

Through various trades and experiments, Leylin estimated that his skills had far surpassed that of his mentor, Professor Kroft, after leaving the Four Seasons Garden, and had even reached the realm of a Potion Grandmaster!

A Potions Grandmaster! Their success rate for brewing high-grade potions was around 30%, and they could even research and try brewing new types of potions on their own!

Chapter 319: Negotiations

There were only a few Potion Masters in the entire south coast, and they were all pursued and worshipped by many major powers.

Hence, Leylin did not dare to expose his attainment in potioneering.

Advancing to rank 2 at his age was already heaven-defying, but if he revealed his skill in potioneering, he would be called not a normal genius, but a freak of nature!

A Potion Master’s progress was not dependent on his theory research—he had to do a great amount of practical work. Only after wasting lots of resources could he get plenty of experience and thus make progress.

Even if Leylin was freakishly talented, he simply could not be promoted to a higher level in potioneering without doing anything.

If many Magi decided to investigate him, the existence of his A.I. Chip might even be exposed!

Because of this, Leylin had always concealed his genuine realm in Potions, choosing to stay silent regarding this.

The most important aspect of a Potions Master was innovation! By relying on their wealth of knowledge and experience, they could improvise formulas and still attain a very high success rate.

Thanks to Leylin’s current attainments in potioneering, he only had to think for a short while before being able to recall several formulas to be used together with Icy Jade Scorpion’s Breath that would negate its side effects.

“En! In order to completely eliminate the side-effects of the Icy Jade Scorpion’s Breath, I’ll need Arrow Frog Venom, Reddish Stony Feces, and the egg of the Black Mountain Goat, and then I’ll be able to start the neutralisation process…”

Leylin eventually selected a formula. “Coincidentally, I have one portion of all of these items!”

Soon after, he was deeply immersed in the brewing process.

The usage of this Icy Jade Scorpion’s Breath concerned the success or failure of eliminating the side effects from his bloodline, and thus, he had to be serious.

……

Two days passed before Leylin emerged from his laboratory.

There were slight differences between his condition from 2 days ago and now. His personality had become colder, and he now gave off an unapproachable aura. His skin had turned softer, and it constantly emitted a jade-like luster.

A chilliness seemed to emit from his black hair, decreasing the surrounding temperature by a few degrees.

After having brewed the potion, Leylin was itching to make use of it and see if it would successfully suppress his bloodline.

The A.I. Chip had already given Leylin definite assurance that while the potion was in effect, even if Leylin was to take part in bloody battles every day, the effects of his bloodline wouldn’t corrupt his rational thinking.

Only now did Leylin have the confidence to research on the Icy Jade Scorpion’s Breath.

“Siegfried! Previously, I asked you to get some intelligence about Celine’s guild. Is there any news on that matter?”

“Celine! I now have some time, so tell me where it is! We can go there directly and talk in person about the matter concerning the Icy Jade Scorpion!”

The first thing Leylin did was send out two short messages using secret imprints.

A few minutes later, he received an answer. A khaki coloured imprint of a mechanical arm shone upon the contact book.

“I had previously gathered some intelligence, and coupled with your generous reward, I have already gotten a better understanding of Nature’s Alliance. I’ll pass on the information to you later.”

Siegfried conveyed some good news to Leylin.

“Thank you! I will come and visit you later.” Leylin smiled.

Compared to Siegfried, Celine’s answer was much simpler. There was a time and a place, and everything else could only be discussed once they reached the place.

“What a shrewd woman!” Leylin evaluated. “I just hope you don’t go and get yourself ensnared too!”

……

“This is the place.” Leylin had arrived in front of an elegant office in the eastern capital.

This building was rather different from the usual structures of the subterranean world, which placed an emphasis on defence. Here, it was extremely majestic and sought to be elegant and pleasing to the eye—it was adorned with all sorts of flowers and plants, while its defence was unbelievably weak.

This contrasting style, along with the top-class luxurious items inside, had attracted the attention of several aristocrats, causing them to rush madly towards this place. However, it implemented a very strict system for its members, and only a limited number of customers were received. The supporter of this place was also extremely firm, and after rejecting the requests of a few aristocratic families, the demand sharply dropped.

Leylin entered this office and began to recall the information Siegfried had given him.

Nature’s Alliance—this was the guild that Celine was in. It was said that this small sized guild had affinities with various plants from another world, and their greenhouse handling of plants and research of these plants were extremely unique and cutting edge.

Furthermore, although the high-grade meditation technique of the Nature Alliance did not have strong fighting abilities, it was extremely useful in playing the role of support. Furthermore, the training in this technique allowed the practitioner to permanently change their appearance slightly, turning them into handsome men and pretty ladies that would be able to attract pursuit from the opposite sex.

Lastly, the Magi that graduated from these guilds were completely different from traditional Magi with their stubbornness and unwillingness to communicate with others. Most of them were intelligent, capable, and extremely adept at socialising. They had quite a good reputation outside, and even had a good relationship with other small guilds.

This was all the information Siegfried had gathered regarding the guild behind Celine.

Leylin had also found much valuable information from within. “Changing their appearance, being good at socialising, having a powerful backing… It looks like the high-grade meditation technique of Nature’s Alliance can’t directly increase one’s strength. It might increase one’s charisma or illusory abilities!”

“In addition, they have a good relationship with most small guilds, and a few medium-sized guilds. This means that it’s almost impossible for there to be a rank 2 or higher Magus in charge, else it would have long since become a large-scale guild.”

If Leylin was still a rank 2 Warlock, he would naturally force his way through. However, as he was still sustaining an injury and could not yet use his full power, he had to remain low-key indefinitely and not attract unwarranted attention from Magi who were rank 2 and above. Hence, he had to be patient and enter the game that this wily vixen Celine was playing.

“Hello, Mister! Do you have an appointment?”

As Leylin stepped in, he was respectfully stopped by two maidservants. As they greeted him, Leylin caught a whiff of an extremely simple yet elegant perfume. The two maidservants were dressed extremely well, and they clearly had training in their poise, which could rival that of women in nobility.

However, the few Knights that stood behind the maidservants were enough to cause people to dispel their stray thoughts.

“I have an appointment with Celine!” Leylin answered.

“Lord Leylin, please follow me!” After hearing Celine’s name, the two maidservants’ bodies shuddered slightly and they became more respectful to Leylin.

“Lord Celine is waiting for you in the Horizon Pavilion!”

“Horizon Pavilion? Isn’t that the guestroom that is reserved for people of the highest importance?” A passing noble youth squealed, attracting the attention of passers-by.

“I haven’t heard wrongly, it is the Horizon Pavilion!”

“Exactly what background does this young man have? I haven’t heard anything about a noble paying a visit…”

From a secret hall nearby, all sorts of mutters could be heard. Though their voices were extremely low and quiet, they were still able to travel into Leylin’s ear.

Leylin followed behind the maidservants. Under everyone’s astonished gazes, he headed towards the meeting point designated for the people of highest importance.

After walking through several corridors that were lined with flowers and plants, Leylin finally reached the Horizon Pavilion.

The two maidservants opened the door for Leylin before retreating.

Mist! A layer of thin white mist engulfed the entire room, and in certain corners of the room were the glittering of jewels, making the place more magnificent than before, its picturesque beauty like a place of fantasy.

“En? This mist seems to have a type of tranquil and relaxing effect, which is rather useful for even a regular human’s body!”

Leylin made his deduction after catching a single whiff of it. He even understood the formula to replicate the mist. “It’s a pity that it doesn’t have much of an effect on an official Magus.”

Leylin continued to observe the layout of the Horizon Pavilion.

Green plants took up a huge portion of the room, but the layout was extremely neat and tidy, giving off a feeling of being one with nature.

In the Twilight Zone, green plants were extremely valuable resources, as the light from sun stones was used to grow various fungi and oats. As for vegetables and fruits, they were extremely rare items only for the nobility, much less plants that were only used for aesthetic viewing purposes.

Celine rested on a chair made of vines, seemingly unaware of Leylin’s arrival. Her long, slender legs were revealed, and with that beauty of hers that could cause wars between kingdoms, it was no small temptation, even for an official Magus.

“Ahem.” Leylin lightly coughed.

Following which, the woman lying down was roused in shock, and she proceeded to greet Leylin with a smile, “You’re here, Magus Leylin!”

Each and every movement of hers had elegance in it, and coupled with her voice that was as sweet as a skylark’s, it could leave one intoxicated.

“Hello, Magus Celine!” Leylin gave a perfunctory greeting, the expression on his face neither warm nor cold.

The spiritual force of an official Magus was enough to engulf the space within the room, and when Leylin entered, he did not conceal the aura on his body. It would be strange if this woman did not realise his arrival at all!

However, even if it was done on purpose, Celine’s behaviour could not invoke any hatred. It was as if a little girl was playing a prank, which was not annoying.

However, after witnessing this scene, Leylin was even more sure of the meditation technique she cultivated in.

A superior illusory technique was not only cast on opponents, but also on the user. It would often leave opposing Magi finding it unbearable to inflict pain on them.

It was extremely obvious that Celine’s meditation technique had reached such a level.

Chapter 322: Crystal Mask

Celine herself had only just advanced to become an official Magus.

Compared to Skrill, she was obviously lacking. In addition, all the Magi that were on good terms with Nature’s Alliance were not willing to offend a semi-converted Magus just for this small matter, as with their responsibilities in their respective guilds, they had to consider many more things than most other Magi.

Even if Celine were to win over a few Magi by using her body, those she could win over would at most be regular official Magi that would be much weaker than Skrill.

This was what had allowed Skrill to be so unreserved with his actions.

The smile on Celine’s face gradually became more forced as Skrill made things more difficult for her along every step of the way. At the same time, she also sent warnings to Obo and Ilya, telling them not to do anything that might provoke Skrill.

Obo and Ilya felt as if their hearts had been slashed, as they were only able to clench their fists at this scene.

Celine continued, “The reason I’m here is to welcome a famed professor into my guild. He wishes to enter the icy caves.”

“Famed professor?” Skrill’s brows furrowed.

“Is it Wagrin or Noah? With just their measly amount of strength, they’ll just be a burden…”

Skrill sneered.

“No! The professor we’ve invited is a travelling Magus from the eastern capital. In fact, I myself was rather surprised that he actually agreed to enter Nature’s Alliance.”

A grin surfaced on Celine’s face. “Anyways, he’s already here!”

“Hehe… how powerful can a travelling Magus be? Celine, I hope you didn’t get cheated!” Skrill’s disdainful expression was still on his face. “Hm, he’s here? Where is he?”

“Here!”

Leylin’s cold voice sounded from behind Skrill.

Skrill’s body stiffened. How powerful was this official Magus to be able to escape his detection and sneak behind his back without any trouble?

If not for the greeting, it would have been an easy task for Leylin to kill him with just a spell.

He turned around rigidly to the sight of a young Magus in black standing behind him with a gentle smile on his lips.

However, the aura he was giving off was terrifyingly strong!

The moment he appeared, dense dark elemental particles permeated the area, repelling the elemental particles revolving around Skrill.

“The aura of an elemental essence conversion… A p- peak rank 1 Magus!” Skrill had even begun to stutter.

Oh, great Gaia! A peak rank 1 Magus was basically a tyrant in the Twilight Zone. Why would one choose to enter a small guild such as Nature’s Alliance to be a professor?

Skrill could not make sense of this situation.

“Looks like you aren’t very respectful to the guild master of our Nature’s Alliance, huh?” Leylin stared at this Magus with interest.

“Surgical transplants? Or meditation techniques that can alter the body shape? I really want to explore further with that research…”

Though his words were indirect, Leylin’s gaze was enough to cause Skrill to shiver in trepidation.

“My lord, you’re such a joker! We of the Eight-Claw Spider Guild and Nature’s Alliance have always been friendly with each other, so why would I be trying to make things difficult for guild master Celine? Haha… haha…”

Skrill bowed towards Leylin, lowering his head and smiling apologetically.

“Is that so?” Leylin shot Celine a glance.

“Yes, Lord Leylin!” Celine glared coldly at Skrill until an imploring look appeared in his eyes, and then spoke.

“In that case, go back first. I still have some matters that I wish to discuss with Celine!” Leylin instructed.

“Of course, of course. Many thanks, my lord!” Skrill immediately ran back to the fort as if he had been granted an official pardon, not daring to overstep his boundaries.

“Celine! It looks like your Nature’s Alliance isn’t doing that well.”

Leylin looked at Celine, and then slightly eyed the two level 3 acolytes, both of whom were gradually flushing red.

“My apologies!” Celine gave a wry smile.

“Ever since my mentor passed away, we of Nature’s Alliance have not seen anyone advance to an official Magus in a long time. All that’s left is me working alone, which has caused our situation to go downhill. However, with my lord joining us, I’m sure the situation will improve.”

A peak rank 1 Magus was the trump card of middle-scaled guilds. With Leylin, Nature’s Alliance would obviously be able to develop more.

“Whatever. However, I hope you remember our arrangement. If not, I won’t actually help you if you cause some trouble that’s difficult to deal with.”

Leylin reminded Celine. What he had agreed on was that in exchange for her high-grade meditation techniques, accumulation of information regarding Magi as well as easy access to the icy cave, he would be a professor in name.

In fact, Leylin would only be joining the Nature’s Alliance in name. Though he had other plans, he did not wish for Celine to use his name to create trouble outside.

“Don’t worry!” Celine guaranteed. She was an intelligent woman and knew not to touch Leylin’s bottom line.

“Obo and Ilya, quick, greet my lord!” She called out to the people behind her.

Upon hearing her words, Obo and Ilya bowed, looking dazed.

“We give our greetings to our lord!”

Their heads were low, and they did not dare to look at Leylin. However, from their voices, their admiration was apparent.

A peak rank 1 Magus! Obo and Ilya had never imagined that such a Magus would appear in Nature’s Alliance.

Now, with a top-notch Magus like Leylin in charge, Nature’s Alliance seemed like it would once again emerge as a top power.

Obo and Ilya were immeasurably emotional. Ever since they were young, they had been taken in by Nature’s Alliance and naturally had developed very deep feelings for the guild, hoping that it would become more powerful.

Even their resentment from Celine almost being snatched away had lowered considerably.

“Alright! Celine, where are the things I wanted?”

Leylin gestured with his hands, getting the level 3 acolytes to leave, and then spoke to Celine.

Seeing that Obo and Ilya were not enough to catch Leylin’s eye, Celine could only sigh in her heart. She then produced a light gold-coloured leaf and a sheet of dark yellow parchment paper.

“This is a map! In the other hand, recorded on this gold leaf is the only high-grade meditation technique that we have: the original Crystal Mask. I hope you can take care of it!”

Celine’s expression was very sincere

This attitude was rather surprising to Leylin.

He immediately took the map and took a look. Within were numerous potholes and markings; it was obvious that Nature’s Alliance had been exploring the icy caves for a long time.

Even so, they had not explored the deepest level of the cave, which went to show the immense size of the cave. This was the reason why Leylin had wanted the map.

Otherwise, wouldn’t it mean that he would need to blindly explore the icy caves for months or even years before he could gather enough of the Icy Jade Scorpion Breath?

“Also, this Crystal Mask?”

Leylin naturally knew the significance of Celine passing down the original high-grade meditation technique to him. To some extent, this was a symbol of Nature’s Alliance. Celine’s actions were like she was handing over much of her authority to Leylin.

In addition, handing out the original meditation technique allowed Leylin to see that she did not do anything suspicious to the technique.

……

Celine was unafraid as she met Leylin’s gaze, her eyes filled with a fervent hope and… pleading?

Leylin pursed his lips and extended his hand to take the gold leaf, and a trace of silver spiritual force entered it.

[Discovery of spiritual force, permission to allow transmission of information?] The A.I. Chip prompted.

“Permission granted!” Under Leylin’s orders, large amounts of data entered his brain, which also answered the question of why Celine had been so generous as to pass him the original.

“There are only two levels to the Crystal Mask?”

Leylin found it hard to believe as he looked at Celine. “Shouldn’t all high-grade meditation techniques have at least four levels?”

In ancient times, high-grade meditation techniques were not just any simple techniques. They represented a route that could allow one to enter the ranks of the Morning Star Magi!

In other words, high-grade meditation techniques had at least four levels of information, allowing Magi to train until they became Morning Star Magi!

“The second half of the technique is lost, my lord!” Celine looked bitter.

“To be honest, most of the high-grade meditation techniques in the Twilight Zone are incomplete. There is no way to advance further.”

After listening to Celine’s narration, Leylin suddenly thought of Siegfried’s meditation technique, Gaia’s Might.

The high-grade technique of the Earth Fire Association seemed to only have three levels, allowing Magi to train until rank 3. There was no another way for them to advance.

“Even in ancient times, high-grade meditation techniques were not staple goods, and there were a few wars in Twilight Zone. Though the inheritances were successfully passed down, we now lack a lot of the information regarding sub-topics and other information.”

Celine explained to Leylin.

“In addition, even though we have two levels of the Crystal Mask, none of the Magi in Nature’s Alliance have successfully trained in both levels. The contents of the second level need to be supplemented with Mirage Crystals from the Fog World, but unfortunately, these materials have been gone from the Twilight Zone for over ten thousand years.”

Seemingly afraid that Leylin would think of this meditation technique as having little value, Celine quickly handed out something else.

“These are the spell models that Nature’s Alliance has been accumulating until now, within which are our research materials on four rank 2 magic spells.”

She produced a crystal ball and passed it to Leylin. “In addition, we can increase our offerings to you to a million magic crystals per year!”

“Rank 2 spells?” Leylin was inwardly exhilarated, but his expression remained stolid. “Don’t worry. I’ve made my promise to you, and I definitely won’t go back on my words.”